<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Podcasts</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Abigail Hilton&apos;s Website]]>" url="http://www.fauness.com/" type="link" text="<![CDATA[Abigail Hilton&apos;s Website]]>" description="<![CDATA[Abbie is an ICU nurse and amateur naturalist. She writes fantasy for children, young adults, &amp; all young at heart.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Website for The Prophet of Panamindorah trilogy]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/TheProphetOfPanamindorah" htmlUrl="http://www.panamindorah.com/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Website of The Prophet of Panamindorah trilogy]]>" description="<![CDATA[A full feed of The Prophet of Panamindorah trilogy.  Including all chapters &amp; the books in pdf format.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Prophet of Panamindorah, Book I Fauns and Filinians]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-prophet-of-panamindorah-book-1/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Prophet of Panamindorah, Book I Fauns and Filinians]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-prophet-of-panamindorah-book-1/" description="<![CDATA[Corry showed up at the orphanage two years ago, unable to remember how he&apos;d gotten there. He spoke a language no one recognized, and he was afraid of cars and planes and computers. Corry can remember snippets of another life, but no matter how hard he tries to remember, it just keeps slipping away. Then one day, he meets a fauness in an orange grove. She&apos;s from a world called Panamindorah, and he can understand her language. In addition, Corry can read a language that no one in Panamindorah has been able to read for three hundred years; has he really been gone that long? Now he must recover his lost memories and rebuild his life, because the person who tried to kill him once is about to try again.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Prophet of Panamindorah, Book II Wolflings and Wizards]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-prophet-of-panamindorah-book-2/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Prophet of Panamindorah, Book II Wolflings and Wizards]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-prophet-of-panamindorah-book-2/" description="<![CDATA[Things have gone horribly wrong for the fauns at the spring festival of Lupricasia. A princess has been kidnapped, and visiting feline dignitaries have been blamed for the kidnapping. Corry, the young wizard shape shifter who saw the kidnapping, has been sent hurdling over a waterfall at a deadly height. Meanwhile the wolfling bandits who unwittingly hold the clues that would explain the kidnapping are about to be discovered by a bounty hunter and his employer, bent on their destruction.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Guild of the Cowry Catchers]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/GuildOfTheCowryCatchers" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Guild of the Cowry Catchers - by Abigail Hilton]]]>" htmlUrl="http://cowrycatchers.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Guild of the Cowry Catchers</h1><h3>Abigail Hilton</h3><p>A story of Pirates and Panamindorah.&nbsp; Among the querulous island kingdoms of Wefrivain, the only unifying power is religion - a  wyvern cult ruled by an eccentric High Priestess.&nbsp; The system is under attack by a gang of pirates called the Guild of the Cowry Catchers who prey on Temple treasure ships.&nbsp; The Temple Police charged with eradicating this menace keep disappearing.&nbsp; Enter Gerard, a young prince, exiled from his small kingdom for rashly marrying the court minstrel.&nbsp; He has been chosen by the High Priestess as the new captain of Police.&nbsp; Gerard is smart, honorable, and a little naive.&nbsp; To break the pirate ring, he must cooperate with a wily, amoral colleague, who has already tried to kill him twice.&nbsp; As Gerard struggles to protect his talented wife, obey his seductive employer, and forge a complicated friendship with his dangerous co-worker, he becomes increasingly aware that the pirates have a legitimate quarrel with the wyverns.&nbsp; Dark secrets lurk in the Temple dungeons, and solving them will cost Gerard far more than his honor.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Guild of the Cowry Catchers, Book I Embers]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-guild-of-the-cowry-catchers-book-1/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Guild of the Cowry Catchers, Book I Embers - A free audiobook by Abigail Hilton]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-guild-of-the-cowry-catchers-book-1/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Guild of the Cowry Catchers, Book I Embers</h1><h3>by Abigail Hilton</h3><p>Among the querulous island kingdoms of Wefrivain, the only unifying power is religion - a  wyvern cult ruled by an eccentric High Priestess.&nbsp; The system is under attack by a gang of pirates called the Guild of the Cowry Catchers who prey on Temple treasure ships.&nbsp; The Temple Police charged with eradicating this menace keep disappearing.&nbsp; Enter Gerard, a young prince, exiled from his small kingdom for rashly marrying the court minstrel.&nbsp; He has been chosen by the High Priestess as the new captain of Police.&nbsp; Gerard is smart, honorable, and a little naive.&nbsp; To break the pirate ring, he must cooperate with a wily, amoral colleague, who has already tried to kill him twice.&nbsp; As Gerard struggles to protect his talented wife, obey his seductive employer, and forge a complicated friendship with his dangerous co-worker, he becomes increasingly aware that the pirates have a legitimate quarrel with the wyverns.&nbsp; Dark secrets lurk in the Temple dungeons, and solving them will cost Gerard far more than his honor.The Guild of the Cowry Catchers is a fullcast audio experience featuring the voices of Nathan Lowell, Norm Sherman, Kim the Comic Book Goddess, Chris Lester, Kimi Alexander, and many more.&nbsp; Cowry Catchers is also an illustrated podcast, with high quality watercolor illustrations available on the website.&nbsp; You may remember Abigail Hilton&apos;s first series, the Prophet of Panamindorah.&nbsp; Cowry Catchers is a darker, grittier story set in the same world.&nbsp; It is not for children.&nbsp; Subscribe, and experience a Panamindorah you&apos;ve never heard before.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
