<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			The Works of: Basil Sands.&nbsp; Podcasts, fiction, novels, &amp; audio dramas.
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Fresh Kills]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/fresh-kills/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Fresh Kills - A free audiobook by Basil Sands and The Authors of The Killzone Blog]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/fresh-kills/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Fresh Kills - A free audiobook</h1><p>Fresh Kills is a podcast collection of original short stories by the authors of the popular literary blog The Kill Zone.&nbsp; Reminiscent of the Twilight Zone, these killer tales vary from the paranormal to the chilling to the just plain scary.&nbsp; Each delivers a finely crafted tale that will keep you clicking through the pages.&nbsp; Contributors to the podcast version include these award winning and best selling authors: John Gilstrap, Michelle Gagnon, James Scott Bell, Kathryn Lilley, John Ramsey Miller, Clare Langley-Hawthorne, Joe Moore and Basil Sands.&nbsp; Originally posted as an ebook at Amazon and Smashwords, the podcast version includes 3 extra stories, not available in print including one by award winning podcast author and narrator Basil Sands.&nbsp; So pop on the ear phones and buckle your seatbelt for a trip to the edge of sanity....it&apos;s going to be a wild ride.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Faithful Warrior]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/faithful-warrior/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Faithful Warrior - A free audiobook by Basil Sands]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/faithful-warrior/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Faithful Warrior</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Basil Sands</h3><p>Pastor Michael Farris was a well loved man.&nbsp; Loving husband and father, Shepherd of his church, Courageous minister to the inner city gangs of Columbus Ohio.&nbsp; He helped people change their lives for the better.&nbsp; But when his peaceful life is suddenly shattered by a senseless drive by shooting, a side of Pastor Farris that almost no one knew comes to the surface...a violent shadow of a life that he had been able to keep secret all these years.&nbsp; As he seeks to right the crimes committed against him he is unexpectedly confronted by a ghost from his past, and Mike Farris suddenly finds himself in a race against the clock to stop an insane terrorist from killing thousands, maybe even millions in one fell swoop.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[In the Shadows]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/in-the-shadows/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[In the Shadows - A free audiobook by Basil Sands]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/in-the-shadows/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>In the Shadows</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Basil Sands</h3><p>A collection of Short Stories by action author Basil Sands.&nbsp; These stories will get your heart racing in thirty minutes or less as you plummet to the depths of human emotion and the desire to protect what is dearest when all hell breaks loose and there is no one there to do anything about it but an Average Joe...or an almost Average Joe.&nbsp; Think of each episode as something like the Twilight Zone, with guns, knives, and whatever the hero can find to defend themselves and their families from the bad guys.&nbsp; These are Basil&apos;s original action novels taken down to single episode bite size chunks that&apos;ll get your blood pressure up on the commute to the office, or while on the treadmill at the gym.&nbsp; From a former Navy Seal, to a dad trying to make things right for his son, to a bunch of twenty something adventurers high on an Alaskan mountain you&apos;ll get the hardcore action you crave.&nbsp; Twice a month, delivered right to your MP3 player.&nbsp; You want action?&nbsp; You want pulse pounding excitement?&nbsp; You want to see the bad guys get their due?&nbsp; Here it is in a way that only a guy named Basil can do.&nbsp; So make sure to put your tray table in the upright and locked position, and fasten your seat belt... it&apos;s going to be a wild ride.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[65 Below]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/65-below/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[65 Below - A free audiobook by Basil Sands]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/65-below/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>65 Below</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Basil Sands</h3><p>After twenty years hunting terrorists under orders to &quot;render harmless&quot;, USMC Master Sergeant Marcus Orlando Johnson, Mojo to his friends, settles into a quiet rural retirement on his childhood home in the Alaskan backwoods.&nbsp; But the idyllic retirement is shattered when Marcus comes across soldiers of America&apos;s staunchest enemy who are about to unleash a nightmarish biological weapon on the world from the most unexpected of places.&nbsp; With the help of his ex-fiancee, the beautiful Korean born State Trooper Lonnie Wyatt, and the chance reunion of his old special operations buddy Harley Wasner, they race to stop a potentially devastating terrorist attack with worldwide implications but even nature is against them as the temperatures plummet to 65 below.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Karl's Last Flight]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/karls-last-flight/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Karl's Last Flight - A free audiobook by Basil Sands]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/karls-last-flight/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Karl's Last Flight</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Basil Sands</h3><p>Karl Alexander had been an adrenaline junky for twenty five years.&nbsp; Whether flying Harriers in the Marines, piloting the shuttle for NASA, or as the chief astronaut for StrataCorp Space Flight his happiness was only found when he hit five Gs.&nbsp; But when a series of minor mishaps sends his ship crashing into the desert of an unknown country, Karl finds a new kind of adrenaline rush as he is swept into a raging torrent of  the world at the edge of war.&nbsp; Spies, insurgents, secret police, and an infamous Saudi millionaire terrorist all threaten to make his next flight, his last.&nbsp; Come and get your fix of hardcore, adrenaline laced action that&apos;ll make your heart race and your muscles tense.&nbsp; Basil Sands brings you the podcast novel that started it all.&nbsp; When you listen, be sure to put your tray table in the upright and locked position and fasten your safety belt... it&apos;s going to be a wild ride.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>

