<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			Blackbird Crow Raven&apos;s Comedy podcast novels.
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Wacky Misadventures of Warble McGorkle]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-wacky-misadventures-of-warble-mcgorkle/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Wacky Misadventures of Warble McGorkle - A free audiobook by Blackbird Crow Raven]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-wacky-misadventures-of-warble-mcgorkle/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Wacky Misadventures of Warble McGorkle</h1><h3>by Blackbird Crow Raven</h3><p>&quot;The Wacky Misadventures of Warble McGorkle&quot; is a picaresque satire that, through the protagonist&apos;s zany antics, pokes fun at the &apos;get rich quick&apos; and &apos;get rich by any means possible&apos; philosophies prevalent in today&apos;s society.Warble McGorkle considers himself a genius.&nbsp; In reality, he is a jumble-headed, paranoid megalomaniac.&nbsp; My novel is the (somewhat darkly) humorous account of his meteoric rise from drifter to President of the United States.&nbsp; Warble and his wife Mary crisscross the U.S.A.&nbsp; at breakneck speed, as Warble endeavors to stay one step ahead of pursuers (most of them imaginary). Everywhere he and Mary go, Warble concocts a cockamamie scheme to get fabulously rich and to propel himself to the pinnacle of society, where his fame--so he reasons, anyway--will make him safe from the forces supposedly arrayed against him.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Zany Time Travels of Warble McGorkle]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-zany-time-travels-of-warble-mcgorkle/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Zany Time Travels of Warble McGorkle - A free audiobook by Blackbird Crow Raven]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-zany-time-travels-of-warble-mcgorkle/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Zany Time Travels of Warble McGorkle</h1><h3>by Blackbird Crow Raven</h3><p>In &apos;The Zany Time Travels of Warble McGorkle&apos; (book II of a trilogy, and the first one recorded), Warble Poundcake McGorkle and his entourage (wife, employees, a sales team, and a canine) travel back in time to revise history.&nbsp; Their meddling in events during American Revolutionary War Times, at Custer&apos;s Last Stand, the Alamo, Woodstock, and  many other pivotal events--as well as a detour to 1st Century Jerusalem to kidnap Jesus (or Judas)--leads to catastrophic consequences for those living in modern times.&nbsp; Among the things Warble and his gang perpetrate are:1. Banishing George Washington to England for inventing the peanut (and thus being responsible for &apos;Peanut Envy&apos;)2. &apos;Helping out&apos; at the Alamo, so that it&apos;s the Mexicans who ultimately get &apos;saddled&apos; with Texas3. Originating Pre-emptive Strikes (umpires calling strikes before the ball is thrown)4. Changing song lyrics at Woodstock to influence the politics and modify the personalities of the concert-goers These are just a few of the outrageous shenanigans that culminate in a climactic scene as the protagonists return to the  present and see what their changes have wrought.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>

