<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>&apos;s audio dramas &amp; podcast novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[&apos;s audio dramas]]>" url="" type="link" text="<![CDATA[Podcast audio dramas from ]]>" description="<![CDATA[Podcast audio dramas from ]]>" />-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Space Casey]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/space-casey/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Space Casey - A free audiobook by Christiana Ellis]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/space-casey/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Space Casey - A free audiobook</h1><p>Some heroines will steal your heart.&nbsp; This one will steal your wallet.&nbsp; In the future, mankind has expanded to fill the solar system, but when a snarky con-woman steals the wrong spaceship, she finds herself stranded in a distant galaxy.&nbsp; She is humanity&apos;s first emissary to a galactic civilization, and all she wants to do is go home.&nbsp; Preferably, without being arrested.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Nina Kimberly the Merciless (Remastered)]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/nina-kimberly-the-merciless/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Nina Kimberly the Merciless (Remastered) - A free audiobook by Christiana Ellis]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/nina-kimberly-the-merciless/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Nina Kimberly the Merciless (Remastered) - A free audiobook</h1><p>She&apos;s on a mission to kill the man who loves her.&nbsp; Why?&nbsp; Because he&apos;s an idiot.&nbsp; Ten years ago, Nina Kimberly the Merciless was cheated out of the life of adventure that she truly deserves.&nbsp; Her father, the fearsome barbarian conqueror Marcus the Merciless, met his first and only defeat at the hands of, well... a gopher hole.&nbsp; Ever since this epic humiliation, she and the rest of the horde have been stuck in the rural backwater kingdom of Langia.&nbsp; Now Francis IX, the idiotic king, has decided that he and Nina should be married.&nbsp; She can&apos;t kill him without starting a succession war, but the alternatives?&nbsp; Eww!&nbsp; Nina has long yearned for a hero to sweep her up on a glorious quest, but Francis&apos; unwanted affections have forced her hand.&nbsp; No more waiting for a quest to find *her*, it&apos;s time to get proactive.&nbsp; She sets off into the big wide world, but the King decides to tag along, complete with a security spell to alert the Kingdom if he&apos;s killed.&nbsp; Nina is forced to swallow her pride and keep him safe... at least until she can find a way to break the spell.&nbsp; But nothing is ever simple in the life of a barbarian princess, and nothing is ever quite what it appears.&nbsp; The dragon is a pacifist (sometimes). The handsome rogue is a con-artist, but who is he conning?&nbsp; And even the wizard has a few surprises in store.&nbsp; While seeking the answer to all her problems, Miss the Merciless discovers that what she&apos;s always wanted may not actually be what she *wants*. *Nina Kimberly the Merciless* is a comic coming of age story filled with magic, mayhem and mercenaries, but mercy?&nbsp; Never.&nbsp; This is a remastered version of the novel, with an all-new higher quality recording.&nbsp; The classic version of Nina Kimberly the Merciless is also available.&nbsp; Nina Kimberly the Merciless is now in print, available for purchase at Amazon.com</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Nina Kimberly The Merciless (Classic)]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/nina-kimberly-the-merciless-classic/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Nina Kimberly The Merciless (Classic) - A free audiobook by Christiana Ellis]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/nina-kimberly-the-merciless-classic/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Nina Kimberly The Merciless (Classic) - A free audiobook</h1><p>She&apos;s on a mission... To kill the man who loves her...Why?&nbsp; Because he&apos;s an idiot.&nbsp; Nina Kimberly The Merciless is the story of a teenage barbarian princess who must rid herself of an obnoxious royal suitor, replace him with a hero, and then grow into her destiny as a...Well, that she hasn&apos;t decided yet. </p>]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast audio drama from ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by .  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
	</body>
</opml>
