<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>David Lee Summers&#039;s Works &amp; Podnovels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[David Lee Summers&#039; Homepage]]>" url="http://www.davidleesummers.com/" type="link" text="<![CDATA[David Lee Summers&#039; Homepage]]>" description="<![CDATA[Homepage &amp; Website for the author David Lee Summers]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[<em>The Cluster Saga&#039;: Prelude</em> - The Pirates of Sufiro]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-pirates-of-sufiro/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Pirates of Sufiro - <em>The Cluster Saga&#039;: Prelude</em> - a free audiobook by David Lee Summers]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-pirates-of-sufiro/" description="<![CDATA[The story of a planet and its people -- of Ellison Firebrandt the pirate captain living in exile; of Espedie Raton, the con-man looking to make a fresh start for himself and his wife on a new world; of Peter Stone, the ruthless bank executive who discovers a fortune and will do anything to keep it; and of the lawman, Edmund Ray Swan who travels to Sufiro seeking the quiet life but finds a dark secret.  It is the story of privateers, farmers, miners, entrepreneurs, and soldiers -- all caught up in dramatic events and violent conflicts that will shape the destiny of our galaxy.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[<em>The Cluster Saga&#039;: Book I</em> - Children of the Old Stars]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/children-old-stars/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[<em>The Cluster Saga&#039;: Book II</em> - Children of the Old Stars - a free audiobook by David Lee Summers]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/children-old-stars/" description="<![CDATA[The Cluster is a vast alien machine that destroys starships indiscriminately in its quest for something or someone.  Commander John Mark Ellis, disgraced and booted out of the service when he fails to save a merchant ship, believes the key to stopping the Cluster is communication.  His mother, Suki Firebrandt Ellis is a historian who believes the very leaders of the galaxy are withholding information about the Cluster.  Clyde McClintlock believes the Cluster is God incarnate, seeking retribution.  G'Liat is an alien warrior whose own starship was destroyed by the Cluster.  All together, they set out to solve the mystery of the Cluster before it finds the object of its quest.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[<em>The Cluster Saga&#039;: Book II</em> - Heirs of the New Earth]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/heirs-of-the-new-earth/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Heirs of the New Earth - <em>The Cluster Saga&#039;: Book II</em> - a free audiobook by David Lee Summers]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/heirs-of-the-new-earth/" description="<![CDATA[The Earth has gone silent. John Mark Ellis and the crew of the Sanson are sent to investigate. When they arrive, they find vast alien machines known as Clusters in orbit. Fearing the worst, they land and discover that the once overcrowded, polluted Earth has become a paradise of sorts. The problem is over half the population is dead or missing and the planet's leaders don't seem to care. As Ellis works to unravel the mystery, sudden gravitational shifts from the galaxy's center indicate something even worse is in the offing. Can Ellis save the galaxy from the heirs of the new Earth?]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a free audiobook by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
