<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Edward G. Talbot&#039;s Works &amp; Podnovels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" url="" type="link" text="<![CDATA[]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Intercast Season One]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/intercast-season-one/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Intercast - A short stories collection edited by Edward G. Talbot]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/intercast-season-one/" description="<![CDATA[In this collection of short stories, Edward G. Talbot provides thrills, chills, laughs, and drama in abbreviated form.&nbsp; If you like bite-sized fiction, allow Talbot and selected guest authors to take you on a ride.&nbsp; The stories are varied, with an emphasis on twists and improbable situations.&nbsp; A talk show appearance gone very wrong. An athlete willing to sacrifice to win.&nbsp; And a strip club bouncer discovering that Heaven isn't what he expected.So sit back, close your eyes, and put on your headphones.&nbsp; And enjoy the stories.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[New World Orders]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/new-world-orders/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[New World Orders - A free Audiobook by Edward G. Talbot]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/new-world-orders/" description="<![CDATA[In the nineteen-sixties, a group of wealthy men concludes that it&#039;s already too late to stop global warming from destroying the planet.&nbsp; But they have a plan to save themselves.Twenty years later, Jack Crowley and Jim Patterson stumble onto the conspiracy, and every answer they find is accompanied by more questions - and more deaths.Jack is a former idealist, turned cynical by his years working as a New York tabloid editor.&nbsp; But his enthusiasm returns as he looks into the work of a NASA scientist who tells Jack about cover-ups at the space agency.&nbsp; Jim is a detective with little patience for conspiracy nuts.&nbsp; But he hates loose ends, and is unable to let go of the inconsistencies in another suspicious NASA death.&nbsp; Soon, his investigation leads him to Jack, and they join forces.As Jack and Jim dig deeper, they are targeted by the type of killers that don&#039;t usually miss.&nbsp; From Washington to Las Vegas to the Middle East, they manage to stay one step ahead of their pursuers in a race to expose the truth, and maybe, just maybe, save the world.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Flatlands]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/flatland/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Flatlands - A free audiobook by Edward G. Talbot]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/flatland/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Math. Geometry. Physics. Violence? Is this the same book I read in school? Yep.</p><p>One of the joys of rediscovering old books is that they still have the ability to surprise, even shock.</p><p>&quot;If my poor Flatland friend retained the vigour of mind which he enjoyed when he began to compose these Memoirs, I should not now need to represent him in this preface, in which he desires, fully, to return his thanks to his readers and critics in Spaceland ... But he is not the Square he once was. Years of imprisonment, and the still heavier burden of general incredulity and mockery, have combined with the thoughts and notions, and much also of the terminology, which he acquired during his short stay in Spaceland. ...&quot;</p><p>You may remember Flatland as a clever children's story about squares and triangles and such living a happy life in a sheet of paper, a story about math and geometry and such. No, not so much.</p><p>Sure, there's no Adult Language or Sex. But there's plenty of violence. I recall recording one scene wherein over 120,000 people were stabbed to death, torn to pieces and eaten by their fellow Flatlanders. Yes. Way.</p><p>Assuming you consider Isoceles Triangles people. In Flatland, they are. Mostly.</p>]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - A free audiobook by Edward G. Talbot]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
