<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			Emerian Rich, aka: Emmy Z. Madrigal&appos;s podcasts &amp; podcast novels.
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Night's Knights Vampire Podnovel published on Podiobooks.com]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/nights-knights/feed/" text="<![CDATA[Night&#39;s Knights - a free podcast novel by Emerian Rich]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/nights-knights/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Three vampires challenge each other to create the perfect offspring.&nbsp; Beings from another realm attempt to orchestrate things to serve their purpose.&nbsp; Luckily a tough street chick named Jespa is there to kick some immortal butt.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Night's Knights Vampire Podnovel published on Mevio.com]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.mevio.com/feeds/vamp.xml" text="<![CDATA[Night&#39;s Knights - a free podcast novel by Emerian Rich]]>" htmlUrl="http://vamp.mevio.com/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Three vampires challenge each other to create the perfect offspring.&nbsp; Beings from another realm attempt to orchestrate things to serve their purpose.&nbsp; Luckily a tough street chick named Jespa is there to kick some immortal butt.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Sweet Dreams]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/sweet-dreams/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Sweet Dreams]]>" htmlUrl="http://sweetdreamsnovel.com/" description="<![CDATA[At twenty-one, Rob Malloy is a successful San Francisco entertainment manager and has achieved more than most men twice his age. Wealthy and famous for closing any deal, he may seem to have everything a man could want. However, he longs to meet a woman he can share his life with. Victoria Knox is a poor eighteen year old student who dreams of nothing but becoming a singer. Dating is the last thing on her mind when she accidentally bumps into Rob in an airport gift shop on Christmas day. Instant attraction draws them to one another, despite their different lifestyles. Looking as if he stepped out of a GQ ad, Rob exudes high class and money. Victoria is convinced he is too good for her, but Rob is immediately attracted to how she freely shares her innocently opinionated views. He likes her down to earth personality that is such a breath of fresh air compared to the gold digging socialites he is normally plagued with.In this love story, Rob introduces Victoria to a high society world where she meets the rich and famous. For the first time she dares to believe her dream of becoming a singing star is possible through Rob&apos;s industry connections. However, Rob is different from anyone she has ever met and she fears she won&apos;t fit into his world. Her mother adds fuel to Victoria&apos;s misgivings by questioning Rob&apos;s intentions. Though sincere, Rob may have trouble convincing his country club parents that Victoria is a proper match. Join Rob and Victoria as they battle social class lines, parental disapproval and ghosts from their pasts to prove that their love is meant to last.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Star Struck]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/star-struck/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Star Struck - A free audiobook by Emmy Z. Madrigal]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/star-struck/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Star Struck</h1><h3>by Emmy Z. Madrigal</h3><p>This is the second book in the Sweet Dreams series.&nbsp; Three days is not very long, but to Victoria, who&apos;s been away from her new love Rob Malloy, it seems like forever.&nbsp; Returning from Colorado, Victoria reconnects with her friends, finding one particular friend isn&apos;t too happy about her having a high society boyfriend.&nbsp; Imagine waking from a nap to find your favorite boy band star sitting in the chair across from you.&nbsp; That&apos;s what happens to Cynthia Porter.&nbsp; She can hardly believe she isn&apos;t dreaming when Derek Montgomery shows up at Rob&apos;s apartment.&nbsp; The initial shock gives way to real mutual admiration as they spend time together.&nbsp; Unfortunately, it seems Derek&apos;s old girlfriend haunts him too much to let go.&nbsp; Will Cynthia ever find a guy who is completely into her?&nbsp; Or will she constantly be the friend and counselor to these screwed up males?&nbsp; Music provided by: Neil MacPherson, Brad Wait and Pleasure Trip.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[True Love]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/true-love/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[True Love - A free audiobook by Emmy Z. Madrigal]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/true-love/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>True Love</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Emmy Z. Madrigal</h3><p>This is the third book in the Sweet Dreams series.Victoria has an awesome boyfriend, great friends, and her singing career on its way.&nbsp; Are the nightmares she&apos;s been having a warning, or are they just a symptom of her subconscious second-guessing the happiness she is feeling for the first time in her life?&nbsp; Rob gives her even more good news as he whisks her off on a weekend trip planned completely in her honor.&nbsp; Unbeknownst to him, someone from her past has another agenda designed to ruin her for good.&nbsp; Will Rob be able to save her from the devious plans of an obsessed mastermind?Boy band star Derek Montgomery is falling for Cynthia Porter in a big way, but she&apos;s not sure she wants anything to do with him.&nbsp; Competing with the memories of Derek&apos;s ex and tabloid rumors, Cynthia would rather let go of him than deal with all the drama.&nbsp; Can Derek prove to her that he&apos;s serious and that she&apos;s not just the rebound girl?&nbsp; Find out in True Love.Music provided by: Brad Wait.Cover model: Heidi Kaden</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>

