<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>&#039;s podcast novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Interview for a Wizard]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/interview-for-a-wizard/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Interview for a Wizard - a free podcast novel by J.A. Areces]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/interview-for-a-wizard/" description="<![CDATA[On Halloween night, the greatest vacation spot in the world is about to be scared to death.&nbsp; A dangerous and mad wizard has escaped from jail, and there is no one who can identify him.&nbsp; With only seven days left before Halloween, Jesse and wizard special agent Ch-U-Ch race to solve the mystery, but time is quickly running out.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Secret Society of Seven Sorcerers]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-secret-society-of-seven-sorcerers/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Secret Society of Seven Sorcerers - a free podcast novel by J.A. Areces]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-secret-society-of-seven-sorcerers/" description="<![CDATA[Nicholas Fidgewidge returns to claim Lord Bane&#039;s crystal ball causing Jesse to seek the wizard Ch-U-Ch&#039;s aid.&nbsp; Meanwhile, the remaining sorcerer&#039;s are being scared to death, and with Raven Claw out of jail the chase begins.&nbsp; However, things quickly become very complicated when the wizard&#039;s two teenage boys get involved.&nbsp; On Halloween night, Lord Alex will become the next Dark Sorcerer even if it means destroying everyone who knows of his initiation.&nbsp; Follow the wizard Ch-U-Ch, his cousin Ana and Jesse into the dark world of the Society as they try to prevent Lord Alex from joining the Circle of Seven and achieving a greater goal, to obtain the secret&#039;s of Lord Bane&#039;s crystal ball.&nbsp; On Halloween night, everything must remain a secret at any price.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Sorcerer's Secret]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-sorcerers-secret/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Sorcerer's Secret - a podcast novel by J. A. Areces]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-sorcerers-secret/" description="<![CDATA[Book 3 of the Salem Concord begins where The Secret Society of Seven Sorcerers left off.&nbsp; In the Sorcerer's Secret, Jesse ventures deeper into the wizarding world and discovers that the Wizardry must live a secret.&nbsp; A secret that history altered.&nbsp; A secret that FOLK must never learn.&nbsp; It's up to Jesse and the secret wizard agent Ch-U-Ch to stop the forces that are trying to breach the Salem Concord and cause another Witch War.&nbsp; Meanwhile, Andrew and Brendan are learning that being a wizard in a FOLK world has its consequences.&nbsp; As their secret is revealed, they learn that they're placing their friends lives in danger.&nbsp; It's up to them and Chief Fabiano to stop Lord Alex from obtaining two of the most powerful magical items in the world.&nbsp; Time is running out, and on Halloween, one cry will be heard throughout the land, &quot;The Witches are Coming!&quot;]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title//feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by J. A. Areces]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title//" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
