<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>&apos;s podcast novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[J. C.  Hutchins' uber feed.  New Fiction And Author Updates]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/jchutchins?formt=xml" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://jchutchins.net/site/consume/" text="<![CDATA[J.C. Hutchins: New Fiction And Author Updates]]>" description="<![CDATA[You&pos;ll receive the latest announcements about new projects and news from the author, plus sneak peeks at shiny new fiction as it&pos;s released. There’s even a chance you&pos;ll experience other authors&pos; fiction here, as J.C. likes to share the spotlight with his colleagues. Always timely, this podcast delivers the latest and greatest from J.C. Hutchins.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[UltraCreatives Interview Series]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/UltraCreatives" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.ultracreatives.com/" text="<![CDATA[J.C. Hutchins&apos; UltraCreatives Interview Series:  Conversations with New Media movers and shakers.]]>" description="<![CDATA[In 2008, J.C. Hutchins launched “UltraCreatives,” a series in which he interviewed entrepreneurs, filmmakers, entertainers and novelists. In-depth but casual, these conversations explore the creative spirit in all its forms. While this podcast is currently on hiatus, there are more than 20 interviews to enjoy. UltraCreatives received a Podcast Peer award for best Arts & Entertainment programming. Click the image on the left to visit UltraCreatives.com, and subscribe to nearly 25 hours of free audio content.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[7th Son: 7 Days (Prequel Anthology) - A free audiobook by J.C. Hutchins]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/7th-son-7-days/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[7th Son: 7 Days (Prequel Anthology) - A free audiobook by J.C. Hutchins]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/7th-son-7-days" description="<![CDATA[7th Son: 7 Days is a audio prequel anthology to J.C. Hutchins&apos; thriller novel, 7th Son: Descent. Set two weeks before Descent&apos;s extraordinary events, the series reveals the lives of seven seemingly unrelated men, and their everyday challenges.&nbsp; In the world of 7th Son, &quot;everyday challenges&quot; are far from ordinary. Each of these seven stories stars a unique John Michael Smith. Witness criminal profiler Dr. Mike&apos;s quest to hunt an unstoppable serial killer. Watch blue-collar musician John realize a lifelong dream. Ride shotgun with USMC captain Michael on a dangerous black ops mission in the Middle East. Behold the worldwide influence of deranged computer hacker Kilroy2.0 ... and more.7th Son: 7 Days represents the creative reboot of the popular 7th Son thriller series. Designed to tightly integrate with 7th Son: Descent&apos;s print novel storyline, 7 Days is a perfect introduction to the 7th Son universe. Meet the Beta clones ... before they knew they were clones.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[7th Son: Book One - Descent (The Beta Version) - A free audiobook by J.C. Hutchins]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/7th-son-book-one---descent/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[7th Son: Book One - Descent (The Beta Version) - A free audiobook by J.C. Hutchins]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/7th-son-book-one---descent/" description="<![CDATA[Three weeks ago, the U.S. president was murdered by a four-year-old boy.Today, seven men stare at each other in a locked conference room. Kidnapped and brought to this underground facility, the strangers are sitting in silence, thunderstruck. Despite minor physical differences, they all appear to be the same man, with the same name ... and the same childhood memories.Unwitting participants in a secret human cloning experiment, these seven &quot;John Michael Smiths&quot; have been gathered by their creators for one reason -- to capture the mastermind behind the president&apos;s assassination.Their target? The man they were cloned from; the original John Michael Smith, code-named John Alpha.Soon our heroes -- John, Jack, Michael, Kilroy2.0 and the others -- realize the president&apos;s murder was merely a prologue to Alpha&apos;s plans. As the mystery deepens and the implications of Alpha&apos;s scheme are slowly revealed, the clones decide to stand against John Alpha. The outcome will unearth a conspiracy larger than they could have ever imagined.Descent is the first novel in J.C. Hutchins&apos; 7th Son thriller trilogy.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[7th Son: Book Two - Deceit (The Beta Version) - A free audiobook by J.C. Hutchins]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/7th-son-book-two---deceit/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[7th Son: Book Two - Deceit (The Beta Version) - A free audiobook by J.C. Hutchins]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/7th-son-book-two---deceit/" description="<![CDATA[Two days ago, seven human clones -- John, Michael, Father Thomas, Dr. Mike, Jonathan, Jack and Kilroy2.0 -- were torn away from their &quot;normal&quot; lives to stop a ruthless plot created by their progenitor, a man code-named John Alpha. Their quest was a descent into conspiracy, violence and death.The clones were successful in their mission, but victory was not without its price.As 7th Son: Book Two - Deceit begins, the Beta clones are demoralized, reeling from their loss ... and about to learn that John Alpha&apos;s plans are far from over.To prevent the next phase of Alpha&apos;s plan, John, Kilroy2.0, and the others must unearth more dark secrets about the government project from which they were spawned. They will experience the horrors of betrayal, and race cross-country to track John Alpha.And they will finally realize the scope of Alpha&apos;s wrath -- the bloodshed the clones have witnessed is merely a prelude to the world-rending destruction to come. Unless they can stop it first.Deceit is the second novel in J.C. Hutchins&apos; 7th Son thriller trilogy.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[7th Son: Book Three - Destruction (The Beta Version) - A free audiobook by J. C. Hutchins]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/7S3-Destruction/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[7th Son: Book Three - Destruction (The Beta Version) - A free audiobook by J. C. Hutchins]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/7S3-Destruction/" description="<![CDATA[As day four in the 7th Son adventure begins, John Alpha&apos;s quest for anarchy and genocide enters its final stage.At every turn, the global terrorist has been triumphant. The world is reeling from a nuclear attack. An unprecedented energy crisis is upon us. Alpha himself has exclusive access to the White House, and secret weapons primed to propel his conspiracy into the endgame. The goal: planetary chaos.Amidst this turmoil, the 7th Son&apos;s four surviving Beta Clones -- John, Father Thomas, Kilroy2.0 and Jack -- must defy their creators and hunt Alpha on their terms. Their mission: to stop the greatest assassination plot in history. The secrets John and his brothers discover will press them toward a final battle with their progenitor ... a battle in which the clones are outgunned, outnumbered and out of time.Alliances will be made. Heroes will die. The end is nigh.Destruction is the final novel in the J.C. Hutchins&apos; 7th Son thriller trilogy.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Personal Effects: Sword of Blood - A free podcast novel by J.C. Hutchins]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/personal-effects-sword-of-blood/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Personal Effects: Sword of Blood - A free audiobook by J.C. Hutchins]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/personal-effects-sword-of-blood/" description="<![CDATA[Brinkvale Psychiatric Hospital art therapist Zach Taylor is endlessly curious, perhaps to a fault. When his cheerful elderly patient Gertrude &quot;Spindle&quot; Spindler completes her latest quilt and informs Zach that a 30-year-old &quot;grand design of nine&quot; has just concluded, Zach&apos;s curiosity is piqued ... and he soon embarks on a quest to unwind the meaning of the woman&apos;s cryptic phrase.He isn&apos;t expecting a descent into a world filled with mystery and ruthless subcultures -- and he isn&apos;t expecting to be haunted by Spindle&apos;s coy clues. What is The Great Blade of Blood? What are The Charred? What is the grand design of nine? And who is the dark-skinned stranger stalking Zach at every turn, threatening his life?The answers may lie in Spindle&apos;s granddaughter, a willowy self-proclaimed psychic named Hen. But Zach soon discovers that Hen may be crazier than the patients he treats ... and the treasure he&apos;s pursuing may be more dangerous -- and deadly -- than he ever imagined.Personal Effects: Sword of Blood is a podcast-exclusive novella written by J.C. Hutchins, author of the 7th Son trilogy. It is a prequel to Hutchins&apos; print novel debut, Personal Effects: Dark Art.]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by .  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
