<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>JP O'Donnell&apos;s podcast novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by JP O'Donnell » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by JP O'Donnell.  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Fatal Gamble - A free audiobook by JP O'Donnell]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/fatal-gamble/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Fatal Gamble - a free podcast novel by JP O'Donnell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/fatal-gamble/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Twenty years ago, a group of doctors formed a partnership to build a medical office plaza in Massachusetts. While it wasn't the most above-board deal ever made, the doctors have found continued profit and success--until now.</p><p<Someone wants the doctors dead, and he or she has already succeeded in murdering two of them. The identity of the killer remains unknown. Is it a madman with a vendetta against the medical profession, a small-time bookie seeking revenge for a shady real estate deal, or a disgruntled former construction manager who was unjustly fired?</p><p<The widow of one of the slain doctors has a clue--but she's too afraid to tell the police. She hires Boston private investigator Daniel Gallagher to help track down the murderer. But as Gallagher begins to unravel the mystery, he finds himself entangled in a web of danger and political intrigue.</p><p<With the stakes growing higher, Gallagher faces a growing threat to keep him quiet before he reveals the damaging truth. But when push comes to shove, has Gallagher made a Fatal Gamble?</p>]]>"/>
			<outline title="<![CDATA[Deadly Codes - A free audiobook by JP O'Donnell]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/deadly-codes/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Deadly Codes - A free audiobook by JP O'Donnell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/deadly-codes/" description="<![CDATA[In this podiobook: Deadly Codes: A Gallagher Novel is the award-winning sequel to Fatal Gamble. Daniel Cormac Gallagher, Jr., a Boston private eye, is hired to investigate the death of Jennifer Clark, tragically killed in a car bombing in her own driveway.  Gallagher has been commissioned by Jeanne Campbell, Jennifer&apos;s twin sister, to find a mysterious woman--Jennifer&apos;s secret lesbian lover who vanished immediately after the bombing.  While the authorities continue to pursue their suspicions that the terrorist act may have been intended for Jennifer&apos;s husband, Bill, who holds a top-secret position in the counter-intelligence division of the National Security Agency, Jeanne reveals intricate details to Gallagher that intrigue him enough to take on the case.  While Gallagher begins searching for the missing woman, he has no idea that a bounty has been placed on his own head.  Two hired gunmen are plotting to kill him.  Gallagher&apos;s search takes him to Washington D.C. where he discovers that the car bombing is only a backdrop to a complex, treasonous scheme to sell code-breaking formulas to a hostile enemy nation.  As the violent mystery unravels, Gallagher finds himself under deadly attack from two shocking but powerful forces -- one he knows and another he never expects.]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ - A free audiobook by JP O'Donnell » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by JP O'Donnell.  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
