<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>The Works of Jack Mangan: podcasts, podcast novels, and audio fiction.</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Spherical Tomi: A Novel of Despair - A free audiobook by Jack Mangan]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/spherical-tomi-a-novel-of-despair/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Spherical Tomi: A Novel of Despair - A free audiobook by Jack Mangan]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/spherical-tomi-a-novel-of-despair/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Spherical Tomi: A Novel of Despair - by Jack Mangan</h1><p>  &quot;Star Wars is over.&nbsp; Star Trek is dead.&nbsp; In Spherical Tomi, Jack Mangan has opened up a new frontier.&quot;- Ernest Hogan, author of Smoking Mirror BluesA top-secret AI project.&nbsp; A deadly power struggle between warlords.&nbsp; Tomi was once lead combat programmer for the Shogun Ryogi, on the front lines of his conflict against President William the Black of Cerberus.&nbsp; When she failed to prevent William from killing the samurai she loved, she abandoned all sides, all loyalties, all hope.&nbsp; In her fury, Tomi destroyed the Greatship, Hades IV, and almost everyone onboard.&nbsp; Almost everyone. . .William the Black escaped with his life.&nbsp; She now hides out in a remote monastery, awaiting the day when she can kill the three she holds responsible for the death of her samurai:  William, Ryogi, and herself. . .With her real body in exile, Tomi&apos;s consciousness inhabits a deteriorating clone body on a satellite around Cerberus.&nbsp; She&apos;s lived and worked incognito in orbit for almost three years now, monitoring the planet&apos;s subspace debris cleanup.&nbsp; But some histories will not stay buried.&nbsp; Tomi again finds herself in the crossfire when Ryogi&apos;s forces ambush the Presidential shuttle in her sector.&nbsp; Ryogi&apos;s samurai have pirated remote control of her satellite&apos;s store of dormant clone bodies; his combat programmers fight her for the station&apos;s computers, while the planet&apos;s extrasphere swarms with deadly smart-mines.&nbsp; Will she be able to protect the President&apos;s shuttle to secure her own vengeance?&nbsp; Will she be able to hold her satellite together?&nbsp; Or will Tomi abandon it all and give in to despair?&quot;Spherical Tomi&quot; is an action-packed tale of deception, revenge, redemption, fragmented identity, and the limitations of the human and artificial mind.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Duel of the Fates]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/duel-of-the-fates/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Duel of the Fates - A free audiobook by Jack Mangan]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/duel-of-the-fates/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Duel of the Fates - A free audiobook</h1><p>As originally heard on the Dragon Page Wingin&apos; It!&nbsp; Podcast: Duel of the Fates assembles highly diverse, iconic combatants from across the wide universe of speculative fiction and pits them head-to-head in meaningless contests of 5 silly categories.&nbsp; Hear!&nbsp; An exhibition duel between Darth Vader vs.&nbsp; Gandalf!&nbsp; Witness!&nbsp; Another exhibition of, um, something, between Molly (from Neuromancer) and Batman!&nbsp; Behold!&nbsp; The bracketed 8-character elimination tournament! 1) Tomi (from Spherical Tomi)2) Spider-Man3) Captain James T. Kirk4) Ash (from Evil Dead)5) Godzilla6) Starbuck from the original Battlestar Galactica (Dirk Benedict)7) Harry Potter8) HAL-9000 (from 2001) Who has the best look?&nbsp; Who has more Love Prowess?&nbsp; Who&apos;d win in a fight?&nbsp; Who&apos;d be more fun at a party?&nbsp; Relive the mayhem -- or experience this popular series for the first time -- as author Jack Mangan examines the quirks, strengths, and weaknesses of these notable SF characters (along with one of his own). There are quite a few surprises as characters are eliminated, and ultimately, a winner is crowned Duel of the Fates champion.&nbsp; You&apos;ll laugh, you&apos;ll think, you&apos;ll cry (if you&apos;re a bit of a nut), you&apos;ll disagree at times; you&apos;ll look at these characters in new and different ways.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Duel of the Fates, Tournament 2 - A free audiobook by Jack Mangan]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/duel-of-the-fates-tournament-2/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Duel of the Fates, Tournament 2 - A free audiobook by Jack Mangan]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/duel-of-the-fates-tournament-2/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Duel of the Fates, Tournament 2  by Jack Mangan</h1><p>Author Jack Mangan (Spherical Tomi) is back with Duel of the Fates 2! As originally heard on the Dragon Page Wingin&apos; It!&nbsp; Podcast: Duel of the Fates 2 assembles highly diverse, iconic combatants from across the wide universe of speculative fiction and pits them head-to-head in comparative contests of 5 monumentally important categories. 1) Dr.&nbsp; Evil (Austin Powers)2) Six Million Dollar Man3) TD-0013 (A Diff&apos;rent Point of View)4) The Mighty Thor5) Ash (Evil Dead)6) Starbuck from the new Battlestar Galactica (Katee Sackhoff)7) Gandalf the Grey/White (Lord of the Rings)8) T-800 TerminatorDr.&nbsp; Evil vs.&nbsp; The Terminator!&nbsp; Six Million Dollar Man vs.&nbsp; Gandalf!&nbsp; TD-0013 vs.&nbsp; Starbuck!&nbsp; Thor vs.&nbsp; Ash!&nbsp; Plus!&nbsp; An exhibition battle of Kermit the Frog vs. the Silver Surfer.&nbsp; And that&apos;s only the first round. . .Who&apos;d win in a fight?&nbsp; Who&apos;d make the better 4th companion for Dorothy on her quest to see the wizard?&nbsp; Whose name makes the better acronym?&nbsp; Whose all-important Intangibles outweigh their opponent&apos;s?&nbsp; Subscribe and listen, if only to hear Jack&apos;s wife read the Love Prowess category!&nbsp; Then subscribe to the original Duel of the Fates series!&nbsp; Then subscribe to the Spherical Tomi Podiobook!&nbsp; Who will be the second tournament&apos;s big winner?</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
