<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>James Melzer&apos;s podcasts &amp; podcast novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[You have no idea what you&apos;ve just done...]]>" xmlUrl="http://jamesmelzer.net/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[You have no idea what you&apos;ve just done...]]>" htmlUrl="http://jamesmelzer.net/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>You have no idea what you&apos;ve just done...</h1><p>Home of horror/thriller author, James Melzer.&nbsp; Including The Zombie Chronicles &amp; Hull&apos; Landing podcast novels as well as his new interview series, UNLEASHED, sponsored by Permuted Press.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[UNLEASHED: The Podcast to F*&k Up Your Sh%t!]]>" xmlUrl="http://jamesmelzer.net/featured/unleashed/?feed=rss" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[UNLEASHED: The Podcast to F*&k Up Your Sh%t!]]>" htmlUrl="http://jamesmelzer.net/featured/unleashed/" description="<![CDATA[It&apos;s raw, it&apos;s gritty and it&apos;s unscripted...as you&apos;ll soon hear. It&apos;s me talking to you, and maybe eventually some others. We&apos;ll see about that. Hell, this things so goddamn new that it doesn&apos;t even have it&apos;s own theme song...]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Zombie Chronicles: Escape]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-zombie-chronicles-escape/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Zombie Chronicles: Escape]]>" htmlUrl="http://jamesmelzer.net/" description="<![CDATA[When an asteroid passes by our planet and leaves a trail of death in its wake, a quarter of the population have become the living dead.&nbsp; Twenty-five years later the zombies are under the control of the government.&nbsp; Citizens are chosen to participate in Project Mirror, a cloning project in which their &quot;mirrors&quot; are used as food for the undead.&nbsp; When one man discovers that something in his blood is being used to create an army of super-zombies, he decides to help his mirror escape.&nbsp; In doing so he uncovers a secret so guarded that the powers that be will stop at nothing to eliminate him and all those that he loves.&nbsp; The Zombie Chronicles: Escape is the first book is a series of edge-of-your-seat thrillers that will take you on an adventure beyond your wildest imagination and leave you wanting more with each episode.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Hull's Landing]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/hulls-landing/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Hull's Landing - A free audiobook by James Melzer]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/hulls-landing/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Hull's Landing</h1><h3>A free audiobook by James Melzer</h3><p>Nestled deep in the heart of Pennsylvania is the small town of Hull&apos;s Landing.&nbsp; While it may seem like just an ordinary place, The Landing holds a secret so dark, that there are those who will do anything to protect it.For decades, young girls have been disappearing like clockwork.&nbsp; While some have their suspicions, the entire town lives in fear, and for good reason.&nbsp; When Rita Clemens, a former member of the Pittsburgh Bureau of Police, decides to make her new home in Hull&apos;s, she begins to uncover what the locals have tried to keep hidden for so long.As the race against time begins, Rita will have to do everything she can to protect herself, and to save a child&apos;s life, before one of the world&apos;s oldest evils can be unleashed.Hull&apos;s Landing is an original novella from the author of THE ZOMBIE CHRONICLES: ESCAPE, coming to bookstores everywhere in March 2011 from Permuted Press and Simon and Schuster.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
