<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			James D. Priest&appos;s podcast novels &ndash; prensented by: podiobooks.com
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[KIRINS: The Spell of No'an]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/kirins-the-spell-of-noan/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[KIRINS: The Spell of No'an - A free audiobook by James D. Priest ]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/kirins-the-spell-of-noan/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>KIRINS: The Spell of No'an by James D. Priest </h1><p>A race of tiny, magical beings lives on Earth today. They dwell in elaborate tree homes and mysterious underground sanctuaries. Because of an ancient dispute, however, humans are unaware of their hidden civilization.They are kirins.For thousands of years they lived in peace. But a deadly menace now threatens their existence. A party of daring explorers, led by the wise magician Speckarin, is sent on trained ravens to destroy an evil lurking a continent and an ocean away. Failure of...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The KIRINS Trilogy, Book Two: The Flight of the Ain]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-flight-of-the-ain/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The KIRINS Trilogy, Book Two: The Flight of the Ain - A free audiobook by James D. Priest]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-flight-of-the-ain/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The KIRINS Trilogy, Book Two: The Flight of the Ain by James D. Priest</h1><p>A race of tiny magical beings lives on Earth today. They are kirins.Because of an ancient dispute, however, humans are unaware of their hidden civilization. For thousands of years they lived in peace, but a deadly menace now threatens their existence. A party of daring explorers led by the wise magician, Speckarin, is sent to destroy an evil lurking a continent and an ocean away.In this second book of the KIRINS trilogy, the party reaches the sea, a vast and impassable entity....</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
