<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			Jeremy Robinson&apos;s podcast novels.&nbsp; Presented by: podiobooks.com
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Kronos]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/kronos/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Kronos - a free audiobook by Jeremy Robinson]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/kronos/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Two years after his wife's death, oceanographer and former navy SEAL, Atticus Young, attempts to reconcile with his rebellious daughter, Giona, by taking her on the scuba dive of a lifetime-swimming with a pod of peaceful humpback whales in the Gulf of Maine. But the beauty of the sea belies a terror from the deep-a horrific creature as immense as it is ancient. There is no blood, no scream, no fight. Giona is swallowed whole by the massive jaws. Only Atticus remains to suffer the shame of the survivor and his inconsolable grief turns to an unquenchable thirst for revenge.</p><p>Drawn by the spectacle, Trevor Manfred, a ruthless billionaire, approaches Atticus with a proposition: Trevor will make available all the advanced technology of his heavily armed mega-yacht, the Titan, to aid Atticus in his death-quest. In return, Trevor is to receive the beast's corpse as the ultimate hunting trophy. But in the midst of the hunt, Atticus makes a terrifying discovery that changes the way he sees the ocean's creatures and begs the question: what is Kronos? The answer sets him on a new and much more deadly course.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Beneath]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/beneath/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Beneath - A free audiobook by Jeremy Robinson]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/beneath/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Three thousand years after a chunk of iron the size of Khufu&apos;s pyramid collides with Europa, Jupiter&apos;s sixth moon, an asteroid borne of the collision crashes into Earth&apos;s Arctic ice shelf carrying extraterrestrial microbial life. The first man to come into contact with the microbes hears voices-and then dies.&nbsp; After determining the meteorite originated from Europa, the Global Exploratory Corporation sends oceanographer and biologist, Kathy Connelly, and her crew to the moon aboard the Surveyor, an experimental spacecraft. They are charged with the task of melting through miles of ice to the hidden ocean beneath, where the search for alien microorganisms begins. But a startling discovery awaits them on the surface of Europa. Life. Vast fields of red, plant-like organisms fill the cracks crisscrossing the moon&apos;s surface, surviving on nutrients welling up from the waters below. Intoxicated by thoughts of what might lie beneath, Connelly and her crew activate the Thermal Exploratory System and melt through the ice-toward a world that does not want to be found, toward a force that will do anything to make sure they never leave. They search for life. They find death.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
