<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Joe Cottonwood&apos;s podcast novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[&apos;s audio dramas]]>" url="" type="link" text="<![CDATA[Podcast audio dramas from ]]>" description="<![CDATA[Podcast audio dramas from ]]>" />-->
		<outline title="<!&nbsp; [CDATA[Clear Heart - A free podcast novel by Joe Cottonwood]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.&nbsp; podiobooks.&nbsp; com/title/clear-heart/feed/" type="rss" text="<!&nbsp; [CDATA[Clear Heart - A free audiobook by Joe Cottonwood]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.&nbsp; podiobooks.&nbsp; com/title/clear-heart/" description="<!&nbsp; [CDATA[<p>Carpenters and craft, friendship and rivalry:  Wally is building a mansion for a dot-com multimillionaire in the Silicon Valley of California.&nbsp; As the dot-com&apos;s stock keeps rising, the size of the house - and the owner&apos;s ego - keep growing.&nbsp; Wally and his colorful crew may be into something that&apos;s over their heads.&nbsp; When little guys work for bigshots, who gets nailed?&nbsp; From bungling to burglary, from demolishing concrete to racing beltsanders, from love of tools to falling in love, everyone will encounter Wally&apos;s Laws of Construction - or are they Laws of Life?&nbsp; Each house, it seems, is a miracle.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Famous Potatoes - A free podcast novel by Joe Cottonwood]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/famous-potatoes/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Famous Potatoes - A free audiobook by Joe Cottonwood]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/famous-potatoes/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Willy Middlebrook is a nice boy from the suburbs, a Vietnam vet, a college drop-out majoring in Human Kindness.&nbsp; Framed for the murder of a cop, Willy goes on the lam from the law, crisscrossing America while encountering the people of the humble cafes and dusty bars, underground:  &quot;They have rough brown skin and soft wrinkled eyes.&nbsp; They are round and they are usually dirty.&nbsp; They are hard because they have to be, but if you warm them they get soft and you can make them sweet.&quot;  Famous Potatoes is a road novel with a touch of noir, a tall tale that has been called &quot;exuberant, funny, and humane.&quot;</p><p>This podcast is rated deep R for bad language and occasional scenes of funky sex.&nbsp; And a lot of joy.</p><p>Author&apos;s note:  I wrote this novel forty years ago as a cockeyed love letter to the USA.&nbsp; I was a young man without children.&nbsp; Now I am a grandfather.&nbsp; A few of the passages, as I review them now, could make a grandfather blush.&nbsp; Nevertheless I have resisted the impulse to censor any youthful excess.&nbsp; I&apos;ve also let stand the passages that would now be deemed Politically Incorrect.&nbsp; They are an accurate rendition of the times (1971).</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Boone Barnaby - A free podcast novel by Joe Cottonwood]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/boone-barnaby/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Boone Barnaby - A free audiobook by Joe Cottonwood]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/boone-barnaby/" description="<![CDATA[<p>If you liked Clear Heart, I think you&apos;ll like this one too.&nbsp; It&apos;s got great characters, it&apos;s down-to-earth, it&apos;s fun.&nbsp; And better yet, this one&apos;s friendly to children.&nbsp; Boone Barnaby is about three boys testing the limits of life in their scrappy little town.&nbsp; It&apos;s about collecting garbage, climbing trees, catching a criminal, and talking to dragonflies.&nbsp; Boone Barnaby lives in a small town full of large characters:  San Puerco, California.&nbsp; There&apos;s Boone&apos;s father, who loves Studebakers and doo-wop, and who has a habit of walking around the dark streets of town late at night carrying a can of gasoline.&nbsp; There&apos;s Boone&apos;s friend Danny, who has nothing-sometimes not even a home-but who wants everything, even if he has to steal for it.&nbsp; There&apos;s Boone&apos;s other friend Babcock, who finds trilobites and organizes a picket line and looks like a wet coconut.&nbsp; There&apos;s Walt, the soccer coach, who drives a Harley-Davidson motorcycle.&nbsp; And there&apos;s Boone himself, who has a few problems:  His soccer team is thrown out of the league.&nbsp; The dogcatcher is after Boone&apos;s dog.&nbsp; The town hoodlum is throwing rocks.&nbsp; Boone&apos;s father is arrested for burning down houses.&nbsp; The adult world doesn&apos;t seem fair, but with the help of his friends-Danny and Babcock-Boone tries to make things right and maybe learn just who he is and what he stands for.&nbsp; Boone Barnaby is Part One of the San Puerco Trilogy, three award-winning novels that have been loved by adults and children alike, about the adventures of three boys in a town of cranks and dreamers-and adventurous children.(One note before you listen:  The novel was written in 1988 before every house had a computer, every person could get a cell phone, and every mom drove an SUV.&nbsp; It was written when every President was a white man.&nbsp; It wasn&apos;t all that long ago.)</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Babcock - A free podcast novel by Joe Cottonwood]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/babcock/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Babcock - A free audiobook by Joe Cottonwood]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/babcock/" description="<![CDATA[<p>A fat boy with the blues.&nbsp; A skinny girl who runs marathons.&nbsp; And a con man on the lam.&nbsp; If you liked Clear Heart, or if you liked Boone Barnaby, you&apos;ll like this one, too.&nbsp; The themes are a bit more grown up than Boone Barnaby, but it&apos;s still family-friendly for reading.&nbsp; For any age it&apos;s my brand of writing:  humane, down to earth, good-natured, sometimes funny and sometimes sad.&nbsp; Babcock plays electric guitar.&nbsp; He&apos;s writing songs - and trying to figure out the true meaning of rock and roll - but he keeps coming up with the blues.&nbsp; Babcock is trying to start a friendship with a girl, Kirsten, who is as different as can be:  Kirsten is skinny; she hates insects.&nbsp; And she&apos;s white.&nbsp; Babcock is fat; he speaks to dragonflies.&nbsp; And he&apos;s black.&nbsp; In some ways Kirsten is like a dragonfly:  quick and bright.&nbsp; She never walks; she runs everywhere.&nbsp; Her family has money.&nbsp; Her mother thinks Babcock is a little too &quot;rough.&quot;  Opposites attract.&nbsp; But can they make music?Babcock&apos;s family is struggling for money.&nbsp; Then Babcock&apos;s Uncle Earl moves in - and he moves into Babcock&apos;s bedroom with Babcock&apos;s menagerie of animals (including Martin Luther Kingsnake.).&nbsp; Uncle Earl is a con man on the lam.&nbsp; Uncle Earl used to play drums for Chuck Berry.&nbsp; Babcock wants to be Chuck Berry.&nbsp; Uncle Earl wants to coach a Little League baseball team - as a &quot;business venture.&quot;  Babcock hates baseball.&nbsp; Babcock wants to learn &quot;charm&quot; from Uncle Earl.&nbsp; Uncle Earl wants to learn how to live a normal life and marry a normal woman - who happens to be Babcock&apos;s schoolteacher.&nbsp; Maybe Babcock and Uncle Earl have something to teach each other.&nbsp; Babcock&apos;s father runs a car repair shop.&nbsp; At night, in the kitchen, he draws cartoons.&nbsp; Some day he wants to quit repairing cars and sell his cartoons.&nbsp; But nobody&apos;s buying.&nbsp; Kirsten is hotheaded.&nbsp; Sometimes she needs protection - from herself.&nbsp; Her mother tries to protect her - from Babcock.&nbsp; For help with his problems Babcock goes to an unlikely source: his Uncle Earl, the man with good charm and bad behavior.&nbsp; But the biggest lessons from Uncle Earl - and, perhaps, from rock and roll - are not what anyone expected.&nbsp; In short, it&apos;s about character.&nbsp; About making music.&nbsp; About family, hard work, about love and loss.&nbsp; Sometimes there&apos;s laughter.&nbsp; Sometimes the lights are off in the kitchen; papa&apos;s got blues.&nbsp; But always life is rich and deeply moving...I call Babcock a post-Obama novel.&nbsp; It&apos;s about the friendship of a black boy with a white girl, and it isn&apos;t about racial issues - well, not much.&nbsp; Have we really reached that point?&nbsp; Is our cup half full?&nbsp; The odd thing is, I wrote this novel in 1992 when nobody, including me, had heard of Barack Obama and when book critics wanted bloody racial conflict whenever black and white characters mixed in the pages of a novel.&nbsp; Maybe I was 16 years ahead of the times.&nbsp; Babcock is part of the San Puerco trilogy, which makes it a companion book to Boone Barnaby:  same characters (plus a few new ones) and more adventures in the scrappy little town of San Puerco.&nbsp; The book won awards as a novel for children, but it has many adult fans, too.&nbsp; Most of the issues appeal to an adult perspective as well as a child&apos;s, though with different understanding.&nbsp; Other issues, of course, only a young person can understand.&nbsp; That&apos;s life.&nbsp; That&apos;s rock and roll.</p>]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast audio drama from ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by .  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
	</body>
</opml>
