<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			The Works of: John Lenahan.&nbsp; The &quot;Shadowmagic Saga&quot;&nbsp; Podcast novels.
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Shadowmagic]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/shadowmagic/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Shadowmagic - A free audiobook by John Lenahan]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/shadowmagic/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Shadowmagic</h1><h3>by John Lenahan</h3><p>&quot;Hi, my name is Conor.&nbsp; Other than my father being a bit of an eccentric lunatic, my life was pretty normal until I got attacked in my living room and whisked away to Tir na Nog, the mystical land of the ancient Celts, where it turns out Dad is the usurped heir to the throne and everybody wants me dead because of some prophecy.&nbsp; Don&apos;t you just hate when that happens?&quot;Shadowmagic is a rip roaring fun fantasy adventure novel by John Lenahan very loosely based on Irish mythology where every chapter ends on the edge of a cliff (or at least a high curb.)  Join Conor as he grapples with typical teenage problems like, how to deal with a father&apos;s high expectations, how to survive in the world on your own and how to woo a beautiful girl - that wants you dead.&nbsp; Shadowmagic a podcast novel for young adults from 12 to 112.Rated 10 out of 10 on The Geek Beat!</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Prince of Hazel and Oak]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-prince-of-hazel-and-oak/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Prince of Hazel and Oak - A free audiobook by John Lenahan]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-prince-of-hazel-and-oak/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Prince of Hazel and Oak</h1><h3>by John Lenahan</h3><p>The Prince of Hazel and Oak  by John LenahanPart 2 of the Shadowmagic Series.&nbsp; Podiobooks no. 1 voted podcast returns for another action and laugh packed sequel.&nbsp; Finally listeners can find out what happened to Conor on his return to the Real World from Tir na Nog.   (He was arrested for his father&apos;s murder.)  Join Conor (and a very confused Scranton cop) as they try to survive The Prince of Duir&apos;s chaotic return to The Land.&nbsp; The Prince of Hazel and Oak is the second novel from real life magician and comedian - John Lenahan.&nbsp; John&apos;s first novel, Shadowmagic, is available in paperback, epub and Kindle editions from HarperCollins UK.&nbsp; For more details go to www.shadowmagic.co.uk </p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>

