<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Michele Roger&apos;s works &amp; creations.&nbsp; Podcasts, fiction, novels, &amp; audio dramas.</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Dark Matter]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.micheleroger.com/DarkMatter.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Dark Matter - A free podcast novel by Michele Roger]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.micheleroger.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Dark Matter</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Michele Roger</h3><p><p>In a freak accident that leads to her untimely death Louella, a plain Jane from the suburbs finds herself transformed into one of the walking undead.&nbsp; Michael, the Archangel, offers her a chance to win her life and family back.</p><p>Louella learns that even in the afterlife nothing is free.&nbsp; She must pit her meager supernatural abilities against the mounting forces of darkness.&nbsp; Confronting problematic demons and monsters from Otherworld and beyond who agressively continue to tip the scales in the war of good and and evil in the favor of the Dark One.&nbsp; With the help of Steven, the altruistic vampire and De Vok, a dead librarian from the ancient Alexandria, Luella walks the world between the living and the dead.&nbsp; In her quest to regain her life she learns that even the forces for good have their own agendas and cannot always be trusted.</p><p>This book is a macabre stew of horror, fantasy, science fiction and humor.</p></p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Something Wicked This Way Strums]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.micheleroger.com/MicheleRoger.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Something Wicked This Way Strums - Free Podiocast Short Stories from the dark mind of Michele Roger]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.micheleroger.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Something Wicked This Way Strums - Free Podiocast Short Stories from the dark mind of Michele Roger</h1><p>A horror anthology by Michele Roger.</p><p>Darkness, darkness and more darkness.&nbsp; Michele Roger presents an anthology of short stories of the dark horror genre.&nbsp; Combining Science Fiction, fantasy and horror with enough of a twist to leave you shaken and not stirred.</p>"]]> />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Conservatory]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.micheleroger.com/TheConservatory.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Conservatory - A free audiobook by Michele Roger]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.micheleroger.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Conservatory</h1><h3>by Michele Roger</h3><p>Tom Brady has won the &apos;hardship&apos; scholarship to the prestigous Hillford Conservatory for Music.&nbsp; He faces not only stiff competition from the other &apos;more privileged&apos; students but he also faces the horror of the darkness and curse that surrounds the school.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>

