<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			The Works of: Mike Bennett.&nbsp; Podcasts, fiction, novels, &amp; audio dramas.
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Mike Bennett's Big Feed: Original and Classic Fict]]>" xmlUrl="http://mikebennett.libsyn.com/rss" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Mike Bennett's Big Feed: Original and Classic Fiction.  Including the podcast novel: &quot;Underwood &amp; Flinch&quot;]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.mikebennettpodcast.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Mike Bennett's Big Feed: Original and Classic Fict</h1><p>This is the all-in-one feed for podcast novelist, Mike Bennett.&nbsp; Including Underwood and Flinch Part One.&nbsp; For hundreds of years, the eldest born male member of the Flinch family has become servant and guardian to the vampire, Lord Underwood.&nbsp; In 1958, a world-weary Underwood lies down to rest for fifty years.&nbsp; Now the time has come for his resurrection, and role of guardian has fallen to David Flinch, a man raised outside the family tradition of service and homicide, and who would happily pass the job on to his sister, Lydia.&nbsp; Until he realizes that Lydia has a zeal for death that that goes beyond family tradition, and even beyond Underwood himself.&nbsp; This feed is also home to Mike Bennett&apos;s earlier podcast works including One Among the Sleepless, a novel about sex, death and noisy neighbours; Hall of Mirrors, Tales of Horror and the Grotesque, and Mike Bennett Sometimes: classic fiction and random absurdities.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[One Among The Sleepless]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/one-among-the-sleepless/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[One Among The Sleepless - A free audiobook by Mike Bennett]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/one-among-the-sleepless/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>One Among The Sleepless</h1><h3>by Mike Bennett</h3><p>&quot;One Among The Sleepless&quot; is a contemporary fiction novel set in Brighton, England about sex, death and noisy neighbors: a thriller with a rich vein of dark humor that flows from both the narrative and the dialogue of the characters.&nbsp; It&apos;s a largely character-driven story; the people and their various shifting relationships compel the plot forward through sometimes subtle, sometimes brutal plot twists towards the final, nail-gnawing climax.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Hall of Mirrors: Tales of Horror and the Grotesque]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.mevio.com/feeds/hallofmirrors.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Hall of Mirrors: Tales of Horror and the Grotesque]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.mevio.com/shows/?show=hallofmirrors" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Hall of Mirrors: Tales of Horror and the Grotesque</h1><p>A second helping of podcast fiction from &apos;One Among the Sleepless&apos; author, Mike Bennett. &apos;Hall of Mirrors&apos; is a short story collection featuring tales of horror, the grotesque and people in... &apos;unusual&apos; circumstances.</p><p>Delivered in a style that pays homage to Night Gallery, Alfred Hitchcock Presents and the old British horror anthology movies of the 1960s, this is a collection of modern gothic tales with a nail of dark humour hammered through its heart.&nbsp; So roll up, ladies and gentlemen, and enter the Hall of Mirrors – if you dare.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Sometimes]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.mevio.com/feeds/thebonustrack.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Mike Bennett Sometimes]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.mevio.com/shows/?show=thebonustrack" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Mike Bennett Sometimes</h1><p>An occasional treat for lovers of great stories and strange behaviour.&nbsp; Podcast novelist Mike Bennett reads classic short fiction from authors including Saki and Edgar Allen Poe.&nbsp; He also plays choice music and has bizarre encounters with everything from Snickers-loving silverfish to a Jingle Repair Man.</p>]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>

