<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>&apos;s podcast novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Salmon and Dusk: Time Travel Crime tales]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/kilbeysalmon" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Salmon and Dusk: Time Travel Crime tales - A SERIES OF SHORT STORIES BY MYKE BARTLETT]]>" htmlUrl="http://mykebartlett.com/?q=taxonomy/term/12/0" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Salmon and Dusk: Time Travel Crime tales - A SERIES OF SHORT STORIES BY MYKE BARTLETT</h1><ul><li>Kilbey Salmon has charm, a quick gob and an instinct for self-preservation.</li><li>Nero Dusk has a lot of patience, a grumpy demeanour and a way with his fists.</li></ul><p>Using a time-travelling London cab, these two scrape together a living finding things that never existed and solving crimes that never happened for people desperate enough to seek their help. Mostly, they get themselves in trouble. And when there's trouble for Salmon &amp; Dusk, it's the strangest sort of trouble London has ever seen...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[How to Disappear Completely - A free podcast novel by Myke Bartlett]]>" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/how-to-disappear-completely/feed/" text="<![CDATA[How to Disappear Completely - A free audiobook by Myke Bartlett]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/how-to-disappear-completely/" description="<![CDATA[Part film noir detective story, part fantasy adventure, part East End gangster tale, How to Disappear Completely concerns Theo Braithwaite, a failed actress and worse waitress, becoming involved in an unseen world populated by history's rejects and runaways from a secret society known as The Footmen. A stranger to London, waiting for life to come and find her, she is instead found by a part-time thief called Kilbey Salmon who, along with his rockabilly-obsessed partner, is attempting to eke out a living stealing things that have already been stolen and finding people who don't want to be found.&nbsp; An episodic narrative, Kilbey and Nero's capers will drag Theo through the forgotten parts and people of London, hunted by ancient sects, carnivorous shadows, cannibalistic butchers and off-duty policemen. Along the way she'll meet the Eternal Footmen, blow up Hammersmith Bridge, reach the end of history and quite possibly disappear completely.&nbsp; If Theo is to survive, she'll need to get her life sorted before all of our futures catch up with her.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Electricity]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/electricity/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Electricty - A free podcast novel by Myke Barlett]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/electricity/" description="<![CDATA[From the Author of How to Disappear Completely:1999Aston Somerfield, casual smoker and part-time alcoholic, has come to London to find himself.&nbsp; He knows who he's looking for, he's seen him on the cover of the NME.&nbsp; Drawn across oceans by fame and fate, Aston is keeping his diary empty to make sure he's available.&nbsp; Won't commit to anything until it's everything.&nbsp; London, however, has other ideas.&nbsp; When a virtual stranger calls Aston a few hours before his death, fate catches up with him, derailing his barely-made plans.&nbsp; Amid a hundred boozy evenings and romantic deadends, a mystery unfurls.&nbsp; Equally assisted and hindered by tremulous accountant Tom Hensley and dedicated loafer Steven Black, Aston uncovers a different London, one of murder, ghosts, dangerous emails and the second big bang.&nbsp; As chaotic and random as the city it inhabits, Electricity gradually evolves into a mystery bigger than the universe itself.&nbsp; Being of a somewhat useless persuasion, Aston does his best to ignore it.]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by .  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
