<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			The Works of: Patrick E. McLean.&nbsp; Podcasts, fiction, novels, &amp; audio dramas.
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Seanachai]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.theseanachai.com/feed/podcast/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Seanachai]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.theseanachai.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Seanachai</h1><h3>The Seanachai</h3><p>The official podcast of author Patrick E.&nbsp; McLean.&nbsp; Averaging 5-7 minutes in length, these pieces involves skillful sound design that enhance and move the telling forward.&nbsp; Most episodes are funny, some are moving, but each and every one takes full advantage of the medium of audio.&nbsp; Think this American Life on Steroids.</p><p>Short audio stories very well produced.&nbsp; Unlike anything you've heard; think NPR meets radio drama in the back of a pub.&nbsp; Actually, don't think, Just listen.&nbsp; If it's not absolutely one of the best podcasts you've ever heard your lost time will be refunded.</p><p>Patrick&apos;s online presence includes <a href='http://www.goodwordsrightorder.com/'>http://www.goodwordsrightorder.com/</a>, <a href='http://patrickemclean.com/'>http://patrickemclean.com/</a>, <a href='http://theseanachai.com/'>http://theseanachai.com/</a>, and <a href='http://succeedinevil.com/'>http://succeedinevil.com/</a></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Stories I Told Myself]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/stories-i-told-myself/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Stories I Told Myself - A free audiobook by Patrick E. McLean]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/stories-i-told-myself/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Stories I Told Myself</h1><h3>by Patrick E. McLean</h3><p>Funny, moving, and always exquisitely well-produced.&nbsp; This collection of short stories and essays from the award-winning <a href='http://www.theseanachai.com/'>Seanachai</a> podcast is not to be missed.&nbsp; If you like This American Life, but wish that Ira Glass&apos; voice was a bit softer on the ears, then this is the audio book for you.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[How to Succeed in Evil: The Novel]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/how-to-succeed-in-evil-the-novel/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[How to Succeed in Evil: The Novel - A free audiobook by Patrick McLean]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/how-to-succeed-in-evil-the-novel/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>How to Succeed in Evil: The Novel</h1><h3>by Patrick McLean</h3><p>Alternately funny and dark, a HtSiE is the story of Edwin Windsor, Evil Efficiency Consultant. A biting satire of both modern business and the conventions of the superhero genre.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[How To Succeed in Evil: The Original Podcast Episodes]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/how-to-succeed-in-evil-the-original-podcast-episodes/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[How To Succeed in Evil: The Original Podcast Episodes - A free audiobook by Patrick McLean]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/how-to-succeed-in-evil-the-original-podcast-episodes/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>How To Succeed in Evil: The Original Podcast Episodes</h1><h3>by Patrick McLean</h3><p>How to Succeed in Evil - Original Podcast Episodes are best thought of as notes and sketches for the novel length work How to Succeed in Evil:The NovelThis is not to take anything away from these episodes, the first 10 of which won a Parsec Award.&nbsp; Semi- Spoiler Alert: These episodes cover longer arc of story than the novel.&nbsp; Some of the stuff that happens in the podcasts might make it into a future novel.&nbsp; Then again, it might not.&nbsp; But then again, who cares.&nbsp; Shakespeare gave away the plot of most of his plays in the first 10 lines and it turned out okay for him.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Vampire in My Face]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.theseanachai.com/category/podcast/the-vampire-in-my-face/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Seanachai &#187; The Vampire in My Face]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.theseanachai.com/category/podcast/the-vampire-in-my-face/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Seanachai &#187; The Vampire in My Face</h1><p>The worst monsters are the ones who believe they have your best interest at heart.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Bright Lights]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.theseanachai.com/category/podcast/bright-lights/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Seanachai &#187; Bright Lights]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.theseanachai.com/category/podcast/bright-lights/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Seanachai &#187; Bright Lights</h1><h3>The Seanachai</h3><p>The incident of the man murdering his guitar was represented to me as a true story.&nbsp; But I don&#8217;t even care if it&#8217;s really true or not.&nbsp; It was just such a fascinating set up  I had to see where it went.</p><p>This is another one of those multipart stories where I wrote the first part and had no idea how I was going to end it.&nbsp; It certainly motivates you to come up with an ending when you&#8217;ve publicly committed to finishing the thing. (perhaps I have found the cure for Writer&#8217;s Block)</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Flinchy and the Mexican Show Truck]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.theseanachai.com/category/podcast/flinchy-and-the-mexican-show-truck/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Seanachai &#187; Flinchy and the Mexican Show Truck]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.theseanachai.com/category/podcast/flinchy-and-the-mexican-show-truck/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Seanachai &#187; Flinchy and the Mexican Show Truck</h1><h3>The Seanachai</h3><p>The official podcast of author Patrick E. McLean. Averaging 5-7 minutes in length, these pieces are crafted specifically for audio. This involves skilful sound design that enhances and moves the telling forward rather than just a flat read.  Most episodes are funny, some are moving, but each and every one takes full advantage of the medium of audio. Think this American Life on Steroids.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[How to Succeed in Evil]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.theseanachai.com/category/podcast/how-to-succeed-in-evil/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Seanachai &#187; How to Succeed in Evil]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.theseanachai.com" description="<![CDATA[<h1>How to Succeed in Evil</h1><h3>The Seanachai</h3><p>The official podcast of author Patrick E. McLean. Averaging 5-7 minutes in length, these pieces are crafted specifically for audio. This involves skilful sound design that enhances and moves the telling forward rather than just a flat read.  Most episodes are funny, some are moving, but each and every one takes full advantage of the medium of audio. Think this American Life on Steroids.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The War with Santa]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.theseanachai.com/category/podcast/the-war-with-santa/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Seanachai &#187; The War with Santa]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.theseanachai.com/category/podcast/the-war-with-santa/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The War with Santa</h1><h3>The Seanachai</h3><p>I discover an interesting fact.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[How I Got My Voice Back]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.theseanachai.com/category/podcast/how-i-got-my-voice-back/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Seanachai &#187; How I Got My Voice Back]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.theseanachai.com/category/podcast/how-i-got-my-voice-back/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>How I Got My Voice Back</h1><h3>The Seanachai</h3><p>Don&#8217;t tell them it ended like this.&nbsp; Tell them I said something.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Driver&#8217;s Re-Education]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.theseanachai.com/category/podcast/drivers-re-education/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Seanachai &#187; Driver&#8217;s Re-Education]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.theseanachai.com/category/podcast/drivers-re-education/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Driver&#8217;s Re-Education</h1><h3>The Seanachai</h3><p>The fall of Fishbinder.</p><p><span id="more-21"></span>A lot of thinking to write my way out of a corner this time.&nbsp; I suppose that&#8217;s good practice. (Building character and all that.)</p><p>I was trying to update Greek tragedy.&nbsp; I don&#8217;t think it succeeded, but here&#8217;s what I was thinking. (I&#8217;m certain I&#8217;m going to oversimply Greek Tragedy.&nbsp; Sorry, I&#8217;m a simple guy.)</p><p>You see, greek tragedy is driven by the idea of Hubris (arrogance) calling forth Nemesis (retribution). So that when Oedipus discovers that he&#8217;s married his mother, well, he just falls apart.&nbsp; His moral sense of the world falls apart.&nbsp; And he blinds himself.</p><p>I think we (in our postmodern times) can only understand this play on the level of religious ritual.&nbsp; Because we don&#8217;t seem to believe in things the way people used to.&nbsp; And if Oedipus happened to day (guy kills his father and marries his mother) we would have a chance to stare into a set of perfect, unblinded eyes as he told us his story on Springer.&nbsp; We would also have ample opportunity to buy a book on the subject, or suffer through a movie of the week.</p><p>And that&#8217;s really the tragedy.&nbsp; Not much sacred.&nbsp; Not much profane.&nbsp; We&#8217;re just left with sensationalism.</p><p>And the idea with Fishbinder is, he has nothing to believe in, so in an effort to make himself whole, he choose the worst thing of all.&nbsp; The laws relating to Motor Vehicles.&nbsp; And when this set of beliefs is challenged, he falls apart.</p><p>Yes, it&#8217;s funny at parts.&nbsp; But if the story works the way I hoped it would, it there should be a realistic sense, that you know people like this.</p><p>I guess another way to look at it would be to start with Saul Bellow who wrote that his work was devoted to the rediscovery of the magic of the world under the debris of modern ideas. Fishbinder is a man crushed by the debris of modern ideas.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Death of a Dishwasher]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.theseanachai.com/category/podcast/death-of-a-dishwasher/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Seanachai &#187; Death of a Dishwasher]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.theseanachai.com/category/podcast/death-of-a-dishwasher/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Death of a Dishwasher</h1><h3>The Seanachai</h3><p>So this is an early draft of the screenplay that eventually became Death of a Dishwasher.&nbsp; Very clearly, I don&#8217;t know what I&#8217;m doing structuring a screenplay &#8212; but some of the scene&#8217;s really snap.&nbsp; And the lines are still funny.&nbsp; I skimmed it as I was building this post and I chuckled to myself in several places.&nbsp; This is good sign, because I&#8217;m pretty critical of my own work.</p>]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>

