<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>&apos;s podcast novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Notes from the Vault - A free podcast novel by Phil Rossi]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/notes-from-the-vault/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Notes from the Vault - A free audiobook by Phil Rossi]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/notes-from-the-vault/" description="<![CDATA[A blizzard cripples an isolated stretch of US Highway where freezing to death would be a mercy. An antique broker holds the internet in the palm of his hand and learns what really brought the system down.  In the forests of upstate Connecticut, a pair of college students visit the site of legendary hauntings.Welcome to the Vault.Phil Rossi, author and twisted mind behind Crescent, brings you a collection of stories that will take you on a terror-fueled ride from the cold abyss of space to your own backyard.  The anthology includes all 7 original Crescent Vignettes, new tales from the Crescent Universe, and many stories in between. &quot;Phil Rossi has taken the podcast novel market by storm. His twisted visions of a Lovecraftian far-future reads like Phillip K. Dick meets David Seltzer. Someone is going make a ton of cash with this guy.&quot;--Scott Sigler,  Best-selling author of Infected, Earthcore, and Ancestor&quot;Phil [Rossi] combines classic space operatic sci-fi with horror in a way Hollywood and many authors have completely failed to do in past years.&quot;--Matt Wallace, two-time parsec-winning author of the Failed Cities Monologues and the short fiction collection the Next Fix.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Harvey - A free podcast novel by Phil Rossi]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/harvey/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Harvey - A free audiobook by Phil Rossi]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/harvey/" description="<![CDATA[Television singing sensation Calvin Hubbard has been caught with his hand in cookie jar. An illicit affair with a contest judge costs him not only the competition crown, but his musical credibility as well.  Fleeing the media fallout, Calvin exiles himself to the backwoods town of Harvey, Virginia. With a little solitude and a lot of cheap beer, he plans to write the next great rock and roll album and resurrect his career.  But Calvin doesn&apos;t know that a man has just been buried alive in the woods outside of town, and that this quiet murder is just the first in a string of macabre events.  As the town goes silently mad around him, Calvin is unable to abandon the record of his dreams. Drunk on inspiration and blinded by an inexplicable lust, he careens headlong into the maelstrom, only to discover that he may be the town&apos;s only salvation. Something is alive in the trees-an ageless, nameless evil-and it&apos;s coming for everyone in Harvey. Now Calvin has to decide whether to run or to stay and fight... if it isn&apos;t already too late.&quot;...sexy and full of scares. Harvey is dark, well-crafted, and downright menacing.&quot;  -Philippa Ballantine, award-winning author of Chasing the BardPhil Rossi breaks new ground with Harvey--visit http://www.harveythenovel.com for the Harvey Sessions--the very album that Calvin Hubbard is composing and recording at the Little Rock Motel.  Listen as the record&apos;s tracks take form and evolve from idea, to demo, to fully arranged song as impacted by the events in the novel. ]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Eden - A free podcast novel by Phil Rossi]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/eden/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Eden - A free audiobook by Phil Rossi]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/eden/" description="<![CDATA[The tree is beautiful and they call her Eden.  Her branches reach for the stars.  She is like all other trees on planet Earth save for her enormous size. Still, she has leaves and she has bark. She turns sunlight into life. But this tree does not sprout from the dirt. Eden fills the sky, high in orbit above the blue expanse of Uranus.  There she changes humanity&apos;s very concept of extraterrestrial life. Dr. Malcolm Green is sent to Eden to audit a science team studying this extraordinary tree from the dark confines of space station Lola. But with unexplainable accidents plaguing the team, tensions are mounting between scientists and custodial staff. Is there a future for this project and Lola?  Only Malcolm Green can make that call. From the second he sets foot on Lola, Malcolm&apos;s own future becomes at stake.  He soon finds that love, friendship, and his own mortality tremble like a leaf at the sound of Eden&apos;s call. Eden is the latest podcast fiction offering from Phil Rossi, author of Crescent and Notes from the Vault.  ]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Crescent - A free podcast novel by Phil Rossi]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/crescent/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Crescent - A free audiobook by Phil Rossi]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/crescent/" description="<![CDATA[Crescent is the last stop at the intergalactic crossroads of gritty sci-fi and pucker-inducing horror. --Scott Sigler, New York Times bestselling author of ContagiousCrescent is the ultimate sci-fi / horror mashup. It&apos;s a wicked blend of the claustrophobia seen in Ridley Scott&apos;s Alien, and the viral demonology of Carpenter&apos;s Prince Of Darkness with the hard-drinkin&apos; bad attitude of Battlestar Galactica added for good measure. The future has never been so frightening. Phil Rossi brings it. --J.C. Hutchins, author of Personal Effects: Dark Art and 7th Son: DescentPhil Rossi has crafted a space station tale with sex, horror, and vibrant attention to tech and human detail. Evocatively served, highly recommended. ---Paul Levinson, author of The Plot to Save SocratesDarkness has inspired fear since mankind first watched the sun go down. Bad things hide in the dark feral beasts with mouths full of razors waiting for a taste of flesh. But now, the darkness is stirring with a life of its own. Crescent Station is the last bastion of civilization, floating in the cold, outer systems where colonized space gives way to the sparser settlements of the Frontier. Like the boom towns of distant Earth s Old American West, Crescent Station is a gateway to power, wealth, and opportunity for anyone who isn t afraid to get his or her hands dirty. But deep within the station s bowels, in Crescent s darkest and most secret places, an ancient evil is awakening and hungry, and it threatens the very fabric of space and time. Will the residents of Crescent Station find a way to stop it before the terror drives them insane? Or is it already too late?This is the original Podiobook as released in 2007.]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by .  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
