<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>&#039;s Works &amp; Podnovels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Checkwolf&#039;s Website]]>" url="http://checkwolf.com/" type="link" text="<![CDATA[Checkwolf&#039;s Website]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" url="" type="link" text="<![CDATA[]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Checkwolf: Book 1]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/checkwolf-1/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Checkwolf: Book 1 - A free audiobook by Remy Gibson]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/checkwolf-1/" description="<![CDATA[Checkwolf is a crimefighting organization, a group of talented vigilantes who have come together to battle corruption in their own way. Led by the enigmatic Sean Matts, this group of a dozen skilled men venture out into a small-scale area in the fictional metropolis named Kewanee, righting wrongs that the police are unable to touch.  Initially, they operate from a small garage owned by one of the Checkwolf members, the epitome of a minor operation.  But Sean Matts has a greater vision for his group, one that will take them from their humble beginnings and turn them into a force to be feared.The Checkwolf series is a collection of stories chronicling the activities of Checkwolf&#039;s third phase, from its mainstream recognition to its full integration.  Book 1 is a group of general stories: getting to know Checkwolf and their methods as they gain mainstream recognition, watching them learn and adapt to new situations.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Checkwolf: Book 2]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/checkwolf-2/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Checkwolf: Book 2 - A free audiobook by Remy Gibson]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/checkwolf-2/" description="<![CDATA[The second of four books about the fictional crimefighting team known as Checkwolf picks up directly after the first.  The members of Checkwolf get a chance to meet a childhood idol, expand their team, and encounter new strangeness as they work to make the city they live in safer, one criminal at a time.The Checkwolf series is a collection of stories chronicling the activities of Checkwolf&#039;s third phase, from its mainstream recognition to its full integration.Book 2 features a mix of different kinds of stories, including appearances by other characters in the Checkwolf universe.  After becoming familiar with the mission and methods of Checkwolf in Book 1, the slightly different feel and perspective of many of these stories help to reflect the maturation of the group as a force in the fictional city of Kewanee.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Checkwolf: Book 3]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/checkwolf-3/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Checkwolf: Book 3 - A free audiobook by Remy Gibson]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/checkwolf-3/" description="<![CDATA[The third of four books in the Checkwolf series examines the aftereffects of the drama from the end of the previous book, as well as introducing a major new threat to the organization and city they are sworn to protect, all while the team tries to maintain unity within the ranks.The Checkwolf series is a collection of stories chronicling the activities of Checkwolf&#039;s third phase, from its mainstream recognition to its full integration.Book 3 demonstrates a darker and more threatening tone than the previous two releases - which is no surprise in view of the concluding moments of Book 2.  The ability of the group to function as a team is put under a constant strain, reflecting the difficult times they are facing.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Checkwolf: Book 4]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/checkwolf-4/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/checkwolf-4/" text="<![CDATA[Checkwolf: Book 4 Failure not Tolerated- a free podcast novel by Remy Gibson]]>" description="<![CDATA[<p>The forth and final book of the Checkwolf series picks up directly after the events of the previous book. Operatives of Master, the antagonist that Checkwolf has been made progressively more aware of, kick into high gear, and Checkwolf is tasked with trying to figure out exactly what is going on. Though things look increasingly bleak, there is light at the end of the tunnel....</p><p>The Checkwolf series is a collection of stories chronicling the activities of Checkwolf's third phase, from its mainstream recognition to its full integration.</p><p>In Book 4 are some of the darkest moments in the entire series. Expect major changes to occur. Also, the format of the book is altered slightly, as Book 4 is a coherent whole, "number 38", if you will.</p>]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by Remy Gibson]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
