<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Richard S. Tuttle</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" url="" type="link" text="<![CDATA[]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Richard S. Tuttle]]>" url="http://rstuttle.com/" type="link" text="<![CDATA[Richard S. Tuttle&apos;s Homepage]]>" description="<![CDATA[Richard S. Tuttle&apos;s Homepage]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Richard S. Tuttle]]>" url="http://rstuttle.com/library.htm" type="link" text="<![CDATA[Richard S. Tuttle&apos;s Audiobooks]]>" description="<![CDATA[Richard S. Tuttle&apos;s Audiobooks library]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Origin Scroll, Book 1 of the Targa Trilogy]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/origin-scroll/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Origin Scroll, Book 1 of the Targa Trilogy - A free audiobook by Richard S. Tuttle<br/>Origin Scroll is the first volume of the Targa Trilogy and the cornerstone of the epic fantasy Alcea Collection which spans sixteen volumes in three series.]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/origin-scroll/" description="<![CDATA[Alexander Tork is an apprentice lumberman, a fifteen year old who is forced to take the lead when his village is attacked by a pack of vicious beasts. But darker things lurk in the lands of Targa and Cordonia, an evil questing for an artifact that will shake the very Universe. Alex, and two more unknown youths, Oscar and Jenneva, are the only ones who can prevent the end of their universe... they just don&apos;t know it yet.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Dark Quest, Book 2 of the Targa Trilogy]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/dark-quest/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Dark Quest, Book 2 of the Targa Trilogy - A free audiobook by Richard S. Tuttle<br/>Dark Quest is the second volume of the Targa Trilogy, which is the cornerstone of the epic fantasy Alcea Collection which spans seventeen volumes in three series. The Targa Trilogy began with Origin Scroll.]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/dark-quest/" description="<![CDATA[The evil magician, Sarac, has been banished to another Universe, but his followers strive to free him. Sarac&apos;s assistant. Mordac, gathers hundreds of dark magicians and instructs them to gather every book in the world, no matter what it takes. While his minions brutally execute his orders, Mordac plots the downfall of all of the governments on the continent. As Alexander and Jenneva try to halt the coming chaos, their own country turns against them.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Ancient Treasure, Book 3 of the Targa Trilogy]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/ancient-prophecy/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Ancient Treasure, Book 3 of the Targa Trilogy - A free audiobook by Richard S. Tuttle<br/>Dark Quest is the third volume of the Targa Trilogy, which is the cornerstone of the epic fantasy Alcea Collection which spans seventeen volumes in three series. The Targa Trilogy began with Origin Scroll.]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/ancient-prophecy/" description="<![CDATA[Ages ago, elves and dwarves unknowingly migrated between Universes via a Junction. Jenneva and Egam believe they have found a Junction and plan a trip with Alexander to test the theory and investigate the origins of the elves and dwarves. Because they believe that the perennial animosity between the two races is due to misunderstandings about their histories, the mages include the prince of elves and the prince of dwarves in the group. Trouble begins at the very start of the journey as Egam falters going through the Junction, awakening an old nemesis, the evil demon, Alutar. It appears that the excursion will not just clarify history, but actually change it. As the group discovers they are trapped in the new Universe, the shocking truth of the real history of the races is overshadowed by impending doom as an ancient prophecy begins to unfold. Meanwhile, the evil sorcerer, Sarac, not only gains freedom from his imprisonment, but also gains the blessing of the evil demon, Alutar. With the blessing, Sarac is given new powers and is promised a reign of a thousand years. The race is on to prevent Sarac from unfettered control of the Universes, as our trio stands incapable of altering the prophecy of destruction.&nbsp; Ancient Prophecy is the third volume of the Targa Trilogy."/>
	</body>
</opml>
