<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>The Works of: Seth Harwood.&nbsp; Podcasts, fiction, novels, &amp; audio dramas.</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[CrimeWAV]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/crimewav" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CrimeWAV - the crime stories podcast]]>" htmlUrl="http://crimewav.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CrimeWAV - the crime stories podcast</h1><p>This is the home for the premier series of crime short stories on the internet. This is the only podcast devoted to crime. THIS IS CRIMEWAV.</p>]]>" />
		<!-- <outline title="<![CDATA[CrimeWAV]]>" xmlUrl="http://crimewav.com/?q=feeds/all_podcasts.xml/8" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CrimeWAV - the crime stories podcast]]>" htmlUrl="http://crimewav.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CrimeWAV - the crime stories podcast</h1><p>This is the home for the premier series of crime short stories on the internet. This is the only podcast devoted to crime. THIS IS CRIMEWAV.</p>]]>" /> -->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Seth Harwood Audiobooks]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/sethharwood" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Seth Harwood Audiobooks]]>" htmlUrl="http://sethharwood.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Seth Harwood Audiobooks</h1><p>Before Jack Palms ever shook &apos;em down, Junius Ponds came up on tough streets outside Boston way back in the day.&nbsp; In the middle of drugs, gang violence, and the toughest set of tower-projects you ever knew, Young Junius fights to escape the consequences of a murder he had to commit and tries to live long enough to avenge the death of his brother.</p>]]>" />
		<!-- <outline title="<![CDATA[Seth Harwood Audiobooks]]>" xmlUrl="http://sethharwood.com/feeds/all_podcasts.xml/4" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Seth Harwood Audiobooks]]>" htmlUrl="http://sethharwood.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Seth Harwood Audiobooks</h1><p>Before Jack Palms ever shook &apos;em down, Junius Ponds came up on tough streets outside Boston way back in the day.&nbsp; In the middle of drugs, gang violence, and the toughest set of tower-projects you ever knew, Young Junius fights to escape the consequences of a murder he had to commit and tries to live long enough to avenge the death of his brother.</p>]]>" /> -->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Jack Wakes Up]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/jack-wakes-up/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Jack Wakes Up - A free audiobook by Seth Harwood]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/jack-wakes-up/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Jack Wakes Up by Seth Harwood</h1><p>What does a movie-star one-hit-wonder and ex-drug-addict do when he&apos;s cleaned up, down on his luck, and running out of money?&nbsp; In the three years since Jack Palms went clean - no drugs, no drinking, no life -  he&apos;s added fourteen pounds of muscle, read 83 books, and...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Jack Palms II: This Is Life]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/jack-palms-II-this-is-life/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Jack Palms II: This Is Life - A free audiobook by Seth Harwood]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/jack-palms-II-this-is-life/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Jack Palms II: This Is Life by Seth Harwood</h1><p>Jack Is Back!&nbsp; Yes, Jack Palms is back to bring you more of the action, suspense and excitement that you came to expect from the hit podiobook Jack Wakes Up.&nbsp; In This Is Life, Jack Palms finds himself caught in a working relationship with none other than the San Francisco police.&nbsp; When one of their own gets killed and corruption invades the Hall of Justice, Sgt.&nbsp; Mills Hopkins hires Jack to poke around.&nbsp; Is Jack ready for his own brand of police work?&nbsp; Is San Francisco?&nbsp; Follow Jack Palms as...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Jack Palms 3]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/jack-palms-3/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Jack Palms 3 - A free audiobook by Seth Harwood]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/jack-palms-3/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Jack Palms 3 by Seth Harwood</h1><p>This is where it boils down, eager listeners.&nbsp; JACK PALMS is back out on the streets of San Francisco after a brief stint in the hospital, and he&apos;s ready to track down the man at the heart of the city&apos;s problems, Alexi Akakievich.&nbsp; With the Czechs back in town, Detective Shaw more pissed off than ever, and a new batch of thugs on the loose, everything&apos;s dialed up to eleven once again.&nbsp; Will Jack make it through this?&nbsp; Will we see JACK PALMS 4? Listen now to follow this action-packed, episodic...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Young Junius]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/young-junius/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Young Junius - A free audiobook by Seth Harwood]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/young-junius/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Young Junius by Seth Harwood</h1><p>Before Jack Palms ever shook &apos;em down, Junius Ponds came up on tough streets outside Boston way back in the day.&nbsp; In the middle of drugs, gang violence, and the toughest set of tower-projects you ever knew, Young Junius fights to escape the consequences of a murder he had to commit and tries to live long enough to avenge the death of his brother.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[CrimeWAV]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/crimewav/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CrimeWAV - A free audiobook by Seth Harwood]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/crimewav/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CrimeWAV by Seth Harwood</h1><p>CrimeWAV.com is a new podcast series of crime short stories by some of today&apos;s best contemporary writers in the genre.&nbsp; Call it detective fiction, hard boiled, action, mystery, whatever you want.&nbsp; This is the place for the stories you&apos;ll love!</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[CrimeWAV Season 3]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/crimewav-3/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CrimeWAV Season 3 - A free audiobook by Seth Harwood]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/crimewav-3/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CrimeWAV Season 3 by Seth Harwood</h1><p>CrimeWAV is a podcast series of crime stories that I?m continuing with the aim of introducing the work of published crime writers, some of the great folks I?ve been able to meet, to the podcast crime audience that I?ve developed with my JACK PALMS CRIME podcasts.&nbsp; I?m doing this for two reasons: I want to bring some of the great work that?s out there by people in the crime writing scene to the crime listeners I?ve developed with my podcast series?&nbsp; I want to give my listeners more great crime...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[A Long Way from Disney - Part I]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/a-long-way-from-disney/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[A Long Way from Disney - Part I - A free audiobook by Seth Harwood]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/a-long-way-from-disney/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>A Long Way from Disney - Part I by Seth Harwood</h1><p>It&apos;s the 1980s in Boston: the Celtics are rolling, the Patriots got crushed by the Bears, and the Sox are the Sox.&nbsp; Adam Berkman is learning how far from the warm feelings and epiphanies of Disney Americana his life can be when his parents get a divorce and he has to...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[A Long Way from Disney - Part II]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/a-long-way-from-disney-2/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[A Long Way from Disney - Part II - A free audiobook by Seth Harwood]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/a-long-way-from-disney-2/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>A Long Way from Disney - Part II by Seth Harwood</h1><p>In the second season of A Long Way from Disney, an older (and perhaps wiser) Adam Berkman deals with his own series of relationships, love, marriage, and the ever-difficult question of what does one do with his or her life.&nbsp; It&apos;s about decisions now, not just fun in the twenties.&nbsp; Boston, New York, and the middle of the Midwest are backdrops to the stories here.</p>]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast audio drama from ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by .  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
	</body>
</opml>
