<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			Sir Arthur Conan Doyle&apos; podcast novels of his great works.
			&nbsp; Thnx to: the public domain, passionate readers, Project Gutenberg, and LibriVox.org
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Adventures of Sherlock  Holmes by Sir Arthur Conan Doyle]]>" xmlUrl="http://librivox.org/bookfeeds/the-adventures-of-sherlock-holmes.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Librivox: Adventures of Sherlock  Holmes, The by Sir Doyle Arthur Conan]]>" htmlUrl="http://librivox.org/the-adventures-of-sherlock-holmes/" description="<![CDATA[<p>The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes is a collection of twelve stories by Sir Arthur Conan Doyle, featuring his famous detective. They were originally published in the Strand Magazine from July 1891 to June 1892. The title character was named after famous American poet Oliver Wendell Holmes, Sr. (Summary from Wikipedia)</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Memoirs of Sherlock Holmes, The by Doyle, Arthur Conan, Sir]]>" xmlUrl="http://librivox.org/bookfeeds/the-memoirs-of-sherlock-holmes-by-sir-arthur-conan-doyle.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Memoirs of Sherlock Holmes, The by Doyle, Arthur Conan, Sir]]>" htmlUrl="http://librivox.org/the-memoirs-of-sherlock-holmes-by-sir-arthur-conan-doyle/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>http://librivox.org/the-memoirs-of-sherlock-holmes-by-sir-arthur-conan-doyle/</h1>Sherlock Holmes is a fictional detective of the late 19th and early 20th centuries, who first appeared in publication in 1887.&nbsp; He was devised by Scottish author and doctor Sir Arthur Conan Doyle.&nbsp; A brilliant London-based detective, Holmes is famous for his prowess at using logic and astute observation to solve cases.&nbsp; He is perhaps the most famous fictional detective, and indeed one of the best known and most universally recognizable literary characters.&nbsp; Join Dr.&nbsp; Watson and Sherlock Holmes, in Holmes&apos; fourth book. (summary from Wikipedia and TBOL3)]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Return of Sherlock Holmes, The by Doyle, Arthur Conan, Sir]]>" xmlUrl="http://librivox.org/bookfeeds/the-return-of-sherlock-holmes-by-sir-arthur-conan-doyle.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Return of Sherlock Holmes, The by Doyle, Arthur Conan, Sir]]>" htmlUrl="http://librivox.org/the-return-of-sherlock-holmes-by-sir-arthur-conan-doyle/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>http://librivox.org/the-return-of-sherlock-holmes-by-sir-arthur-conan-doyle/</h1>Having left Sherlock Holmes apparently deceased at the conclusion of The Final Problem (in The Memoirs of Sherlock Holmes), we now find that he is alive after all!&nbsp; In this collection, first published in 1905, the great detective causes Watson to faint (The Empty House), demonstrates that cryptography is elementary (The Dancing Men), and gets engaged (Charles Augustus Milverton).  Join in the fun as Holmes deduces his way through these thirteen adventures.  (summary by Laurie Anne Walden)]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>

