<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>&#039;s Works &amp; Podnovels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" url="" type="link" text="<![CDATA[]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Colorado Squence]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-colorado-sequence/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Colorado Squence - A free audiobook by Stacey Cochran, narrated by Owen Daly]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-colorado-sequence/" description="<![CDATA[Physicist Dr. Amy Levine has discovered a mathematical sequence--the Colorado Sequence--that describes an underlying pattern and a guiding force within the very fabric of reality. Now she&#039;s on the verge of an astonishing breakthrough, and the U.S. government wants to know how she has done it. How has Dr. Levine learned to accurately predict the future? And they&#039;re willing to kill her to find out. Levine and a group of friends escape to Colorado to unravel the mystery of the sequence, but there they become snowbound. They must locate a secret treasure room, find a hidden key, and answer an ancient riddle before a devastating eruption destroys them all ... and the power of the Colorado Sequence is lost forever.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Kiribati Test]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-kiribati-test/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Kiribati Test - A free audiobook by Stacey Cochran]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-kiribati-test/" description="<![CDATA[Kickass scifi and crime fiction collection in the tradition of Philip K. Dick and Jim Thompson.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Amber Page and the Legend of the Coral Stone]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/amber-page-and-the-legend-of-the-coral-stone/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Amber Page and the Legend of the Coral Stone - A free audiobook by Stacey Cochran]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/amber-page-and-the-legend-of-the-coral-stone/" description="<![CDATA[On the island of Maui, a sixteen-year-old international spy named Rio Kayenta discovers a two-thousand-year-old coral stone. Legend has it that the stone is meant for a girl named Amber and that with it, she can stop the evil S.H.R.O.U.D. organization. Amber Page lives in the Arizona desert and wants one thing more than anything else in the world: to see her mom and dad back together again. Amber&#039;s mom is a school bus driver who has split with her dad, but Amber believes the two still love one another. When a strange old man stops at nothing to tell Amber that the legendary stone is meant for her, it frightens her and her family deeply. It is a race against the clock to get the stone to Amber and to see if she will realize its legendary powers. For with the stone strengthening her, Amber may be able to save her family and the world.]]>"/>
	</body>
</opml>
