<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			Steven H. Wilson&apos;s podcast novels, fiction, &amp; audio dramas.
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Prometheus Radio Theatre]]>" xmlUrl="http://prometheus.libsyn.com/rss" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Prometheus Radio Theatre features all-original Science Fiction and Horror audio theatre content.]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.prometheusradiotheatre.com/" description="<![CDATA[Prometheus Radio Theatre, a group of experienced Baltimore-area Fan actors, writers and directors, is embarking on what we like to think is a bold, new path (then again, maybe we&apos;re just deranged!)  We&apos;re bringing original, SF radio dramas to Fan audiences at area conventions, and we plan to offer said dramas via CD and streaming audio in the near future.&nbsp; Our current project is an episodic series, The Arbiter Chronicles, which author Steve Wilson describes as &quot;a sort of Hornblower the Vampire Slayer in Space.&quot;  &quot;Arbiters&quot; tells the tale of young midshipmen (and women) in a future Navy, when the human race has expanded off earth, and things ain&apos;t as bright and cheerful as some might expect.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Taken Liberty - A Tale from the Arbiter Chronicles]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/taken-liberty---a-tale-from-the-arbiter-chronicles/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Taken Liberty - A Tale from the Arbiter Chronicles - A free audiobook by Steven H. Wilson]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/taken-liberty---a-tale-from-the-arbiter-chronicles/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Taken Liberty - A Tale from the Arbiter Chronicles</h1><h3>by Steven H. Wilson</h3><p>Aer&apos;La only wants to be free...The Confederated Worlds are unparalleled as a society of free people, yet, somehow, slavery still manages to exist.&nbsp; Aer&apos;La, a non-human, was bred to serve as a pleasure slave.&nbsp; Years ago, she escaped her masters and masqueraded as a human, joining the Confederate Navy, where she worked her way up to ship&apos;s Bos&apos;n under the heroic Captain Jan Atal.&nbsp; Now, Aer&apos;La&apos;s secret has been discovered by Atal&apos;s superiors, the media, and the world at large.&nbsp; Branded a sociopath, she learns that even a free society isn&apos;t willing to grant freedom - or justice - to all.Library Journal says: &quot;The author of the Arbiter Chronicles, an award-winning audio drama, vividly brings to life a cast of compelling characters while telling a story that measures the cost of freedom.&nbsp; The far-future military setting should appeal to fans of David Weber&apos;s &quot;Honor Harrington&quot; series as well as the military sf of David Drake.&quot;</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Peace Lord of the Red Planet]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/peace-lord-of-the-red-planet/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Peace Lord of the Red Planet - A free audiobook by Steven H. Wilson]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/peace-lord-of-the-red-planet/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Peace Lord of the Red Planet</h1><h3>by Steven H. Wilson</h3><p>Shepherd Autrey is a Quaker, a physician, and a man deeply disturbed by the madness around him as the War Between the tates bears down on his America in 1863.&nbsp; Dared by a friend to take an active role, Shep volunteers to provide humanitarian aid to the victims of Sherman&apos;s scorched earth campaign in the Shenandoah Valley.&nbsp; There he runs foul of a Confederate recruiting drive and fi nds himself hanged by the neck from a tree.&nbsp; Awakening in a strange land which can&apos;t possibly be earth, Shep is plunged into battle and saves the life of an alien warrior prince.&nbsp; Hailed by bloodthirsty killers as the bravest man alive, Shep combats his conscience, his lagging faith, and an ever-growing number of people who want him dead.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>

