<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Zombie podcast audio drama</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[HG World: An Original Zombie Horror Serial]]>" xmlUrl="http://3015north.podomatic.com/rss2.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[HG World: An Original Zombie Horror Serial]]>" htmlUrl="http://3015north.podOmatic.com" description="<![CDATA[<p>3015 North Studios brings you the audio horror serial "HG WORLD" telling the story of a small town riding out a global zombie uprising from inside the walls of a massive House and Garden warehouse in the rurals of north-central Pennsylvania.  </p><p>This is a full-cast audio drama presented by the HG WORLD COMPANY PLAYERS.</p><p>TODD RAGE: THE REQUEST LINE is OPEN! (206) 350-3317 Tell us about your zombie experiences, share your thoughts on the show, flirt with Ayoub Khote, tell Jeb where to stick it....anything! Call now!</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[We're Alive - A &quot;Zombie&quot; Story of survival.]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.zombiepodcast.com/The_Zombie_Podcast/Were_Alive_-_Podcast/rss.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[We're Alive - A &quot;Zombie&quot; Story of survival.]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.zombiepodcast.com/The_Zombie_Podcast/Were_Alive_-_Podcast/Were_Alive_-_Podcast.html/" description="<![CDATA[A classic style radio drama. With a full cast of actors and full realized sound effects and music track, you will feel like you are there!  A small riot in LA has spread past its containment. Three reserve soldiers are called to their deserted duty station. Believed to be the last remaining armed servicemen in the area, Michael, Angel, and Saul witness the true cause of the riot; people are starting to change and attack each other. Armed with only what they can carry, they set out to secure an apartment building and rescue survivors scattered amongst the shattered remains of civilization. In a world turned upside down, every day is a struggle, as those who have taken refuge in the tower find out that their safe haven is under constant threat. In this place, however, the strengths of those who stand together, might just be enough to live long enough to see things start to change.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[You've Got Dead On You]]>" xmlUrl="http://deadonyou.libsyn.com/rss" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[You've Got Dead On You Studios]]>" htmlUrl="http://deadonyou.blogspot.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>You've Got Dead On You Studios</h1><p>You&apos;ve Got Dead On You Studios, where all things zombie come to feast upon awesomeness.</p><p>Join Dead On You Studios owner Craig, with co-founder Jay and the hapless Announcer as they venture into the world of zombies.&nbsp; From debating zombie topics, assessing how well a city will survive a zombie apocalypse, providing commentary on zombie movies and, of course, their pride and joy, the &quot;You&apos;ve Got Dead On You&quot; zombie comedy.</p><p>If you love zombies, this is the place to be.</p><p>All characters appearing in this world are fictitious.&nbsp; Any resemblance to real persons, living, dead, or undead, is purely coincidental.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
