<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>CyberPunk Works &amp; Podnovels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" url="" type="link" text="<![CDATA[]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Self Made » MP3 Podcast]]>" xmlUrl="http://darusha.ca/selfmade/category/podcast/mp3/?feed=rss2" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://darusha.ca/selfmade/category/podcast/" text="<![CDATA[Self Made - a podcast novel by M. Darusha Wehm]]>" description="<![CDATA[<p><i>Ever wish things were different?</i></p><p>Ivy Velasquez did, so she became someone else. In the 3D virtual world Marionette City, you can be anything you want — but everyone still knows who you are. Driven by her desire for a new life, Ivy takes her future in her hands when she makes another identity for herself. A brilliant designer, Ivy works for one of the huge firms which control the online system the world relies upon for both business and pleasure. But one day, Ivy discovers that her alternate self, Reuben Cobalt, had been murdered.</p><p>Since alternate identities are forbidden by the firms which control access to the nets and to M City, Ivy has nowhere to turn — until she finds Andersson Dexter. Part private eye, part vigilante and part cop, Dex sets out to uncover Reuben’s killer. Since the firms control almost every aspect of life, including law and order, justice for average people comes only at the hands of the outlaw organization to which Dex belongs.</p><p>Self Made is a murder mystery set in a vision of a future that seems to lurk just over the horizon. But above all, it is a story of how people strive to control their own destinies, and how that desire affects them and the people around them in ways they could never imagine.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Beautiful Red » MP3 Podcast]]>" xmlUrl="http://darusha.ca/beautifulred/category/podcast/mp3/?feed=rss2" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Beautiful Red - A free podcast novel - by M. Darusha Wehm]]>" htmlUrl="http://darusha.ca/beautifulred/category/podcast/" description="<![CDATA[The future is boring. Technology has solved the world&apos;s most pressing problems, leaving people with tedious work and mundane play. Jack is a Security Officer Class 5, which sounds important, but isn&apos;t. However, her banal life as a cubicle worker by day and tinkerer by night is interrupted when she discovers that her employer&apos;s computer system has been invaded.&nbsp; Jack enlists the help of her only friends - her co-worker, Gilles and Adrian, an online friend she&apos;s never met - to help her track down the source of the invasion. Her investigation leads her to a shadowy group called the Red, where Jack learns that not everyone lives a life of quiet servitude.&nbsp; Even though she believes that the Red are responsible for a series of gruesome attacks, Jack begins to become attracted to their worldview. In her search for the people responsible for the attacks, she confronts the leaders of the group as well as her own burgeoning sense of self-awareness.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Spherical Tomi: A Novel of Despair]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/spherical-tomi-a-novel-of-despair/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Spherical Tomi: A Novel of Despair - A free audiobook by Jack Mangan]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/spherical-tomi-a-novel-of-despair/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Spherical Tomi: A Novel of Despair - A free audiobook</h1><p>A deadly power struggle between warlords.&nbsp; Tomi was once lead combat programmer for the Shogun Ryogi, on the front lines of his conflict against President William the Black of Cerberus.&nbsp; When she failed to prevent William from killing the samurai she loved, she abandoned all sides, all loyalties, all hope.&nbsp; In her fury, Tomi destroyed the Greatship, Hades IV, and almost everyone onboard.&nbsp; Almost everyone. . .William the Black escaped with his life.&nbsp; She now hides out in a remote monastery, awaiting the day when she can kill the three she holds responsible for the death of her samurai:  William, Ryogi, and herself. . .With her real body in exile, Tomi&apos;s consciousness inhabits a deteriorating clone body on a satellite around Cerberus.&nbsp; She&apos;s lived and worked incognito in orbit for almost three years now, monitoring the planet&apos;s subspace debris cleanup.&nbsp; But some histories will not stay buried.&nbsp; Tomi again finds herself in the crossfire when Ryogi&apos;s forces ambush the Presidential shuttle in her sector.&nbsp; Ryogi&apos;s samurai have pirated remote control of her satellite&apos;s store of dormant clone bodies; his combat programmers fight her for the station&apos;s computers, while the planet&apos;s extrasphere swarms with deadly smart-mines.&nbsp; Will she be able to protect the President&apos;s shuttle to secure her own vengeance?&nbsp; Will she be able to hold her satellite together?&nbsp; Or will Tomi abandon it all and give in to despair?&quot;Spherical Tomi&quot; is an action-packed tale of deception, revenge, redemption, fragmented identity, and the limitations of the human and artificial mind.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Digital Magic]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.digitalmagicnovel.com/?cat=4&feed=rss2" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.digitalmagicnovel.com/?cat=4" text="<![CDATA[Digital Magic by Philippa J. Ballantine &ndash; Where the Future &amp; Fey Collide]]>" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Digital Magic is the sequel to Chasing the Bard- the award winning podcast novel–written by New Zealand author Philippa Ballantine.</h1><p>Penherem is a quaint, sleepy English village where people go to escape the 21st Century.&nbsp; Hiding from the world of laptop computers, the Internet, and wireless communication, is Ella.&nbsp; A writer, now barren of ideas and drive, she resigns herself to a quiet life of solitude.&nbsp; Everything changes with the arrival of a shapeshifting thief.&nbsp; Suddenly, everyone begins to change–from the local librarian to the lady of the manor–revealing their true natures and dangerous secrets.&nbsp; Something in this sleepy English village is awakening… something that might be better left alone.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Cybrosis]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/cybrosis" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.cybrosisnovel.com/" text="<![CDATA[Cybrosis - A podcast novel by P.C. Haring]]>" description="<![CDATA[Cybrosis is a podcast novel written and narrated by P.C. Haring with the voice talents of some of the biggest names in the podcasting community including Philippa Ballantine, Christiana Ellis, Podcasting’s Rich Sigfrit, Mur Lafferty, Chris Lester, Chuck Tomasi, and Heather Welliver.&nbsp; This full length podcast novel hacks your RSS feeds on 01/01/10]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - A free audiobook by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
