<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Present Day Fantasy Podcast novels from Podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The House of Grey]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-house-of-grey/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The House of Grey - A free audiobook by Collin Earl]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-house-of-grey/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The House of Grey - A free audiobook</h1><p>14-year-old Monson Grey faces the same challenges that any freshman high school kid would.&nbsp; Difficult classes, weird teachers, food fights...girls.&nbsp; Except Monson Grey is not Monson Grey.&nbsp; At least, when he looks at himself in the mirror, the scarred face staring back is not someone he recognizes.&nbsp; Now he finds himself attending an extraordinary school, the recipient of an incredible scholarship, among ridiculously rich classmates, and with no memory of how he got there or what to expect.&nbsp; As bizarre events start to unfold around him, Monson wonders what secrets lay locked in his hidden past.&nbsp; Add all this to a mysterious silver stone, an Indiana-Jones-copycat professor, Merlin the wizard, and even Atlantis, and you&apos;ll find yourself in a fantastic tale in which magic does exist and everything is never as it seems.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Servant and the Soothsayer]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-servant-and-the-soothsayer/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Servant and the Soothsayer - A free audiobook by Eugene Fairfield]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-servant-and-the-soothsayer/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Servant and the Soothsayer - by Eugene Fairfield</h1><p>Paulo, a domestic servant with a reputation for back-talk, is witness to a political murder.&nbsp; When a soothsayer is brought in to solve the crime, she sees Paulo as a tool: he can get close to the suspect, whereas she, as a known mind-reader, would instantly be recognized as a threat.&nbsp; But if Paulo works for her, he may get black-balled by the corporation that provides him job, room, and board.&nbsp; He will certainly get caught in a political conspiracy.&nbsp; If that weren&apos;t enough, there are stories that soothsayers can cause terrible psychic damage, and this one, people say, has something of a temper.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>

