<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Podcast Novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Tales of the Left Hand]]>" xmlUrl="http://talesofthelefthand.com/podcast/?feed=rss2" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://talesofthelefthand.com/podcast/?feed=rss2" text="<![CDATA[Tales of the Left Hand - Swashbuckling, intrigue and a dash of magic]]>" description="<![CDATA[Tales of the Left Hand is a fantasy audiobook written and recorded by John Meagher.  A tale of swashbuckling, intrigue, and a dash of magic.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Empress Sword Podcast]]>" xmlUrl="http://empresssword.com/?feed=podcast" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Empress Sword Podcast]]>" htmlUrl="http://empresssword.com/" description="<![CDATA[A podcast novel by Paulette Jaxton.  A fantasy novel by Paulette Jaxton. The story of a dragon, a prince and a magic sword, but no one is quite what they seem in the kingdom of Caledon.This is not your fathers epic adventure story, but it might just be your mothers.]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[Outcast]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.mevio.com/feeds/outcastnovel.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Outcast]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.mevio.com/shows/?show=outcastnovel" description="<![CDATA[<![CDATA[Dalan Kalamar, a young aristocrat, finds himself stripped of his title, name, and family.  Now an outcast from society, he is forced into a life of marginal living, manual labour, and avoiding the murderous intentions of people once considered his friends.]]>]]>" />-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Outcast]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/podshow/outcast?format=xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Outcast - a free podcast novel by Chris Hvidston]]>" htmlUrl="http://outcastnovel.wordpress.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h3>Dalan Kalamar had it all.</h3><p>An life of luxury, a loving family, and intended bride, and a destiny that would one day see him assume the Eldership of his Clan.</p><p>Then, on a dark night in his 12th year of life, four would-be assassins changed all that. Charged by his father with protecting a sacred artifact, Dalan was left for dead by his attackers, and the artifact subsequently stolen.</p><p>One year later, Dalan awakens from a comatose state not only to find his body healed, but also to the fact that his family has disowned him. Humiliated before his peers, the would-be heir to the Tiger’s Paw Clan is cast out to live amongst the lowest of the low in Bengalan society:</p><h3>The exiles.</h3><p>Outcasts from the Clans, the exiles are a society unto themselves, shunned by all and forced to live in secret. They move through the secular, non-Clan world under the cover of assumed identities, taking jobs where strong backs are favored over questionable pasts. Through an elaborate underground network known as The Foundation, many exiles have found some glimmer of hope in a world committed to rooting them out and exterminating them like so much vermin.</p><p>It is into this world that a 13-year old Dalan is thrust. With no money and only a tiny bit of martial arts training, the young tiger begins his journey through the dark underbelly of Bengalan society. His eyes are quickly opened to the true brutality of the Clans, as he bears witness to an act so horrifying that he begins to question all he’d been brought up to believe.</p><p>Hope does exist for the young tiger, however…in the form of a mysterious trainer who extends an offer to him. The offer is to train Dalan in an ancient fighting form…one that will transform him from a desperate, fearful exile into a beast to be feared and respected by all. The young tiger accepts, and before long finds himself on a journey towards a destiny that will challenge all he’s ever known and believed, and make him see the world in a new, cold light.</p><p>He also finds hope in the loving arms of a fellow exile, one from a far off land running from an alleged curse put on her by those who cast her out. As their love for each other grows, Dalan soon finds himself faced with a choice: Devote his life to his newfound love and abandon any hope of regaining his honor…</p><p>Or risk losing everything for one chance at bloody, unforgiving vengeance</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Morevi: Remastered - A free audiobook by Tee Morris]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/morevi?format=xml" text="<![CDATA[Morevi: Remastered - A free podcast novel by Tee Morris]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.teemorris.com/morevipodcast/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Morevi: Remastered - A free audiobook by Tee Morris</h1><p>The Official Podcast of Rafe and Askana.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[AMNAR: THE AWAKENING - A FREE audiobook BY ISABEL JOELY BLACK]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/amnar-the-awakening/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.joelyblack.net/Amnar/Amnar%3A_The_Awakening.html" text="<![CDATA[AMNAR: THE AWAKENING - A FREE podcast novel BY ISABEL JOELY BLACK]]>" description="<![CDATA[<h1>AMNAR: THE AWAKENING - A FREE audiobook BY ISABEL JOELY BLACK</h1><p>One young woman is about to change the course of history. If she can change her own life first. She is awakening to a new way of being, beyond her wildest dreams. She has the capacity to change and improve the lives of millions... If she has the courage...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[AMNAR: THE AWAKENING - A FREE audiobook BY ISABEL JOELY BLACK]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.joelyblack.net/Amnar/The_Awakening_Podcast/rss.xml" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.joelyblack.net/Amnar/The_Awakening_Podcast/The_Awakening_Podcast.html" text="<![CDATA[AMNAR: THE AWAKENING - A FREE podcast novel BY ISABEL JOELY BLACK]]>" description="<![CDATA[<h1>AMNAR: THE AWAKENING - A FREE audiobook BY ISABEL JOELY BLACK</h1><p>One young woman is about to change the course of history. If she can change her own life first. She is awakening to a new way of being, beyond her wildest dreams. She has the capacity to change and improve the lives of millions... If she has the courage...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Corridor - A free podcast novel by Zan]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/the-corridor" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Corridor - A free podcast novel by Zan]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.the-corridor.info/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Corridor - A free audiobook by Zan</h1><p><h1>The Corridor - A free audiobook by Zan</h1><p>The Corridor is a fantasy/horror story about Stuart Morrow, a man who has lost all hope and reason to live. However, a strange coincidence brings him unexpectedly into contact with a multitude of worlds beyond our own. Hunted by a despot who rules over countless alternate realities, Stuart&apos;s only hope is to seek help amongst the assortment of bizarre and grotesque characters who await him in the Corridor.</p></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[DarkAge: A Fantasy Fiction Podcast Novel]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.mevio.com/feeds/darkage.xml" text="<![CDATA[DarkAge: A Fantasy Fiction Podcast Novel]]>" htmlUrl="http://kirkcast.com/" description="<![CDATA[A group of friends become trapped inside a fantasy role-playing game.]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Some Other Scotland - a free podcast novel by by Mick Bordet]]>" xmlUrl="http://someotherscotland.com/?feed=podcast" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://someotherscotland.com/" text="<![CDATA[Some Other Scotland - a free podcast novel by by Mick Bordet]]>" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Some Other Scotland - a free audiobook by by Mick Bordet</h1><p><h1>Some Other Scotland - a free audiobook by by Mick Bordet</h1><p>&quot;Some Other Scotland&quot; is a weekly podcast story of ancient advanced civilisations, clan wars and conspiracy in an alternative modern Scotland.</p></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Some Other Scotland - a free podcast novel by by Mick Bordet via Podiobooks.com]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/some-other-scotland/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/some-other-scotland/" text="<![CDATA[Some Other Scotland - a free podcast novel by by Mick Bordet via Podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Some Other Scotland - a free audiobook by by Mick Bordet via Podiobooks.com</h1><p><h1>Some Other Scotland - a free audiobook by by Mick Bordet via Podiobooks.com</h1><p><p>Gravestones across Scotland are being defaced. An ancient advanced civilisation is discovered under the remains of Skara Brae. Bonnie Prince Charlie returns to Scotland, two hundred years after his death. Edinburgh police unearth a mysterious surveillance operation on the Queen's residence and the Scottish Parliament. All these events take place in a Scotland which is both familiar and yet slightly twisted.</p><p>Detective Jim Sykes' investigation into hidden cameras and a long-dead pretender to the throne uncovers a sinister plot that dates back centuries before the term 'terrorism' was coined. Archaeologist Erica Wallis digs up more than she bargained for when she encounters an underground civilisation that has existed since before the pyramids of Egypt were built. When one of their misplaced, but deadly artifacts falls into the hands of young street-poet 'Razer', he is launched into the middle of a clan war that has been waged across the World for millenia.</p><p>Events triggered thousands of years ago are about to reach a climax that not only threatens Scotland, but could finally hand the modern World the tools of its own destruction.</p></p></p>]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[The Silverblade Prophecy]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.gcast.com/u/silverblade/main.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Silverblade Prophecy]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.gcast.com/u/silverblade/" description="<![CDATA[Throughout Pankea&apos;s history, messiahs have come and gone. Some succeeded but others fell. As an ancient evil reawakens, a new messiah is called to fulfill her long-prophesied birthright, but can she succeed when her ancestor could not? A young and innocent Marian Silverblade is determined to face her destiny and finds help in the most unlikely allies. But in order to prevent her life from getting snuffed out before the prophecy can be fulfilled, they must first learn how to work together - a task that may prove too difficult.]]>" />-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Silverblade Prophecy]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/TheSilverbladeProphecy?format=xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Silverblade Prophecy]]>" htmlUrl="http://pankea.wordpress.com/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Throughout Pankea's history, messiahs have come and gone. Some succeeded but others fell. As an ancient evil reawakens, a new messiah is called to fulfill her long-prophesied birthright, but can she succeed when her ancestor could not?</p><p>A young and innocent Marian Silverblade is determined to face her destiny and finds help in the most unlikely allies. But in order to prevent her life from getting snuffed out before the prophecy can be fulfilled, they must first learn how to work together - a task that may prove too difficult.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Fortress Draconis - A free podcast novel by Michael A. Stackpole]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.michaelastackpole.com/?cat=21&feed=rss2" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Fortress Draconis - A free podcast novel by Michael A. Stackpole]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.michaelastackpole.com/?cat=21" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Fortress Draconis - A free audiobook by Michael A. Stackpole</h1><p><p><b>Perchance to Dream</b> is the first piece of stand alone fiction from the <b>DragonCrown War</b> world. It chronicles Princess Alexia&#8217;s Dream Raid. The exiles from Okrannel determined that as their children came of age, they should spend one night on their native soil. The dreams they had that night were thought to be prophetic, and the key to their nation&#8217;s liberation. Since Alexia is supposed to be the instrument of that liberation, her dream is very important.</p><p>And some people want to make sure it&#8217;s her last.</p><p>I did the story for the Five Star anthology that came out in 2005, and it&#8217;s been reprinted no where else (save in the German translation of the same anthology).</p></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Mick Aloha&apos; podcast novels]]>" xmlUrl="http://mickaloha.com/fpn/?feed=rss2" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Mick Aloha&apos; podcast novels]]>" htmlUrl="http://mickaloha.com/fpn/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Mick Aloha&apos; audiobooks</h1><p><h1>Mick Aloha&apos; audiobooks</h1><p><a href='http://FreePodcastNovels.Com/'>FreePodcastNovels.Com</a> - Free Podnovels by <a href='http://mickaloha.com/'>Mick Aloha</a>.</p></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Fox - A free audiobook by Arlene Radasky]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.radasky.com/Site/Hear_The_Fox/rss.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Fox - A free podcast novel by Arlene Radasky]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.radasky.com/Site/Hear_The_Fox/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Fox - A free audiobook by Arlene Radasky</h1><p>><h2>adventure, ancient Celtic beliefs, sacrifice, love of family, ancient and modern culture, and divorce.</h2><p>Jahna and Lovern’s clan lay in the Romans’ path of destruction. The death of their people is a certainty, unless a bargain is made with the Gods, even if it means a human sacrifice.</p><h3>Will the trade the Druid Lovern and his visionary wife, Jahna make with the Gods, save their family?<br/>Will there be future generations to sing the songs of their dead?</h3><p>Two centuries later, Aine MacRae is on their trail. She’s a struggling archaeologist, on the verge of uncovering the village were Jahna and Lovern lived. She’s found the farm where her site is located is for sale! But for a ghostly, visit greed almost triumphs leaving the truth and ancient stories buried forever.</p><p>Listen to The Fox and discover if Jahna and Lovern’s bloodline continues and if Aine wins her independence, finds answers to haunting questions and allows a lost love to be rekindled</p>.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Legon Awakening]]>" xmlUrl="http://legonbook.com/blog/?feed=podcast" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Legon Awakening]]>" htmlUrl="http://legonbook.com/" description="<![CDATA[Set in a world that is not our own, Legon Awakening takes you through an epic journey into a land full of imagination and innovation.Join Legon and his sister, Sasha, search to understand their true heritage, confused at the possibility that of being part human and part elf. Surrounded by elves, the newly introduced Iumenta race, Dragons and Humans; Legon and Sasha&apos;s lives are filled with adventure and fantasy on their search for answers as they begin an epic journey of discovery; not to mention the incredible battle scenes which will be surely to capture your imagination!]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
	</body>
</opml>
