<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Ghost &amp; Sprit fantasy podcast novels from Podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Earthbound]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/earthbound/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Earthbound - A free audiobook by Artemis Greenleaf]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/earthbound/" description="<![CDATA[<p>&quot;I didn&apos;t believe in ghosts, not until I became one.&quot;Schuyler Ramsey just wants to be like the other kids in school.&nbsp; Too bad she&apos;s dead.&nbsp; She haunts a farm in windswept western Ireland, along with some of its previous inhabitants.&nbsp; When she partially materializes in front of her sister at breakfast, she is propelled on a quest to stop a fake TV psychic from visiting the farm and stirring up trouble.&nbsp; Along the way, she visits a famous pirate, helps a mermaid rescue a basking shark from fishermen, and encounters Nicniven, queen of the dark elphs.&nbsp; But Schuyler soon finds that the Haunted Planet television show is the least of her problems.&nbsp; As her world unravels, can she find the strength to save her sister from a monstrous evil?</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Freak City]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/freak-city/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Freak City - A free audiobook by Tom Lichtenberg]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/freak-city/" description="<![CDATA[It&apos;s hard to control your destiny while you&apos;re waiting for the bus. The trouble for Argus Kirkham began when a stranger pushed his way through a crowd at a bus stop and pressed a package into his hands. Inside the package were various random items - photos and toys and newspaper clippings. None of it seemed to make any sense, but as Argus and his friends unraveled the clues, very strange things began to occur in this novel of mystery and ghosts.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Purgatory]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/purgatory/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Purgatory - A free audiobook by Tim Dodge]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/purgatory/" description="<![CDATA[Charles Cunningham, a wealthy real estate developer, dies unexpectedly and finds himself in Purgatory, the place between heaven and hell.&nbsp; Though depressed about his early death, he befriends two other souls doing time there - the writer: &quot;Edgar Allan Poe&quot; and a music-loving deadbeat: &quot;Billy&quot;.&nbsp; Upon receiving a letter from God telling him he must learn some unnamed lessons before he can go to heaven, he convinces Poe to join him in the portal back to earth.&nbsp; They hope to make up for their past mistakes, but they arrive on earth in the year 2049, 42 years after Charles&apos; death.&nbsp; Traveling from mid-21st century New York City to Las Vegas, Charles seeks out the daughter he neglected in life, though she is now in her eighties.&nbsp; However, an unfriendly soul from Purgatory follows them to earth.&nbsp; This soul, an employee with whom Charles had an affair and summarily fired, is determined to keep him from winning passage to heaven.&nbsp; She teams up with Charles&apos; grandson, a debt-ridden gambling addict who has a talent for messing things up.&nbsp; Together, they hatch a deadly scheme to foil Charles&apos; plan to get to heaven and net the grandson badly-needed money.&nbsp; Charles learns of their plans and enlists his friends to help stop them.&nbsp; Will they succeed?&nbsp; The only way to find out is to subscribe.]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
