<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Supernatural &amp; Magickal podcast novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[House of Grey: A audiobook by Collin Earl]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/TheHouseOfGreyPodcast" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[House of Grey: A podcast novel by Collin Earl]]>" htmlUrl="http://houseofgreybook.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>House of Grey: A audiobook by Collin Earl</h1><p><h1>House of Grey: A audiobook by Collin Earl</h1><div>14-year-old Monson Grey faces the same challenges that any freshman high school kid would.&nbsp; Difficult classes, weird teachers, food fights...girls.&nbsp; Except Monson Grey is not Monson Grey.&nbsp; At least, when he looks at himself in the mirror, the scarred face staring back is not someone he recognizes.&nbsp; Now he finds himself attending an extraordinary school, the recipient of an incredible scholarship, among ridiculously rich classmates, and with no memory of how he got there or what to expect.&nbsp; As bizarre events start to unfold around him, Monson wonders what secrets lay locked in his hidden past.&nbsp; Add all this to a mysterious silver stone, an Indiana-Jones-copycat professor, Merlin the wizard, and even Atlantis, and you&apos;ll find yourself in a fantastic tale in which magic does exist and everything is never as it seems.</div></p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Inner Demons]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.innerdemonsnovel.com/?feed=rss2" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Inner Demons By Jeri Unselt]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.innerdemonsnovel.com/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Leave Your Fears &amp; Regrets at the door or it&&apos;s hell to pay.</p><p>In the summer of 1990, Jeff Holland, his family and members of his band Quicksilver entered the place known as Hawley Manor in the hopes of a comeback and a new life.&nbsp; A few days later, they were all found dead.</p><p>Because of Jeff’s history of drinking and drugs, police was assumed that he killed everyone inside and then took his own life.</p><p>Eighteen years later, a group of psychic investigators enter to find out what really happened so long ago.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Purgatory &amp; other &quot;Heartwarming&quot; Stories]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/HeartwarmingStoriesByTimDodge" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Purgatory by, Tim Dodge, is a novel about Charles Cunningham, a wealthy real estate developer, who dies unexpectedly and finds himself in Purgatory, the place between heaven and hell.&nbsp; Though depressed about his early death, he befriends two other souls doing time there ]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.timdodgestories.com" description="<![CDATA[Stories of action, humor, horror and outright weirdness from Tim Dodge.&nbsp; PURGATORY is a novel about Charles Cunningham, a wealthy real estate developer, who dies unexpectedly and finds himself in Purgatory, the place between heaven and hell.&nbsp; Though depressed about his early death, he befriends two other souls doing time there ndash;  the writer Edgar Allan Poe and a fun-loving beach bum named Billy.&nbsp; Upon receiving a letter from God telling him he must learn some unnamed lessons before he can go to heaven, he convinces Poe to join him in the portal back to earth.&nbsp; They hope to make up for their past mistakes, but they arrive on earth in the year 2049, 42 years after Charlesrs&quot; death.&nbsp; Traveling from mid-21st century New York City to Las Vegas, Charles seeks out the daughter he neglected in life, though she is now in her eighties.&nbsp; However, an unfriendly soul from Purgatory follows them to earth.&nbsp; This soul, an employee with whom Charles had an affair and summarily fired, is determined to keep him from winning passage to heaven.&nbsp; She teams up with Charlesrsquo; grandson, a debt-ridden gambling addict who has a talent for messing things up.&nbsp; Together, they hatch a scheme to foil Charlesrsquo; plan to get to heaven and net the grandson badly-needed money.&nbsp; Charles learns of their plans and enlists his friends to help stop them.&nbsp; Will they succeed?&nbsp; The only way to find out is to subscribe.]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>

