<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Supernatural &amp; Magickal podcast novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Heartwarming Stories by Tim Dodge]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/HeartwarmingStoriesByTimDodge?format=xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Purgatory by, Tim Dodge, is a novel about Charles Cunningham, a wealthy real estate developer, who dies unexpectedly and finds himself in Purgatory, the place between heaven and hell. Though depressed about his early death, he befriends two other souls doing time there ]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.timdodgestories.com" description="<![CDATA[Stories of action, humor, horror and outright weirdness from Tim Dodge.  PURGATORY is a novel about Charles Cunningham, a wealthy real estate developer, who dies unexpectedly and finds himself in Purgatory, the place between heaven and hell. Though depressed about his early death, he befriends two other souls doing time there ndash;  the writer Edgar Allan Poe and a fun-loving beach bum named Billy. Upon receiving a letter from God telling him he must learn some unnamed lessons before he can go to heaven, he convinces Poe to join him in the portal back to earth. They hope to make up for their past mistakes, but they arrive on earth in the year 2049, 42 years after Charlesrs&quot; death. Traveling from mid-21st century New York City to Las Vegas, Charles seeks out the daughter he neglected in life, though she is now in her eighties. However, an unfriendly soul from Purgatory follows them to earth. This soul, an employee with whom Charles had an affair and summarily fired, is determined to keep him from winning passage to heaven. She teams up with Charlesrsquo; grandson, a debt-ridden gambling addict who has a talent for messing things up. Together, they hatch a scheme to foil Charlesrsquo; plan to get to heaven and net the grandson badly-needed money. Charles learns of their plans and enlists his friends to help stop them. Will they succeed?  The only way to find out is to subscribe.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[FETIDUS - The Foundation for the Ethical Treatment of the Innocently Damned, Undead and Supernatural]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.fetidus.org/fetidus?format=xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[FETIDUS - The Foundation for the Ethical Treatment of the Innocently Damned, Undead and Supernatural]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.fetidus.org/" description="<![CDATA[FETIDUS is a sci-fi/horror/mystery podcast consisting of an original novel and music score set in the grim and fetid alleyways of a post-apocalyptic Washington, DC, circa 2034. A jaded Washington lobbyist who works for The Foundation for the Ethical Treatment of the Innocently Damned, Undead and Supernatural (FETIDUS) takes up the blackmail case of a mysterious woman, which leads him on a twisted adventure filled with noir-humor, suspense and horror.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Lightning Splice - a free podcast novel by Zellie Blake]]>" xmlUrl="http://zellie.podbean.com/feed//" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Dreams made Flesh - homepage of:Lightning Splice - a free audiobook by Zellie Blake]]>" htmlUrl="http://zellie.podbean.com/" description="<![CDATA[Science fiction/Fantasy audio chapters, bonus content, interviews, and writing tips.  Meet Nighthawk...a master of blades, once blind now his vision is so perfect it hurts. Jack Frost....too cold to touch. And Rose.... well, she's hot?  When sickly Analee welcomes a cure for her gene disorder, a side effect makes her the most powerful weapon in a war between patients like her and the genetics corporation that betrayed them. Head over to the main site at http://www.zellie.info/ for bonus scenes, character sketches, and more.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[House of Gray: A audiobook by Collin Earl]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/TheHouseOfGreyPodcast?format=xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[House of Gray: A podcast novel by Collin Earl]]>" htmlUrl="http://houseofgreybook.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>House of Gray: A audiobook by Collin Earl</h1><p><h1>House of Gray: A audiobook by Collin Earl</h1><div>14-year-old Monson Grey faces the same challenges that any freshman high school kid would. Difficult classes, weird teachers, food fights...girls.  Except Monson Grey is not Monson Grey.  At least, when he looks at himself in the mirror, the scarred face staring back is not someone he recognizes.  Now he finds himself attending an extraordinary school, the recipient of an incredible scholarship, among ridiculously rich classmates, and with no memory of how he got there or what to expect.  As bizarre events start to unfold around him, Monson wonders what secrets lay locked in his hidden past.  Add all this to a mysterious silver stone, an Indiana-Jones-copycat professor, Merlin the wizard, and even Atlantis, and you&#039;ll find yourself in a fantastic tale in which magic does exist and everything is never as it seems.</div></p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Dark Matter - A free podcast novel by Michele Roger]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.micheleroger.com/DarkMatter.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Dark Matter - A free podcast novel by Michele Roger]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.micheleroger.com/DarkMatter.xml" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Dark Matter - A free audiobook by Michele Roger</h1><p><p>In a freak accident that leads to her untimely death Louella, a plain Jane from the suburbs finds herself transformed into one of the walking undead. Michael, the Archangel, offers her a chance to win her life and family back.</p><p>Louella learns that even in the afterlife nothing is free. She must pit her meager supernatural abilities against the mounting forces of darkness. Confronting problematic demons and monsters from Otherworld and beyond who agressively continue to tip the scales in the war of good and and evil in the favor of the Dark One. With the help of Steven, the altruistic vampire and De Vok, a dead librarian from the ancient Alexandria, Luella walks the world between the living and the dead. In her quest to regain her life she learns that even the forces for good have their own agendas and cannot always be trusted.</p><p>This book is a macabre stew of horror, fantasy, science fiction and humor.</p></p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Serving Worlds - a free audiobook by John Mierau]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/serving-worlds/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Serving Worlds - a free podcast novel by John Mierau]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/serving-worlds/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Serving Worlds - a free audiobook by John Mierau</h1><p><p>A cowboy on the run to keep his soul. A vampire running a Nigerian investor scam.  A wolf racing to the mountaintop, before a dragon can catch and kill him. A human protecting one of the aliens he fought in war, from an old army buddy. Meet these and other characters in Serving Worlds, the genre-blending podcast fiction collection from John Mierau.  Weekly episodes are 20 minutes or less but Beware: there be cliffhangers here!</p></p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Pieces - A free audiobook compiled by Nobilis]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/pieces/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Pieces - A free podcast novel compiled by Nobilis]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/pieces/feed/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Pieces - A free audiobook compiled by Nobilis</h1><p>Joan&#039;s world has literally fallen apart.-  She lives in one tiny piece of the shattered universe, bounded on all sides by shimmering veils.&nbsp; When the creator god, calling himself &quot;Cassius&quot;, stumbles into the cathedral where she lives, she is drawn into an adventure of cosmic proportions.The story is told through the cracked lens of seven experienced podcast authors.&nbsp; Nobilis, Christiana Ellis, Chris Lester, Graydancer, Paul S.&nbsp; Jenkins, Philippa Ballantine, Brandon Crose and John Tanzer take turns, chapter by chapter writing and reading episodes of the story.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Inner Demons By Jeri Unselt]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.innerdemonsnovel.com/?feed=rss2" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Inner Demons By Jeri Unselt]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.innerdemonsnovel.com/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Leave Your Fears &#38; Regrets at the door or it&#039;s hell to pay.</p><p>In the summer of 1990, Jeff Holland, his family and members of his band Quicksilver entered the place known as Hawley Manor in the hopes of a comeback and a new life.  A few days later, they were all found dead.</p><p>Because of Jeff’s history of drinking and drugs, police was assumed that he killed everyone inside and then took his own life.</p><p>Eighteen years later, a group of psychic investigators enter to find out what really happened so long ago.</p>]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ - a free audiobook by ]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[<h1> - a free audiobook by </h1><p></p>]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>

