<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Vampire podcast novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Prophecy Awakens - a free podcast novel by Benda Wamsley]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.brendawamsley.net/index.php?option=com_podcast&view=feed&format=raw" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Prophecy Awakens - a free audiobook by Benda Wamsley]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.brendawamsley.net/" description="<![CDATA[A girl, Jane, learns there is much more to her than just being a good daughter when she is propelled into a world where demons are real and they want to destroy her because she may fulfill a prophecy.&nbsp; Now she must learn to survive while not destroying her beliefs.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Lilith's Love]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/LilithsLove" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Lilith's Love - A Podcast Novel by Dan Shaurette]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.liliths-love.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>This is the podcast novel LILITH'S LOVE, written and recorded by Dan Shaurette.&nbsp; It is a modern vampire romance story.</h1><p>Donovan, lonely and getting over the recent death of his parents, asks his long-time friend Christian to move in with him when he relocates back home again to Phoenix from Los Angeles.</p><p>After the Vampire Hunters find Lilith in New Orleans, she and her Wiccan friend Anna decide to go where they think no one would expect to find vampires — The Valley of the Sun, Phoenix, AZ.</p><p>Christian, who is also a Wiccan, meets Anna at a Samhain event (Halloween). The chemistry between them is immediate, and when they introduce their roommates to each other, Don realizes Lilith is not only the woman of his dreams — but that she is the woman in his dreams at night.</p><p>Two romances are sparked, and now that both couples have found each other, they must fight the vengeful plans of Lilith’s Master.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Blood Witness]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/BloodWitness" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Blood Witness - a free podcast novel by Dave Hitt]]>" htmlUrl="http://bloodwitness.com/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Catherine is a 1500 year old vampire. (She’s really 1800 but she lies about her age.) Chris is a high school senior.&nbsp; She is a blood sucking creature of the night.&nbsp; He is a Jehovah’s Witness.&nbsp; Together they discover something that threatens the existence of every vampire, and the only solution is to break the One Law that binds them all.</p>]]>"/>
	</body>
</opml>

