<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>cbc.ca&apos;s Arts and Music</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[L'actualit&eacute; musicale]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: L'actualit&eacute; musicale]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.bandeapart.fm/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: L'actualit&eacute; musicale</h1><p>Ce magazine propose chaque semaine un v&eacute;ritable condens&eacute; de l'actualit&eacute; musicale pour tout francophile : nouveaut&eacute;s, entrevues, d&eacute;couvertes concerts et correspondances.<span class='pd_upd'><strong>Fr&eacute;quence de publication :</strong> Hebdomadaire</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Backbencher]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Backbencher]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/backbencher/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Backbencher</h1><p>In Backbencher, we follow the story of Nellie Gordon, a paramedic from East Nova in Nova Scotia who decides to run for MP on a whim and, much to everyone's surprise, gets elected. We go into caucus meetings, the hallways of Parliament and the House of Commons itself and experience it all from Nellie's perspective each and every episode.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Wednesdays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Bande &agrave; part]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Bande &agrave; part]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.bandeapart.fm" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Bande &agrave; part</h1><p>Bande &agrave; part vous propose chaque semaine une s&eacute;lection musicale &agrave; t&eacute;l&eacute;charger, ponctu&eacute;e par de courts extraits de conversations avec des m&eacute;lomanes ou des artisans.<span class='pd_upd'><strong>Fr&eacute;quence de publication :</strong> Hebdomadaire</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Radio 2: Beethoven Nine in 9]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Radio 2: Beethoven Nine in 9]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.radio2.cbc.ca/podcasts" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Radio 2: Beethoven Nine in 9</h1><p>Nine conversations about Beethoven's nine symphonies. Bramwell Tovey - Music Director of the Vancouver Symphony Orchestra - and CBC Radio 2's Bill Richardson consider these mighty works and talk about what makes them so powerful. Tovey illustrates passages on the piano. CBC Radio 2 will broadcast performances by Tovey and the VSO daily starting March 31 2008. The concerts are available for streaming at Concerts on Demand.<span class='pd_upd'>Complete series available.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Between the Covers]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Between the Covers]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/betweenthecovers" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Between the Covers</h1><p>Between The Covers is a podcast serializing the best in Canadian literature, from comedy to tragedy.  Stories are narrated by some of our finest actors, with new installments each week.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated three times weekly.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Book Club <span class='pd_title_sub'>(Audio)</span>]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: The Book Club <span class='pd_title_sub'>(Audio)</span>]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/canadareads/bookclub/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: The Book Club <span class='pd_title_sub'>(Audio)</span></h1><p>Join the Book Club as we celebrate books every month. Host Hannah Sung checks in with our featured authors and special guests. You can get involved and send in questions for the author of our current book pick.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Fridays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Book Club <span class='pd_title_sub'>(Video)</span>]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: The Book Club <span class='pd_title_sub'>(Video)</span>]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/canadareads/bookclub/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: The Book Club <span class='pd_title_sub'>(Video)</span></h1><p>Join The Book Club as we celebrate a new book every month. We have exclusive videos with our featured authors and Book Club weekly news.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Fridays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Radio 2: Canada Live]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Radio 2: Canada Live]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.radio2.cbc.ca/podcasts" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Radio 2: Canada Live</h1><p>Every night on CBC Radio 2, Canada Live presents the best in live music from concert stages across the country.  And every week the Canada Live podcast brings you highlights from some of those amazing concerts,  from pop to jazz, roots to world,  and everywhere in between.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Fridays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Canada Reads]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Canada Reads]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/books/canadareads/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Canada Reads</h1><p>Canada Reads celebrates five Canadian books for three months online, at public events and on air. It all leads up to a week-long show hosted by Jian Ghomeshi. In this annual title fight, five celebrity panelists defend their favourite work of Canadian fiction. One by one, books are voted off the list, until one panelist triumphs with the book for Canada to read this year.<span class='pd_upd'>Full series available.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Christiane Charette]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Christiane Charette]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.radio-canada.ca/radio/christiane/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Christiane Charette</h1><p>Une &eacute;mission ouverte &agrave; tous les horizons, un rendez-vous avec l'actualit&eacute; culturelle, sociale et politique. Entrevues en profondeur, d&eacute;bats, rubriques, tables rondes, toutes les formules seront bonnes pour s'entretenir avec les invit&eacute;s, qu'ils soient &agrave; Montr&eacute;al, Vancouver, Paris, New York ou ailleurs...<span class='pd_upd'><strong>Fr&eacute;quence de publication :</strong> Quotidienne</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Comedy Factory]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Comedy Factory]]>" htmlUrl="faq.html#FAQ1" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Comedy Factory</h1><p>If a joke's worth telling, it's worth repeating. The Comedy Factory collects our favourite skits, commentaries and funny bits that appeared on CBC Radio over the past week. It's an assembly line of humour, safety-tested and priced to move! <span class='pd_upd'>Updated Thursdays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Best of DNTO]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: The Best of DNTO]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/dnto" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: The Best of DNTO</h1><p>DNTO inspires you to understand your own life. Through personal stories from (mostly) regular people, DNTO uncovers the magic and the humour of everyday life. Our friendly host Sook-Yin Lee always looks at the world in new and surprising ways. And the best part of the show is that each week she invites you to make discoveries along with her. DNTO...because everyone has a story.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Saturdays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[DNTO: Enhanced]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: DNTO: Enhanced]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/dnto" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: DNTO: Enhanced</h1><p>If you have iTunes or an iPod, you can now download and experience the Definitely Not the Opera enhanced podcast, complete with chapters, photos and links! The enhanced podcast format makes it easier for you to navigate through our weekly collection of highlights. It's like an audio slideshow on your iPod!<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Saturdays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Eli Glasner on Film]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Eli Glasner on Film]]>" htmlUrl="http://glasneronfilm.blogspot.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Eli Glasner on Film</h1><p>CBC Radio Film Reviewer Eli Glasner shares his big screen thoughts on the latest and greatest movies appearing at theatre near you.  Some cinema smarts (and snark) to go with your popcorn. <span class='pd_upd'>Updated Fridays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Je l'ai vu &agrave; la radio]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Je l'ai vu &agrave; la radio]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.radio-canada.ca/radio/emissions/emission.asp?numero=1356" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Je l'ai vu &agrave; la radio</h1><p>Des rencontres passionnantes avec ceux et celles qui font l'actualit&eacute; culturelle, des comptes rendus &eacute;clairants et des critiques originales.<span class='pd_upd'><strong>Fr&eacute;quence de publication :</strong> Hebdomadaire</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Know-It-Alls]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: The Know-It-Alls]]>" htmlUrl="faq.html#FAQ1" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: The Know-It-Alls</h1><p>Steve Hammerstone and Tawnie Skypunch answer listeners' questions. From gardening, to relationships, to travel, any question is fair game. They know it all. Well, at least they think they do.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Tuesdays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Laugh of the Day]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Laugh of the Day]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/laughoutloud/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Laugh of the Day</h1><p>CBC Radio's Laugh Out Loud presents a new, quick joke for you every day with the Laugh of the Day podcast!<span class='pd_upd'>Updated daily.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Laugh Out Loud]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Laugh Out Loud]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/laughoutloud/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Laugh Out Loud</h1><p>CBC Radio's Laugh out Loud is Canada's new home for comedy. Every week host Ali Rizvi Badshah features the best and funniest comics in the business. Recorded at festivals and comedy clubs across the country, LOL is the show to hear to stay on top of the Canadian comedy scene. From the famous to the found, LOL will bring you the funny every week.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Saturdays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Libre comme l'air]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Libre comme l'air]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.radio-canada.ca/emissions/libre_comme_l_air" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Libre comme l'air</h1><p>Le grand magazine quotidien de la radio publique refl&egrave;te les tendances sociales et culturelles de notre temps. Dominique Poirier, en compagnie des invit&eacute;s et des chroniqueurs, aborde les grands mouvements reli&eacute;s aux arts et &agrave; la cr&acute;ation. Elle nous propose de d&eacute;couvrir diff&eacute;rents courants dans divers domaines. Choc des id&eacute;es, plongeon dans les &eacute;v&eacute;nements de notre soci&eacute;t&eacute;, d&eacute;couverte de nouvelles personnalit&eacute;s. Un carrefour de rythmes, de voix et d'accents.<!--<span class='pd_upd'><strong>Fr&eacute;quence de publication :</strong> Hebdomadaire</span>--></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Listener's Choice]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Listener's Choice]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/documentaries/thechoice/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Listener's Choice</h1><p>The Podcast programmed by YOU! Your favourite interview, documentary or episode selected by YOU - our listeners.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Fridays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Macadam tribus]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Macadam tribus]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.radio-canada.ca/radio/emissions/emission.asp?numero=62" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Macadam tribus</h1><p>Pour un regard libre et diff&eacute;rent sur l'actualit&eacute;, la vie culturelle et la soci&eacute;t&eacute;. Pour d&eacute;couvrir des r&eacute;alit&eacute;s, des cr&eacute;ations et des musiques qui passent souvent inaper&ccedil;ues.<span class='pd_upd'><strong>Fr&eacute;quence de publication :</strong> Hebdomadaire</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Mendelssohn and Schumann]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Mendelssohn and Schumann]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/radio2/programs/saic/2009/11/13/making_the_most_of_mendelssohn.html" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Mendelssohn and Schumann</h1><p>Six conversations about the music and life of Felix Mendelssohn and Robert and Clara Schumann. Bramwell Tovey - Music Director of the Vancouver Symphony Orchestra - joins CBC Radio 2's Bill Richardson as they talk about the life and music of these three great composers and what makes their music endure. Tovey illustrates passages on the piano.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated twice weekly.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Next Chapter]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: The Next Chapter]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/thenextchapter" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: The Next Chapter</h1><p>Shelagh Rogers travels the country, conversing with authors and readers of all kinds.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Mondays.</span><br /></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Par 4 chemins]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Par 4 chemins]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.radio-canada.ca/radio/emissions/emission.asp?numero=26" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Par 4 chemins</h1><p>Avec un esprit d'ouverture et une curiosit&eacute; toujours en &eacute;veil, Jacques Languirand arpente les chemins de la connaissance qui vont droit &agrave; l'essentiel: le moi, la nature, la soci&eacute;t&eacute; et la transcendance avec des questions fondamentales et incontournables. D'o&ugrave; venons-nous? Qui sommes-nous? O&ugrave; allons-nous? Par ses r&eacute;flexions et un choix musical &eacute;clectique, Jacques Languirand se r&eacute;v&egrave;le &agrave; la fois d&eacute;stabilisant et 'tripatif', &agrave; l'image du monde actuel.<span class='pd_upd'><strong>Fr&eacute;quence de publication :</strong> Hebdomadaire</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Q: The Interviews]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Q: The Interviews]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/q/uncut/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Q: The Interviews</h1><p>Q: The Interviews offers individual interviews-to-go:  memorable conversations from North America's liveliest arts, culture and entertainment magazine.  Discover - or revisit - host Jian Ghomeshi's in-depth interviews with some of the world's most fascinating cultural personalities in music, TV and film, books, theatre, visual arts, media, and more.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Mondays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Q: The Podcast]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Q: The Podcast]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/q" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Q: The Podcast</h1><p>Q is Canada's liveliest arts, culture and entertainment magazine. It's a smart and surprising tour through personalities and cultural issues that matter to Canadians. Hosted by Jian Ghomeshi, Q covers pop culture and high arts alike. Q brings you big names, big ideas, and those paving the way in Canada's cultural community. Q is your cultural intervention!<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Daily.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Q: The Video Podcast]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Q: The Video Podcast]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/q" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Q: The Video Podcast</h1><p>QTV is the televised version of CBC Radio One's Q with Jian Ghomeshi, which also airs on CBC's bold tv.  Featuring full length interviews with celebrities and personalities in the worlds of arts, culture and entertainment.  The video podcast brings you the best interviews for you to download and watch.  Check it out.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated often.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The R3-30]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: The R3-30]]>" htmlUrl="http://radio3.cbc.ca/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: The R3-30</h1><p>Every week, host Craig Norris counts down the very best in new music, according to CBC Radio 3. His producer Pedro Mendes rides shotgun as they chow down on a twisted jungle gym of new music, listener picks, Chartbreakers&trade;, and mixed metaphors. And Love. Always Love. <br><span class='pd_upd'>Updated Saturdays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[CBC Radio 3]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: CBC Radio 3]]>" htmlUrl="http://radio3.cbc.ca/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: CBC Radio 3</h1><p>CBC Radio 3 is a weekly hour of 100% Canadian music from new and emerging artists. It's one of the most popular podcasts in the country, playing the best in new rock, pop, singer-songwriters, hip hop, and electronica.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Fridays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[CBC Radio 3 Ab-Originals]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: CBC Radio 3 Ab-Originals]]>" htmlUrl="http://radio3.cbc.ca/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: CBC Radio 3 Ab-Originals</h1><p>Ab-Originals is a weekly podcast of the hottest Aboriginal music in Canada. Four of the best-known musical hosts in Indian Country will bring you live concerts, urban and hip-hop music, top 10 chart artists, and all the rest of it in their musical podlatch.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated weekly.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[CBC Radio 3 Breakfast Club]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: CBC Radio 3 Breakfast Club]]>" htmlUrl="http://radio3.cbc.ca/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: CBC Radio 3 Breakfast Club</h1><p>Join R3 Host Vish Khanna as he meets with musicians and artists for a frank, informal interview over breakfast. They pick the place, Vish picks their brains. And occasionally at their plates...<span class='pd_upd'>Updated weekly.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[CBC Radio 3 Extended Play]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: CBC Radio 3 Extended Play]]>" htmlUrl="http://radio3.cbc.ca/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: CBC Radio 3 Extended Play</h1><p>CBC Radio 3's Extended Play is a bi-weekly podcast that explores current events happening in the world of Canadian independent music. Hosted by Lisa Christiansen, it is an ongoing conversation between artists and listeners about the issues having an impact on music culture today.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated bi-weekly.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[CBC Radio 3 Sessions]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: CBC Radio 3 Sessions]]>" htmlUrl="http://radio3.cbc.ca/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: CBC Radio 3 Sessions</h1><p>When it comes to breaking new sound, we are the jackhammer on the pavement of commercial music. Every week we feature artists recorded live off-the-floor as they experiment with alternate arrangements and new songs before they're released. Hosted by Tariq Hussain, it's music straight from the heart, with artists at their sweaty best.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Wednesdays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Radio 3 Sunshine Show]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Radio 3 Sunshine Show]]>" htmlUrl="http://radio3.cbc.ca/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Radio 3 Sunshine Show</h1><p>Hosted by legendary CBC personality Richard 'Sunshine Dick' Johnson, 'The Sunshine Show' is radio the way it was meant to be, complete with weather updates, community events, sports and good old-fashioned story-telling. And some musical selections by groups that operate without the auspices of a major imprint.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Mondays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Radio 3 Super Feed]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Radio 3 Super Feed]]>" htmlUrl="http://radio3.cbc.ca/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Radio 3 Super Feed</h1><p>CBC Radio 3 is the part of Canada's public broadcaster that devotes itself entirely to new Canadian music.  With the CBC Radio 3 Super Feed, you can catch every podcast we make and loads of amazing new tunes in just one place.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Daily.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[R3TV]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: R3TV]]>" htmlUrl="http://radio3.cbc.ca/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: R3TV</h1><p>Loyal listeners around the world... Music channels not playing videos muchhese days? Ever wanted to see a face behind the voice? Look no further. CBCRadio 3 presents its first video podcast - a weekly mix of Canadian music,comedy, and tales from the screwed-up studio that brings you the breaking newsounds you love.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Thursdays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[R3: NMC Track of the Day]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: R3: NMC Track of the Day]]>" htmlUrl="http://radio3.cbc.ca/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: R3: NMC Track of the Day</h1><p>Each weekday, one of our hosts at CBC Radio 3 will play a track he or she ispassionate about and tell you why you should give it a listen.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Daily.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[ReVision Quest]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: ReVision Quest]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/revisionquest/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: ReVision Quest</h1><p>ReVision Quest is a convention-breaking radio show, hosted by Shuswap comedian Darrell Dennis, that explodes myths about Aboriginal life, and explores what it means to be First Nations in Canada today through story-telling, interviews and comedy.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Wednesdays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The SAIC / NEXT! Podcast]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: The SAIC / NEXT! Podcast]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/radio2/features/next/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: The SAIC / NEXT! Podcast</h1><p>For 10 weeks, Saturday Afternoon in Concerts will feature performances from the next generation of young classical musicians as part of the NEXT! series. The podcast showcases live performances from concerts halls aross the country.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated from January 18 to March 22, 2009.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Saturday Night Blues]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Saturday Night Blues]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/snb/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Saturday Night Blues</h1><p>Saturday Night Blues has been CBC's flagship program of great blues, swing, boogie, gospel and roots music since 1986. Holger Petersen is at the helm. Subscribe to the podcast to download our exclusive interviews.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Saturdays</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Radio 2: The Signal]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Radio 2: The Signal]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.radio2.cbc.ca/podcasts" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Radio 2: The Signal</h1><p>Every week, the Signal Podcast brings you contemporary music without borders, from 'New Music' to new hybrids. A show for the musically curious.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Thursdays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Sunday Edition]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: The Sunday Edition]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/thesundayedition" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: The Sunday Edition</h1><p>A podcast of the best of this lively program with host Michael Enright who tackles everything from politics to pop culture, in Canada and around the world. <span class='pd_upd'>Updated on Mondays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[This Is That]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: This Is That]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/vinylcafe" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: This Is That</h1><p>This Is That is a current affairs program that doesn't just talk about the issues, it fabricates them. Nothing's off limits--politics, business, culture, justice, science, religion--if it's relevant to Canadians, we'll find out the 'This' and the 'That' of the story. Each week, hosts Pat Kelly and Peter Oldring will introduce you to the voices that give this country character and through these stories provide a new perspective as to what it means to live in Canada.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated weekly.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Vinyl Cafe Stories]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Vinyl Cafe Stories]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/vinylcafe" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Vinyl Cafe Stories</h1><p>The stories and misadventures of Dave, the owner of the 'Vinyl Cafe', the world's smallest record store, where the motto is 'We may not be big, but we're small.'<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Saturdays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Vous &ecirc;tes ici]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Vous &ecirc;tes ici]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.radio-canada.ca/radio/vousEtesIci/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Vous &ecirc;tes ici</h1><p>Vous &ecirc;tes ici, une &eacute;mission de radio con&ccedil;ue pour aller au-del&agrave; des id&eacute;es re&ccedil;ues, pour aborder des points de vue singuliers et pour sortir du 'pr&ecirc;t-&agrave;-penser'. <span class='pd_upd'><strong>Fr&eacute;quence de publication :</strong> Quotidienne</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Vous m'en lirez tant]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Vous m'en lirez tant]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.radio-canada.ca/radio/emissions/emission.asp?numero=1658" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Vous m'en lirez tant</h1><p>Entretiens en profondeur, tables rondes, portraits, comptes rendus, mais aussi billets, chansons et textes lus par des auteurs ou des com&eacute;diens.<span class='pd_upd'><strong>Fr&eacute;quence de publication :</strong> Hebdomadaire</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[WireTap]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: WireTap]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/wiretap" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: WireTap</h1><p>Enter the world of Jonathan Goldstein. You wouldn't want to live there, but it's a hell of a place to visit.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated Saturdays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Word of Mouth]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Word of Mouth]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/news/viewpoint/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Word of Mouth</h1><p>Join CBC Radio producer and language fanatic Colleen Ross for Word of Mouth, her monthly podcast about the ever-evolving English language. She pokes her nose into everything from trends in grammar and vocabulary to how multiculturalism, technology, politics and Hollywood affect the way we talk.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated monthly.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Word of the Week]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Word of the Week]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/cestlavie" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Word of the Week</h1><p>C'est la vie's Word of the Week is a window into the life of French-speaking Canadians -- one word at a time.<span class='pd_upd'>Updated weekly.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Writers &amp; Company]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: Writers &amp; Company]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/writersandcompany" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: Writers &amp; Company</h1><p>Host Eleanor Wachtel explores the lives, thoughts and works of remarkable writers from around the world. <span class='pd_upd'>Updated Sundays.</span></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[<span class='pd_title_sub'>Radio 2:</span> Zukerman on Brahms]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[CBC's: <span class='pd_title_sub'>Radio 2:</span> Zukerman on Brahms]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.cbc.ca/radio2/features/brahms/index.html" description="<![CDATA[<h1>CBC's: <span class='pd_title_sub'>Radio 2:</span> Zukerman on Brahms</h1><p>Four conversations about Brahms' Symphonies, with Pinchas Zukerman - Music Director of the NAC Orchestra - and CBC Radio 2 host Bill Richardson. Some musical illustrations are played by violinist Pinchas Zukerman himself, and also by pianist Les Dala. Concert performances of the symphonies by Zukerman and NACO are also available for streaming at CBC Radio 2's Concerts on Demand.<span class='pd_upd'>Complete series available.</span></p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
