<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff&apos;s Works &amp; Podnovels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" url="" type="link" text="<![CDATA[]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Pacific Coast Hellway]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/pacificcoasthellway?format=xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Pacific Coast Hellway: Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff&apos;s Personal podcast]]>" htmlUrl="http://pacificcoasthellway.com/" description="<![CDATA[PCH - &quot;The world&apos;s most offensively enlightened podcast&quot; -Playboy Magazine]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Shadow Falls]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podshow.com/feeds/shadowfalls.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Shadow Falls: Seasons 1, 2, &amp; maybe someday 3?]]>" htmlUrl="http://shadowfalls.mevio.com/" description="<![CDATA[For every light that shines... a SHADOW FALLS. Podcasting's first professionally-produced original drama series, SHADOW FALLS tells the eerie tale of a remote Northeastern town that holds secrets some will kill to protect and others will die to expose. Settled 300 years ago by the survivors of a mysterious tradgedy, the people of Shadow Falls have become pawns being used by two supernatural forces seeking to win a war older than time itself, a war which many believe could trigger the Battle of Armageddon, and wipe out humanity as we know it.Those with alliances believe the time has come once again for the cycle to begin anew as two young women have vanished just as a pair of very mysterious strangers have come into town. This time, they believe this war will finally be decided once and for all and all their toil and sacrifices will be rewarded. What they don't know is that they're wrong.Dead wrong.Spun from the wicked mind of author and screenwriter Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff, SHADOW FALLS is a fully-immersive and addictive mystery that will leave you gasping for breath and begging for mercy.Just don't expect to find mercy here.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Shadow Falls: Season One]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/shadow-falls-season-one/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Shadow Falls: Season One - A free audiobook by Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/shadow-falls-season-one/" description="<![CDATA[A remote Northeastern town holds secrets some will kill to protect and others will die to expose. Settled 300 years ago by the survivors of a mysterious tragedy, the people of Shadow Falls have become pawns being used by two supernatural forces seeking to win a war older than time itself, a war which many believe could trigger the Battle of Armageddon, and wipe out humanity as we know it.Those with alliances believe the time has come once again for the cycle to begin anew as two young women have vanished just as a pair of very mysterious strangers have come into town. This time, they believe this war will finally be decided once and for all and all their toil and sacrifices will be rewarded. What they don't know is that they're wrong.Dead wrong.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Shadow Falls: Season Two: Badlands]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/shadow-falls-badlands/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Shadow Falls: Season Two: Badlands - A free audiobook by Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/shadow-falls-badlands/" description="<![CDATA[After a condemned ex-soldier cheats the gallows and wakes to find everyone in a small Texas town dead and his jail cell door wide open, he begins a cross-country journey to follow his nightmarish visions of mankind's end. But as he searches for a way to stop the coming apocalypse from happening, he soon discovers that what lays behind destiny's door is a darkness beyond his control.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Number One with a Bullet]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/number-one-with-a-bullet/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Number One with a Bullet - A free audiobook by Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/number-one-with-a-bullet/" description="<![CDATA[When the top ten hitmen face off in a last-man standing contest being bet on by some of the world's richest men, the only rule is to stay alive.Assassins are ruthless and clever killers who get paid a lot of money to make problems go away. And pretty soon one of them is going to be a hundred million dollars richer if they can eliminate all the competition, before the competition eliminates them. But for retired hitman Johnny Dane, considered at one point to be the best hired killer in the world, getting out of the life doesn't necessarily mean getting out of the game.Welcome to the world of high-priced hitmen and the game they've been thrust into. The last man (or woman) standing not only gets the prize but will be the only top notch assassin left available for hire. One of the top ten best killers has been notoriously absent from the contest, Johnny Dane. Having left the life, he's disappeared to an oceanfront hideaway and has vowed never to return, but when the game finds him and threatens the only woman he's ever loved, Dane realizes the only way out, is to get back in.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Diary of a Madman]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/diary-of-a-madman/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Diary of a Madman - A free audiobook by Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/diary-of-a-madman/" description="<![CDATA[A man obsessed with serial killers becomes a murderer in search of justice.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Doomsday Club]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-doomsday-club/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Doomsday Club - A free audiobook by Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-doomsday-club/" description="<![CDATA[Scott Lorlon is in a wicked funk. He can't eat, can't sleep, won't go to his classes and has made the awful mistake of cutting his own hair. His fall through the fragile floor of despair comes after his longtime girlfriend has kicked him to the curb without so much as a warning. This darkly comic thriller takes root as Scott's roommate, Hale, and two other buddies try to cheer him up. But for them, it's a loaded bong where all their trouble begins. Busted by a vicious resident assistant, heated words are exchanged and when the R.A. attacks them, Scott unintentionally kills him. The boys panic and hatch a crazy scheme to get rid of the body -- a plan ending with a deadly fireball that only succeeds in getting them deeper over their heads in crisis.]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - A free audiobook by Mark Yoshimoto Nemcoff]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
