<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Mark Jeffrey&apos;s Works &amp; Podnovels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Mark Jeffrey&apos;s: Max Quick Series]]>" url="http://www.maxquickseris.com/" type="link" text="<![CDATA[Mark Jeffrey&apos;s Books &amp; Podnovels of his &quot;Max Quick Series&quot;]]>" description="<![CDATA[Time Travel, Magic, Gowing up, aliens, stories with in stories.  Mark Jeffrey&apos;s &quot;Max Quick Series&quot; has it all &amp; looses nothing.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Pocket and the Pendant]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-pocket-and-the-pendant/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Max Quick, Book 1, The Pocket and the Pendant - A free audiobook by Mark Jeffrey]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-pocket-and-the-pendant/" description="<![CDATA[<h3>Max Quick, Book 1, The Pocket and the Pendant</h3><p>When time mysteriously stops, young Max Quick must travel across America to find the source of this 'temporal disaster'... Along the way, he and his companions encounter ancient mysteries, quantum Books, and clues to the riddle of stopped Time. But the more Max learns, the more it seems that his own true identity is not what he once believed...</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Two Travelers]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-two-travelers/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Max Quick, Book 2, The Two Travelers - A free audiobook by Mark Jeffrey]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-two-travelers/" description="<![CDATA[<h3>Max Quick, Book 2, The Two Travelers</h3><p>Five quiet years have passed in Starland, California since the the time of the Pocket. But when a crazed old man shows up with a warning, Max, Casey, Ian and Sasha suddenly find themselves on the run. Max and Ian go through an Arch back to 1912, where a mysterious Machine is under construction that seems connected to Max’s unremembered secret. Meanwhile, Casey and Sasha follow the old man to the strange town of Arturo Gyp.</p><p>But there is more afoot than meets the eye: the enemies of Mr. E - the nefarious Archons - are abroad. And when Max is at last eye-to-eye with his secret, he realizes nothing will ever be the same again...</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Bane of the Bondsman]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-bane-of-the-bondsman/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Max Quick, Book 3, The Bane of the Bondsman - A free audiobook by Mark Jeffrey]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-bane-of-the-bondsman/" description="<![CDATA[<h3>Max Quick, Book 3, The Bane of the Bondsman</h3>]]>"/>
	</body>
</opml>
