<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Nathan Lowell&apos;s podcast novels on Podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Quarter Share]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/quarter-share/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Quarter Share - a free audiobook by Nathan Lowell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/quarter-share/" description="<![CDATA[A Trader&apos;s Tale from the Golden Age of the Solar Clipper : Book 1<p>When Ishmael Wang is orphaned by a flitter crash, he must make some hard decisions about how to survive in a Company-owned universe. With limited time and fewer options, he lands a job as the newest hand on the Solar Clipper Lois McKendrick and learns there&apos;s more to life than making coffee. Join Ish, Pip, Big Bad Bev, and the rest of the Lois McKendrick&apos;s crew as they sail the galaxy in search of profitable trade.&nbsp; For more information on the book and the Golden Age, see <a href='http://www.durandus.com/golden'>http://www.durandus.com/golden</a>.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Half Share]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/half-share/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Half Share - a free audiobook by Nathan Lowell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/half-share/" description="<![CDATA[A Trader&apos;s Tale from the Golden Age of the Solar Clipper : Book 2<p>After Ishmael Wang is promoted to the environmental section, he&apos;s caught in a swirl of mystery, doubt, belief, lust and a really nice fitting pair of jeans. He has to come to grips with what it means to be a spacer while he&apos;s still trying to figure out what it means to be a man. Join Ishmael, Brillo, Pip, and the rest of the crew of the Lois McKendrick as they help the newest member of the crew adjust to life in the Deep Dark. Half Share is the sequel to Quarter Share, also available at Podiobooks.com.  Note: Some scenes in Half Share involve adult themes, nudity, sex and references to religions not based on Judeo-Christian traditions. Read at your own risk.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Full Share]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/full-share/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Full Share - a free audiobook by Nathan Lowell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/full-share/" description="<![CDATA[A Trader&apos;s Tale from the Golden Age of the Solar Clipper : Book 3<p>The Lois McKendrick runs headlong into trouble when a routine in-system transit goes bad. Ishmael and the rest of the crew must scramble to figure out what went wrong and how to fix it in order to keep the ship alive. Learn more about the officers and crew of the Lois McKendrick as they struggle to keep their ship and discover how Ishmael finds out how wrong he&apos;s been about what it means to be a spacer in this latest Trader&apos;s Tale.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Double Share]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/double-share/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Double Share - a free audiobook by Nathan Lowell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/double-share/" description="<![CDATA[A Trader&apos;s Tale from the Golden Age of the Solar Clipper : Book 4<p>When he graduates from the Academy at Port Newmar, Ishmael Horatio Wang reports for duty in his first assignment as an officer. When he gets to his new ship, he finds things are not exactly the way he&apos;d learned in school. The coffee tastes like used engine oil, the ship has no heart, and the nearest decent tailor is two quadrants away. What&apos;s a new Third Mate to do? Will he be able to trust Billy?</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Captain&apos;s Share]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/captains-share/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Captain&apos;s Share - a free audiobook by Nathan Lowell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/captains-share/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>A Trader's Tale from the Golden Age of the Solar Clipper : Book 5</h1><p>A shuffling of cabins puts Ishmael Horatio Wang in command of the worst ship in the fleet. He learns that being Captain doesn't make you infallible and that life in the Captain's Cabin is filled with new kinds of challenge as he tries to keep the ship moving, the crew out of trouble, and turn a profit to earn his Captain's Share. In a ship where the officers outnumber the crew, how can he manage to keep everybody happy? Welcome to the SC Agamemnon.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Ravenwood]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/ravenwood/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Ravenwood - a free audiobook by Nathan Lowell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/ravenwood/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>A Tanyth Fairport Adventure.</h1><p>After twenty winters on the road, Tanyth makes one last pilgrimage in her quest to learn all she can about the herbs and medicinal plants of Korlay before settling down to write her magnum opus. Her journey is interrupted when she stops to help a small village and learns that much of what she knows of the world may not be quite as it seems.</p><p><i>In this work, Nathan Lowell blends wiccan tradition and shamanistic lore into a fantasy quest and creates a world for a new - if unlikely - heroine to explore. She learns that the familiar sometimes hides the fantastical and that, even when you think you’ve made your decisions, life doesn’t always agree.</i></p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[South Coast]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/south-coast/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[South Coast - a free audiobook by Nathan Lowell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/south-coast/" description="<![CDATA[A Shaman&apos;s Tale from the Golden Age of the Solar Clipper : Volume 1<p>Otto is Richard Krugg&apos;s only son and heir to the Shaman&apos;s gift. The only problem is Otto doesn&apos;t want it. He wants to be a fisherman. When company policies force unwelcome changes onto his life and threaten even the security of the village, Otto discovers that being a shaman isn&apos;t optional.&nbsp; Jimmy Pirano is caught between the devil and the deep green sea when new production quotas are handed down from corporate headquarters. Locked into a century of existing practice, Jimmy is forced to find new ways to fish and new places to do it in or face the very real possibility that Pirano Fisheries will lose the St. Cloud franchise.&nbsp; Join Otto, Richard, and Rachel Krugg as they struggle with what it means to be the son of a shaman. Cast off with Jimmy, Tony, and Casey as they navigate the shoals and shallows of corporate fishery along the South Coast.</p>]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free audiobook by Nathan Lowell]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
