<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			Phil Rossi&appos;s podcast novels &ndash; prensented by: podiobooks.com
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Crescent]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/crescent/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Crescent - A free audiobook by Phil Rossi]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/crescent/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Crescent by Phil Rossi</h1><p>Crescent is the last stop at the intergalactic crossroads of gritty sci-fi and pucker-inducing horror. --Scott Sigler, New York Times bestselling author of ContagiousCrescent is the ultimate sci-fi / horror mashup. It's a wicked blend of the claustrophobia seen in Ridley Scott's Alien, and the viral demonology of Carpenter's Prince Of Darkness with the hard-drinkin' bad attitude of Battlestar Galactica added for good measure. The future has never been so frightening. Phil Rossi brings it....</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Eden]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/eden/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Eden - A free audiobook by Phil Rossi]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/eden/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Eden by Phil Rossi</h1><p><a href='http://parsecawards.com/node/861'><img src='http://farm4.static.flickr.com/3574/3773548318_0f024bb111_o.jpg' align='right' hspace='5' border='0' /></a>The tree is beautiful and they call her Eden.  Her branches reach for the stars.  She is like all other trees on planet Earth save for her enormous size. Still, she has leaves and she has bark. She turns sunlight into life. But this tree does not sprout from the dirt. Eden fills the sky, high in orbit above the blue expanse of Uranus....</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Harvey]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/harvey/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Harvey - A free audiobook by Phil Rossi]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/harvey/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Harvey by Phil Rossi</h1><p><a href='http://www.podiobooks.com/blog/2010/01/05/2009-founders-choice-awards/'><img src='http://farm5.static.flickr.com/4026/4249613583_1c731dc0dd_o.gif' align='right' hspace='10' vspace='10' /></a>Television singing sensation Calvin Hubbard has been caught with his hand in cookie jar. An illicit affair with a contest judge costs him not only the competition crown, but his musical credibility as well.  Fleeing the media fallout, Calvin exiles himself to the backwoods town of Harvey,...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Notes from the Vault]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/notes-from-the-vault/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Notes from the Vault - A free audiobook by Phil Rossi]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/notes-from-the-vault/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Notes from the Vault by Phil Rossi</h1><p>A blizzard cripples an isolated stretch of US Highway where freezing to death would be a mercy. An antique broker holds the internet in the palm of his hand and learns what really brought the system down.  In the forests of upstate Connecticut, a pair of college students visit the site of legendary hauntings.Welcome to the Vault.Phil Rossi, author and twisted mind behind Crescent, brings you a collection of stories that will take you on a terror-fueled ride from the cold abyss of...</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
