<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>&apos;s podcast novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Scott Sigler Audiobooks]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/scottsigler?format=xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Scott Sigler Audiobooks]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.scottsigler.com/feeds/podcasts.xml/podcasts/" description="<![CDATA[This is where Sigler dishes out the good stuff, the pure stuff, the stuff not cut with other stuff that is neither good nor pure.&nbsp; If you like your fiction intense and original, you're in the right place.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Crypt Book 01: The Crew - A free podcast novel by Scott Sigler]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-crypt-01/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Crypt Book 01: The Crew - A free audiobook by Scott Sigler]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-crypt-01/" description="<![CDATA[A far-future military/scifi endeavor from New York Times best-selling author Scott Sigler.&nbsp; It is the best-kept and worst-kept secret in the Planetary Union navy.&nbsp; The PUV James Keeling, a warship that does things that no other ship can do.&nbsp; It is a weapon, and a liability.&nbsp; The rumor is that eighty percent of the people assigned to the Keeling die before their two-year stint is up.&nbsp; That rumor is the reason for the ship&apos;s nickname -- The Crypt, a vessel full of the dead.&nbsp; Those with a promising career, those with connections, those that can can avoid service on the Keeling do just that.&nbsp; But still, the ship must fight, and for that, it needs a crew.&nbsp; The navy assigns the worst of the worst: cowards, thieves, murderers, rapists or those with nowhere else to go, no way to opt out.&nbsp; Your choice is simple: be executed for your crimes, or serve two years on the keeling.&nbsp; If you make it out alive, your record is wiped clean and you get a fresh start.&nbsp; For this crew of just over 100 souls, it will be the longest two years they have ever faced.&nbsp; What is this ship?&nbsp; Where did it come from?&nbsp; And why, oh, why, won&apos;t everyone stop screaming ...]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Nocturnal]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/nocturnal/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Nocturnal - A free audiobook by Scott Sigler]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/nocturnal/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Nocturnal - A free audiobook</h1><p>Something lives deep beneath the streets of San Francisco.&nbsp; Something that has been there for centuries, something which comes out at night to feed on the dregs of society.&nbsp; A sub-culture with its own myths and its own legends.&nbsp; Stories of a leader named The King, who will lead them out of bondage, and their own demon, a hunting shadow known only as Savior.&nbsp; But the legends of Savior's brutality have faded, the fear used only within fables told to the young ones about their hunter.&nbsp; When The King finally appears,just as foretold, the Nocturnals know their time has come -- the time to emerge from under the streets and hunt humanity in the open.</p>]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by .  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[BloodCast, Season 1 - A free podcast novel by Scott Sigler]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/bloodcast-1/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[BloodCast, Season 1 - A free audiobook by Scott Sigler]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/bloodcast-1/" description="<![CDATA[A collection of ten horror-tinged short stories from bestselling author Scott Sigler.&nbsp; Season 1 features the 2008 Parsec winner &quot;Red Man&quot; and 2008 Parsec finalists &quot;Snipe Hunt&quot; and &quot;Hero.&quot; It also includes &quot;Sacred Cow,&quot; which was made into a film for Stranger Things.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[BloodCast, Season 2 - A free podcast novel by Scott Sigler]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/bloodcast-2/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[BloodCast, Season 2 - A free audiobook by Scott Sigler]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/bloodcast-2/" description="<![CDATA[Season Two presents seven more bloody episodes from New York Times best-selling author Scott Sigler.&nbsp; It features the 2009 Parsec Award-winning novella &quot;Eusocial Networking,&quot; and the 2008 Parsec Award finalists &quot;Kissyman &amp; Screaming Jesse Dupre&quot; and &quot;Passenger.&quot; Season Two also includes Scott&apos;s unique satire of the Peanuts characters, and three bonus podcasts from Perry Dawsey, the main character in Scott&apos;s novels INFECTED and CONTAGIOUS. ]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by .  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Infected - A free podcast novel by Scott Sigler]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/infected/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Infected - A free audiobook by Scott Sigler]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/infected/" description="<![CDATA[Across America a mysterious disease is turning ordinary people into raving, paranoid murderers who inflict brutal horrors on strangers, themselves, and even their own families.&nbsp; Working under the government&apos;s shroud of secrecy, CIA operative Dew Phillips crisscrosses the country trying in vain to capture a live victim.&nbsp; With only decomposing corpses for clues, CDC epidemiologist Margaret Montoya races to analyze the science behind this deadly contagion.&nbsp; She discovers that these killers all have one thing in common - they&apos;ve been contaminated by a bioengineered parasite, shaped by a complexity far beyond the limits of known science.&nbsp; Meanwhile Perry Dawsey - a hulking former football star now resigned to life as a cubicle-bound desk jockey - awakens one morning to find several mysterious welts growing on his body.&nbsp; Soon Perry finds himself acting and thinking strangely, hearing voices . . . he is infected.&nbsp; The fate of the human race may well depend on the bloody war Perry must wage with his own body, because the parasites want something from him, something that goes beyond mere murder.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Contagious - A free podcast novel by Scott Sigler]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/contagious/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Contagious - A free audiobook by Scott Sigler]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/contagious/" description="<![CDATA[From the acclaimed author of Infected comes an epic and exhilarating story of humanity&apos;s secret battle against a horrific enemy.&nbsp; Across America, a mysterious pathogen transforms ordinary people into raging killers, psychopaths driven by a terrifying, alien agenda.&nbsp; The human race fights back, yet after every battle the disease responds, adapts, using sophisticated strategies and brilliant ruses to fool its pursuers.&nbsp; The only possible explanation: the epidemic is driven not by evolution but by some malevolent intelligence.&nbsp; Standing against this unimaginable threat is a small group, assembled under the strictest secrecy.&nbsp; Their best weapon is hulking former football star Perry Dawsey, left psychologically shattered by his own struggles with this terrible enemy, who possesses an unexplainable ability to locate the disease&apos;s hosts.&nbsp; Violent and unpredictable, Perry is both the nation&apos;s best hope and a terrifying liability.&nbsp; Hardened CIA veteran Dew Phillips must somehow forge a connection with him if they&apos;re going to stand a chance against this maddeningly adaptable opponent.&nbsp; Alongside them is Margaret Montoya, a brilliant epidemiologist who fights for a cure even as she reels under the weight of endless horrors.&nbsp; These three and their team have kept humanity in the game, but that&apos;s not good enough anymore, not when the disease turns contagious, triggering a fast countdown to Armageddon.&nbsp; Meanwhile, other enemies join the battle, and a new threat - one that comes from a most unexpected source - may ultimately prove the most dangerous of all.&nbsp; Catapulting the reader into a world where humanity&apos;s life span is measured in hours and the president&apos;s finger hovers over the nuclear button, rising star Scott Sigler takes us on a breathtaking, hyper-adrenalized ride filled with terror and jaw-dropping action.&nbsp; Contagious is a truly grand work of suspense, science, and horror from a new master.]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by .  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Earthcore - A free podcast novel by Scott Sigler]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/earthcore/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Earthcore - A free audiobook by Scott Sigler]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/earthcore/" description="<![CDATA[Deep below a desolate Utah mountain lays the largest platinum deposit ever discovered.&nbsp; A billion-dollar find, it waits for any company that can drill a world&apos;s record, three-mile-deep mine shaft.&nbsp; EarthCore is the company with the technology, the resources and the guts to go after the mother lode.&nbsp; Young executive Connell Kirkland is the company&apos;s driving force, pushing himself and those around him to uncover the massive treasure.&nbsp; But Kirkland and EarthCore are not the first to find this treasure.&nbsp; The mountain&apos;s history reveals two centuries of disappearances, murder, and insanity.&nbsp; The discovery of ancient platinum knives, razor-sharp despite lying untouched for 1,000 years, reveals evidence of an ancient culture.&nbsp; If the artifacts are genuine, they show a pre-historic empire that once spanned from the Southern tip of South America all the way up through the American Southwest.&nbsp; Wealth and fame lie under that Utah mountain, but at three miles below the surface, where the rocks are so hot they burn bare skin, something has been waiting for centuries.&nbsp; Waiting ... and guarding.&nbsp; Kirkland and EarthCore are about to find out, first-hand, why this treasure has never been unearthed.]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by .  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Rookie: Remastered MATURE AUDIENCES Edition - A free podcast novel by Scott Sigler]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-rookie/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Rookie: Remastered MATURE AUDIENCES Edition - A free audiobook by Scott Sigler]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-rookie/" description="<![CDATA[Scott Sigler&apos;s thrilling novel which combines intense football action, space opera, and the criminal underworld has now been professionally remastered.&nbsp; This engaging story is most often described as a hybrid of Star Wars, The Godfather, and Any Given Sunday.&nbsp; The Rookie is set amongst a lethal pro football league 700 years in the future.&nbsp; Aliens play positions based on physiology, creating receivers that jump 25 feet into the air, linemen that bench-press 1,200 pounds, and linebackers that literally want to eat you.&nbsp; Organized crime runs every franchise, games are fixed, and rival players are assassinated.&nbsp; Follow the story of Quentin Barnes, a 19 year-old quarterback prodigy that has been raised all his life to loathe those aliens.&nbsp; He was taught rhymes in school about how to kill them.&nbsp; Quentin must deal with his racism and learn to lead, or he will wind up just another casualty on the football field.]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
