<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			The Works of: .&nbsp; 
			Podcasts, fiction, novels, &amp; audio dramas.&nbsp; 
			Brought to you by: .
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Loner In Space]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/loner-in-space/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Loner In Space - A free audiobook by Steve Simons]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/loner-in-space/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Loner In Space by Steve Simons</h1><p>This book was written originally for children,  but the adults in Steve's test audience also enjoyed it.   The book tells the story of a boy who is a bit of a loner at school and in life.  His home life is also a bit in tatters since his mum died.  The book takes up the story when he discovers something in the woods, near where he lives,  little does he know where his discovery will take him, but the title of the book gives you an idea, what will he find there?  Will he still be...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Regenis 4 Chronicles (Book 1)]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/regenis-4-chronicles/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Regenis 4 Chronicles (Book 1) - A free audiobook by Steve Simons]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/regenis-4-chronicles/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Regenis 4 Chronicles (Book 1) by Steve Simons</h1><p>This book is the story of two young men, well they are not exactly boys being 16 and 18.  They make a discovery, that seems to indicate a plot to do serious harm, but harm to whom and by who? There is not a lot to go on.  Just as they are deep into their research their father discovers what they are up to and surprisingly volunteers his services to help out with their investigation, but then he disappears.  Where did he go, when he left home and is he still alive?  Can a 16 and 18 year old...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Regenis 4 Chronicles Book 2 - The Invisible Foe]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/regenis-4-chronicles-2/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Regenis 4 Chronicles Book 2 - The Invisible Foe - A free audiobook by Steve Simons]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/regenis-4-chronicles-2/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Regenis 4 Chronicles Book 2 - The Invisible Foe by Steve Simons</h1><p>Space craft start disappearing, but the authorities can't figure out why, who or what is behind this. There is much fear in the Glaceons family, especially as the eldest son is now a qualified interstellar pilot and regularly traveling through space. Ed and Paul are once again thrown into the thick of things, what is it with these two and disappearances, last time it was their dad. Can they solve the mystery and even more important can they save the lives of those who disappeared along with...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Gateway]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-gateway/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Gateway - A free audiobook by Steve Simons]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-gateway/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Gateway by Steve Simons</h1><p>This book was written for children, it was originally serialised on the podcast show KidsCastSciFi. It follows the adventures of two boys who accidentally discover some form of gateway, that takes them to other worlds or parallel universes. Enjoy.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Sphere Of Time]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-sphere-of-time/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Sphere Of Time - A free audiobook by Steve Simons]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-sphere-of-time/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Sphere Of Time by Steve Simons</h1><p>This is a science fiction story that is suitable for children and adults alike. It tells the story of John Latham a scientist and Engineer, who thinks he has found a way to travel through time, space or even another dimension. However, he is not sure unless he can test out his ideas. John is lucky enough to come across a wealthy man who puts up the money to try out John's idea. But the crux of this book is, if he succeeds in getting there, wherever there actually is, what will he find when he...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Sphere Of Travel (TSOT2)]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-sphere-of-travel/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Sphere Of Travel (TSOT2) - A free audiobook by Steve Simons]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-sphere-of-travel/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Sphere Of Travel (TSOT2) by Steve Simons</h1><p>This story is rated 12 as there is a romantic theme and also death, but nothing explicit, it's still a clean story.We find the team of David and John set to  adventure out again. This time in an improved sphere and both of them are going to travel together.  A new member is introduced to the team, Debbie Gill.  Debbie takes over David's role, predicting the location of the black holes.The trip does not go according to plan, but oh no,don't look to me to spill the beans as to what...</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>

