<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>The Works of Teel McClanahan III</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Modern Evil Podcast]]>" xmlUrl="http://modernevil.com/Podcast/?feed=podcast" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Modern Evil Podcast from Modern Evil Press - works by Teel McClanahan III]]>" htmlUrl="http://modernevil.com/Podcast/" description="<![CDATA[Podcast containing all the audio fiction by Teel McClanahan III from Modern Evil Press.]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/----/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/----/" text="<![CDATA[ - A free audiobook by Teel McClanahan III]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Untrue Tales... Book One]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/UTFBFRoaAP1/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Untrue Tales... Book One - A free audiobook by Teel McClanahan III]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/UTFBFRoaAP1/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Untrue Tales... Book One by Teel McClanahan III</h1><p>FULL TITLE: Untrue Tales From Beyond Fiction - Recollections of an Alternate Past, Book One: An Introduction to Dodgeball -or- Conception and Induction -or- How To Begin An Apocalypse -- Contains mature content not suitable for all readers. Book One is the introduction to this series of books which take place in a world where magic and psychic-like powers exist but are overlooked by most people, and centers on a teenage boy of remarkable magical and mental powers as he is introduced to a...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Untrue Tales... Book Two]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/UTFBFRoaAP2/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Untrue Tales... Book Two - A free audiobook by Teel McClanahan III]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/UTFBFRoaAP2/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Untrue Tales... Book Two by Teel McClanahan III</h1><p>FULL TITLE: Untrue Tales From Beyond Fiction - Recollections of an Alternate Past, Book Two:  The Twofold Invasion -or- Penetration and Destruction -or- How To Make Love With Twins -- Contains mature content not suitable for all readers. Book Two continues the boy&apos;s story from a few months after where Book One leaves off, primarily following his quest to save the life of his unborn child as he finds himself further and further from the life he knew before.  This is the second book of the...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Untrue Tales... Book Three]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/UTFBFRoaAP3/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Untrue Tales... Book Three - A free audiobook by Teel McClanahan III]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/UTFBFRoaAP3/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Untrue Tales... Book Three by Teel McClanahan III</h1><p>FULL TITLE: Untrue Tales From Beyond Fiction - Recollections of an Alternate Past, Book Three: Escape From Exile -or- Confusion and Contraction -or- How To Get Out Of Hell. -- Contains mature content not suitable for all readers. Book Three picks up from the same instant that Book Two left off: in Hell. It is primarily concerned with the boy&apos;s attempts to free his companions from eternal damnation, but has a few twists and turns that will leave you wondering what really happened. This is the...</p>]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/----/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/----/" text="<![CDATA[ - A free audiobook by Teel McClanahan III]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Lost and Not Found]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/lost-and-not-found/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Lost and Not Found - A free audiobook by Teel McClanahan III]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/lost-and-not-found/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Lost and Not Found by Teel McClanahan III</h1><p>Lost and Not Found details one man&apos;s journey all the way from being laid off from his mundane corporate job to becoming the author he truly dreams to be by following his attempt to write his first novel within the challenging timeframe of only four weeks. As his story unfolds we get to read what he is writing and can see the relationship between the author and his work unfold until his life literally unfolds around him.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Forget What You Can't Remember]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/forget-what-you-cant-remember/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Forget What You Can't Remember - A free audiobook by Teel McClanahan III]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/forget-what-you-cant-remember/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Forget What You Can't Remember by Teel McClanahan III</h1><p>Featuring a zombie outbreak and a strange sort of doomsday, but really focusing on how coming through those experiences into utopia and freedom effects different people, Forget What You Can&apos;t Remember is an exploration of the human mind under pressure. It&apos;s about relationships, memory, opportunity, and dealing with their loss - and other kinds of loss.  Forget What You Can't Remember is a spin-off novel in the same universe as Lost and Not Found (also available on Podiobooks.com) which...</p>]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/----/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/----/" text="<![CDATA[ - A free audiobook by Teel McClanahan III]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Dragons' Truth]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/dragons-truth/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Dragons' Truth - A free audiobook by Teel McClanahan III]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/dragons-truth/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Dragons' Truth by Teel McClanahan III</h1><p>When two young boys decide to skip school and seek adventure one day, they end up finding much more than they ever bargained for. More than the dragon and the mountain of riches they see at first, one of the boys finds the entire course of his life changed. That boy, Larry, finds himself at the center of an adventure bigger than anything he'd ever dreamed of. And when Larry&apos;s continuing adventure begins to effect his schoolwork, and then his teachers and his entire school, Larry&apos;s not sure...</p>]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/----/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/----/" text="<![CDATA[ - A free audiobook by Teel McClanahan III]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Cheating, Death]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/cheating-death/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Cheating, Death - A free audiobook by Teel McClanahan III]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/cheating-death/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Cheating, Death by Teel McClanahan III</h1><p>When the walking dead fill the streets, who can cheat death? Who can survive?  Featuring a zombie outbreak that devastates Denver, an indecisive adulterer, and a series of violent, disturbing, and perhaps even heart-rending events of the sort you'd expect when the dead rise up to eat the living, Cheating, Death is a roller-coaster ride through a horror show both of death and of the heart.  Cheating, Death is the fourth glimpse of the storybook universe first seen in Lost and Not Found,...</p>]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/----/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/----/" text="<![CDATA[ - A free audiobook by Teel McClanahan III]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
