<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Timothy Callahan&apos;s Works &amp; Podnovels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Timothy P. Callahan&apos;s Homepage]]>" url="http://www.timothypcallahan.com/" type="link" text="<![CDATA[]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>
		<!-- Starts linsting The Gyssyc trilogy -->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Arwen, Season 1: Regal]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-arwen/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Arwen, Season 1: Regal - A free audiobook by Timothy Callahan]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-arwen/" description="<![CDATA[When a comet the size of a small moon threatens the remote world of Regal the Earth Alliance assigns the most decorated ship in the fleet, the Arwen, to destroy it.   Its Captain, Marjorie Cook, sees this as an opportunity to redeem herself after a tragic mistake in her past causes the death of over 400 of her crew.   It seems like an easy mission but, when the Arwen arrives, it finds things are not what they seem.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Arwen, Season 2: Ulliam]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/arwen-2/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Arwen, Season 2: Ulliam - A free audiobook by Tim Callahan]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/arwen-2/" description="<![CDATA[The Gyssyc ship is in orbit above Ulliam; the Taskforce sent to meet them has been destroyed.  Captain Cook fears the worst, the Gyssyc has declared war on the Ulliam.  The crew of the Arwen must figure out what happened before a second fleet arrives, the fate of three races rests in their hands.&nbsp; The Arwen Season 2: Ulliam is the sequel to th Parsec award winning novella The Arwen Season 1: Regal.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Arwen, Season 3: Armada]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/arwen-3/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Arwen, Season 3: Armada - A free audiobook by Timothy Callahan]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/arwen-3/" description="<![CDATA[The Earth Alliance prepares itself for a new war.  Two old enemy&apos;s have allied themselves with Regal, the planet the Arwen saved two years earlier, to build a massive Armada assigned to destroy Earth. Vice Admiral Payton Cook must defend the planet against insurmountable odds while Captain Cook does battle to save Ulliam from a deadly surprise attack.&nbsp; The Arwen: Season 3 is the final chapter of the Gyssyc trilogy which started with the Parsec award winning novella, the Arwen: Season one Regal, and continued with The Arwen Season two: Ulliam.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Arwen Season 4: The Water Planet]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/arwen-4/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Arwen Season 4: The Water Planet - A free audiobook by Timothy P. Callahan]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/arwen-4/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Arwen Season 4: The Water Planet</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Timothy P. Callahan</h3><p>Arwen Season IV-The Water planet is part one of a four part adventure that will stretch across the vastness of space and time.&nbsp; An exciting follow up to the Gyssyc trilogy, The Water Planet sets in motion events that will change the Arwen, her crew, Earth and the entire United Planets of the Corps forever.   </p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Arwen Season 5: Dyson Sphere]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/arwen-5/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Arwen Season 5: Dyson Sphere - A free audiobook by Timothy P. Callahan]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/arwen-5/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Arwen Season 5: Dyson Sphere</h1><h3>by Timothy P. Callahan</h3><p>The Arwen, Season 5: Dyson Sphere is part two of a four part adventure that will stretch across the vastness of space and time. An exciting  follow up to The Water Planet, Dyson Sphere introduces a new threat to Earth and all her allies. While traveling through the newly discovered Wormhole Beta space the Arwen receives a message from an astronaut thought dead for 450 years.  It's a mystery too curious for Professor Ricter, Captain Cook and her crew to ignore.  The stakes get even higher when it's discovered the signal originates from a massive Dyson Sphere.  What the Arwen and her crew discover changes everything they thought about their place in the galaxy.  </p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Arwen Season 6: The Final Days of Peace]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/arwen-6/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Arwen Season 6: The Final Days of Peace - A free audiobook by Timothy P. Callahan]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/arwen-6/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Arwen Season 6: The Final Days of Peace</h1><h3>by Timothy P. Callahan</h3><p>Part three of a four part adventure that will stretch across the vastness of space and time. An exciting follow-up to The Water Planet, and Dyson Sphere, The Final Days of Peace continues the war between the Earth Alliance and the Handlers, a race of aliens that outnumber humans a billion to one.  The Earth prepares itself for the inevitable arrival of the Handler's.  When they do attack, it's more devastating than anything they could ever imagine.</p>]]>" />
		<!-- Done listing The Arwen Saga -->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Ida]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/ida/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Ida - A free audiobook by Tim Callahan]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/ida/" description="<![CDATA[Ida, one of the largest Asteroid in the belt between Mars and Jupiter, has finally been colonized. A group of engineers lead by John McVey, Craig Osborn, Gail Trabor, Andrew Dee and Jennifer McGee, occupy the largest space station every built to plan the future of the tiny colony. Sent there by Kennedy Lacombe, the richest man in the world, their only task is to find ways to mine the asteroid as efficiently as possible. John, however, has grandiose plans including riding a comet around the sun to obtain enough water for the colony to one day survive independent from Earth. His ambition quickly shifts when he discovers an accident with the station&apos;s birth control pills causes 20 women, including Jennifer, the woman he loves, to become pregnant. The rules on pregnancy are simple; a baby is a drain on resources and must be removed. John, his friends, and a large group of miners will do anything they can to prevent that, including declaring themselves the first independent colony outside of Earth.]]>"/>
	</body>
</opml>
