<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Mystery Works &amp; Podnovels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" url="" type="link" text="<![CDATA[]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Serve It Cold]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/serve-it-cold/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/serve-it-cold/" text="<![CDATA[Serve It Cold - a free audiobook by Ronnie Blackwell]]>" description="<![CDATA[Detective Jonny C. Speed's life can't get much better. He's booked into the  French Quarter's most luxurious guesthouse, and his day job as convenience store manager is 104 miles behind him in Catherine, Mississippi. He's already taken care of one pro-bono missing persons job since he's been in New Orleans, and his paying client's cheating wife is a beautiful and very accommodating exhibitionist. Are things too good to be true? Of course they are. Jonny starts to worry when his client turns up dead, but when the suspects start dropping, Jonny and his crack team of beauty queens, recovering addicts, professional athletes, computer hackers, and pampered dogs find themselves caught in a twisted scheme of revenge that threatens to turn the town of Catherine inside out.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[hackoff.com]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/hackoff/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/hackoff/" text="<![CDATA[hackoff.com - A free audiobook by Tom Elvsin]]>" description="<![CDATA[Larry Lazard, CEO of hackoff.com, takes his company public and watches its stock price soar and collapse. Following a hostile takeover attempt, Lazard is found dead in his office of an apparently self-inflicted gunshot wound.Author Tom Evslin, a serial CEO, also took a company public in the Internet bubble and fought off hostile takeover attempts in the subsequent rubble. Unlike Larry, Evslin lived to tell what may be the definitive story of those strange times.The mystery moves backwards and forwards around the time of Larry&#0039;s death. Sex, power, money, farce, and tragedy mix in boardrooms and bedrooms, the parties of the World Economic Forum in Davos, and the smoky stairway of the South Tower of the World Trade Center.hackoff.com - not a porn site - provides anti-hacker protection for e-commerce. Larry Lazard started the business after his release from prison to which he was sentenced for a confessed hacker attack on banks.The folks at hackoff track the company&#0039;s stock price with fatal fascination; an online chat board provides a Greek chorus of contradictory explanations and expectations; analysts spin golden fantasies from websites and eyeballs; traders conjure real fortunes at their trading desks; and everyone who can clamors for &#quot;friends and family&#quot; stock.hackoff.com&#0039;s characters include CFO Donna Langhorne, Larry&#0039;s ex-lover and classmate from Harvard Business School and a former swimsuit model; Chief Technical Officer Dom Montain, who dropped out of Caltech to write video games; Detective Mark Cohen, NYPD, who&#0039;s investigating Larry&#0039;s death; Larry&#0039;s wife Louise, who is certain her husband was murdered; and Ahmed Qali, who represents a group of Palestinian programmers in Jenin to which hackoff out-sources work. Along with the bankers, CEOs, and CFOs of dotcom America, are eavesdropping limo drivers and waiters, venture capitalists, hackers, terrorists, and the victims and heroes of 9/11.If you&#0039;ve ever wanted to be a fly on the wall of the boardrooms, private jets, and ornate meeting rooms of brokerage firms, hackoff.com gives you your chance. You&#0039;ll be better prepared for the next bubble if you read this book but that&#0039;s not why you&#0039;ll eagerly download each online episode. You&#0039;ll do that because the cleverly woven mystery will have you dying to know whodunit.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Electricity]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/electricity/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/electricity/" text="<![CDATA[Electricty - A free audiobook by Myke Batlett]]>" description="<![CDATA[From the Author of How to Disappear Completely:1999Aston Somerfield, casual smoker and part-time alcoholic, has come to London to find himself. He knows who he's looking for, he's seen him on the cover of the NME. Drawn across oceans by fame and fate, Aston is keeping his diary empty to make sure he's available. Won't commit to anything until it's everything.London, however, has other ideas.When a virtual stranger calls Aston a few hours before his death, fate catches up with him, derailing his barely-made plans. Amid a hundred boozy evenings and romantic deadends, a mystery unfurls.Equally assisted and hindered by tremulous accountant Tom Hensley and dedicated loafer Steven Black, Aston uncovers a different London, one of murder, ghosts, dangerous emails and the second big bang.As chaotic and random as the city it inhabits, Electricity gradually evolves into a mystery bigger than the universe itself. Being of a somewhat useless persuasion, Aston does his best to ignore it.For more details: <a href='http://www.biggerthantheuniverse.com/'>www.biggerthantheuniverse.com</a>]]>"/>						
		-<outline title="<![CDATA[The House Down Cherry Tree Lane]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-house-down-cherry-tree-lane/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-house-down-cherry-tree-lane/feed/" text="<![CDATA[The House Down Cherry Tree Lane - A free audiobook by Ramona Holliday, narrated by Jeffrey Kafer]]>" description="<![CDATA[The House Down Cherry Tree Lane is a story of murder and intrigue to the 100th power. The story mixes the historic Gild family from a small town in Illinois with a modern day sister family. When they purchase the Gild house from a nervous realtor things are never the same for them. It will make your beliefs about ghosts and paranormal change forever. Written by Ramona Holliday, narrated by Jeffrey Kafer.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The May Day Murders]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/may-day-murders/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/may-day-murders/" text="<![CDATA[The May Day Murders - A free audiobook by Scott Wittenburg]]>" description="<![CDATA[The autumnal tranquility of Smithtown, Ohio is shattered when Dr. David Bradley arrives home to find that his wife has been raped and murdered by an intruder who has left no clues behind except the words &quot;May Day&quot; painted in lipstick on his victim's body. When the police later learn that another Smithtown resident has been raped and strangled in her New York City apartment, it becomes frighteningly clear that a cunning serial killer targeting Smithtown women is on the prowl.Newspaper reporter Sam Middleton is determined to help Detective Roger Hagstrom track down the assailant of his ex-wife's best friend. Sam can only hope that his estranged wife and teenage daughter are out of harm's way living hours away in the Columbus suburb of Woodcrest.  One terrifying question continues to gnaw at Sam as the mystery unfolds: Who will the killer's next victim be?]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Onion Files]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-onion-files/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-onion-files/" text="<![CDATA[The Onion Files - A free audiobook by Val Pattee]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - A free audiobook by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - A free audiobook by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - A free audiobook by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - A free audiobook by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - A free audiobook by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - A free audiobook by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
