<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			&apos; podcast novels, fiction, &amp; audio dramas.&nbsp; 
			Presented by: .
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Variable Man, The by Dick, Philip K.]]>" xmlUrl="http://librivox.org/rss/4275" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Variable Man, The by Dick, Philip K.]]>" htmlUrl="http://librivox.org/the-variable-man-by-philip-k-dick/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>http://librivox.org/the-variable-man-by-philip-k-dick/</h1><p>Predictability has come a long way.&nbsp; The computers of the future can tell you if you’re going to win a war before you fire a shot.&nbsp; Unfortunately they’re predicting perpetual standoff between the Terran and Centaurian Empires.&nbsp; What they need is something unpredictable, what they get is Thomas Cole, a man from the past accidently dragged forward in time.&nbsp; Will he fit their calculations, or is he the random variable that can break the stalemate? – The Variable Man first appeared in the September, 1953 issue of Space Science Fiction magazine. (Summary by Gregg Margarite)</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[First Men in the Moon, The by H. G. Wells]]>" xmlUrl="http://librivox.org/bookfeeds/the-first-men-in-the-moon-by-hg-wells.xml/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[First Men in the Moon, The by H. G. Wells]]>" htmlUrl="http://librivox.org/the-first-men-in-the-moon-by-hg-wells//" description="<![CDATA[<h1>First Men in the Moon, The by H. G. Wells</h1>Britain won the Moon Race!&nbsp; Decades before Neal Armstrong took his &quot;giant leap for mankind&quot; two intrepid adventurers from Lympne, England, journeyed there using not a rocket, but an antigravity coating.&nbsp; Mr.&nbsp; Bedford, who narrates the tale, tells of how he fell in with eccentric inventor Mr.&nbsp; Cavor, grew to believe in his researches, helped him build a sphere for traveling in space, and then partnered with him in an expedition to the Moon.&nbsp; What they found was fantastic!&nbsp; There was not only air and water, but the Moon was honeycombed with caverns and tunnels in which lived an advanced civilization of insect-like beings.&nbsp; While Bedford is frightened by them and bolts home, Cavor stays and is treated with great respect.&nbsp; So why didn&apos;t Armstrong and later astronauts find the evidence of all this?&nbsp; Well, according to broadcasts by Cavor over the newly-discovered radio technology, he told the Selenites too much about mankind, and apparently, they removed the welcome mat! (Summary by Mark)]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>

