<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<opml version="1.1">
  <head>
				<title>My Podiobooks Subscriptions</title>
	</head>
  <body>
	<outline title="Podiobooks.com: The Colorado Sequence by Stacey Cochran" text="Podiobooks.com: The Colorado Sequence by Stacey Cochran" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/275/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=275" description="Physicist Dr. Amy Levine has discovered a mathematical sequence--the Colorado Sequence--that describes an underlying pattern and a guiding force within the very fabric of reality. Now she's on the verge of an astonishing breakthrough, and the U.S. government wants to know how she has done it. How has Dr. Levine learned to accurately predict the future? And they're willing to kill her to find out. Levine and a group of friends escape to Colorado to unravel the mystery of the sequence, but there they become snowbound. They must locate a secret treasure room, find a hidden key, and answer an ancient riddle before a devastating eruption destroys them all ... and the power of the Colorado Sequence is lost forever.

&quot;The Colorado Sequence, by Stacey Cochran, is a unique blend of hard science fiction, fantasy, and thriller ... The strength of this book is the story and level of suspense. I didn't want to put this one down simply because of the suspense and wondering who would make it out alive. With strange creatures, harsh elements, and deadly tests, danger seems to lurk around every corner.&quot; -- SciFiChick.com

&quot;A quantum fable of spy intrigue, adventure and thought-provoking speculation on the nature of the universe.&quot; -- Mark Jeffrey, author of The Pocket and the Pendant

&quot;An entertaining fast-paced read.&quot; -- Jeremy Robinson, author of The Didymus Contingency

&quot;Nonstop action makes you want to read 'til the end. I loved it!&quot; -- Richard Triebe, author of On a Rising Tide

&quot;A unique blend of fantasy and suspense, The Colorado Sequence builds a strong female character in Amy Levine.&quot; -- Julio Vazquez, author of Death at Disney

&quot;I have sacks under my eyes because I have been up late the last few nights reading The Colorado Sequence. I finished it last night at 2:31 A.M. because I simply could not put it down. I so enjoyed this book!&quot; -- Ericka Jackson, author of A Mansion Mindset

&quot;Nonstop action ... powerful!&quot; -- Brew City Magazine

&quot;With all the action scenes, running gun battles and explosions this story has all the makings for an action packed, big-screen movie.&quot; -- Gene Curtis, author of The Seventh Mountain

&quot;Thrilling, action packed!&quot; -- Hannah Stone, author of Remembering Our Angels" />
<outline title="Podiobooks.com: South Coast by Nathan Lowell" text="Podiobooks.com: South Coast by Nathan Lowell" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/237/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=237" description="A Shaman's Tale from the Golden Age of the Solar Clipper : Volume 1 

Otto is Richard Krugg's only son and heir to the Shaman's gift. The only problem is Otto doesn't want it. He wants to be a fisherman. When company policies force unwelcome changes onto his life and threaten even the security of the village, Otto discovers that being a shaman isn't optional.Jimmy Pirano is caught between the devil and the deep green sea when new production quotas are handed down from corporate headquarters. Locked into a century of existing practice, Jimmy is forced to find new ways to fish and new places to do it in or face the very real possibility that Pirano Fisheries will lose the St. Cloud franchise.Join Otto, Richard, and Rachel Krugg as they struggle with what it means to be the son of a shaman. Cast off with Jimmy, Tony, and Casey as they navigate the shoals and shallows of corporate fishery along the South Coast." />
<outline title="Podiobooks.com: Double Share by Nathan Lowell" text="Podiobooks.com: Double Share by Nathan Lowell" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/293/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=293" description="A Trader's Tale from the Golden Age of the Solar Clipper : Book 4

When he graduates from the Academy at Port Newmar, Ishmael Horatio Wang reports for duty in his first assignment as an officer. When he gets to his new ship, he finds things are not exactly the way he'd learned in school. The coffee tastes like used engine oil, the ship has no heart, and the nearest decent tailor is two quadrants away. What's a new Third Mate to do? Will he be able to trust Billy?" />
<outline title="Podiobooks.com: Chase Around The World by Tiara Fay" text="Podiobooks.com: Chase Around The World by Tiara Fay" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/292/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=292" description="The first-ever romance fiction title presented on Podiobooks.com, &quot;Chase Around The World&quot; takes you on a wild ride alongside Emerald Harrison, an Australian beauty who, after meeting the French-accented, intriguing and adventurous Ace Black, wakes up to realise that the life she has worked so hard for holds no interest anymore.

Set in the sensuous surrounds of steamy, tropical India, &quot;Chase Around The World&quot; weaves an intricate web of passion and deception as Emerald follows the mysterious Ace into the unknown of a foreign country. With their heightening romance shrouded in deceit, there's plenty of sexual tension and emotional conflicts to keep you glued to your headphones." />
<outline title="Podiobooks.com: Murder at Avedon Hill by P.G. Holyfield" text="Podiobooks.com: Murder at Avedon Hill by P.G. Holyfield" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/229/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=229" description="Lord Avedon has a problem. Generations of Avedons have watched over Avedon Hill and controlled the only pass through the Lantis Mountains. Traditions are important to the Avedon family, but one tradition has tragically come to an end. Gretta Platt, Housemistress of Avedon Manor, has been murdered. A member of the Platt family has always served the Avedons as Housemistress. until now. Only a handful of people live at Avedon Hill, and most are suspects. Arames Kragen, retired Aarronic Advisor and scholar of prophecy, arrives at the gates of Avedon Hill, hoping to gain access to the mountain pass. Lord Avedon is not in a giving mood, however.

This is the story of Arames Kragen and his attempt not only to discover who killed Gretta Platt, but also to uncover the truth about a town that apparently has more secrets than inhabitants.

The Land of Caern: It is a world where the gods, the Children of Az, can choose to be born as mortals to directly affect events in the world, and often do. It is a world where the Priests of Caern frantically search for the mortal incarnations of any of the Children, in order prevent the Prophecies of Iberian from coming to pass.

Welcome to The Land of Caern. Welcome. to Murder at Avedon Hill, the podcast novel by P.G. Holyfield." />
<outline title="Podiobooks.com: Heaven - Season Four: Wasteland by Mur Lafferty" text="Podiobooks.com: Heaven - Season Four: Wasteland by Mur Lafferty" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/260/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=260" description="Daniel has been forced from the afterlife to be exiled in the wasteland, with nothing but his misery and Kate's dead body. But he is not without power entirely, and he begins to make his way in this world that looks less like a wasteland and more like another world. But the volatile power of the wasteland still touches this new world, and Daniel and his friends must not forget the trouble facing Heaven and Hell." />
<outline title="Podiobooks.com: The Veingel by Jeremy James" text="Podiobooks.com: The Veingel by Jeremy James" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/189/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=189" description="When an ancient religious cult hunts his people to the brink of extinction, Jequon, a half-angel, half-human badass fights for the survival of his noble race.

But as his enemies' holy-caust gains support from powerful officials in the U.S. government, our hero is forced to seek help from an unlikely source: a woman defined by her faith in the same God who wants him dead.

Even worse, he starts to fall for her." />
<outline title="Podiobooks.com: Tamshi\'s Imp by Jonathan Fesmire" text="Podiobooks.com: Tamshi\'s Imp by Jonathan Fesmire" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/231/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=231" description="Tamshi Telardian just had an epiphany. She now realizes that her memories are gone, and she has been serving an arch-demon bent on destroying the true gods. Further, her ice imp familiar has vanished in the confusion. How can a simple sorceress stop an entire cult, let alone an ancient demon lord?

&quot;Jonathan Fesmire continues to grow as the fantasist of the new generation. Tamshi's Imp is a blend of magic and mayhem, heartbreak and heroism, sorcery and suspense, but at its heart, it's also a story of redemption and the undying power of love. It is an adventure not to be missed!&quot; -James Clemens, international bestselling author of &quot;The Banned and the Banished&quot;" />
</body>
</opml>	