<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			Science Fiction&appos;s podcast novels &ndash; prensented by: podiobooks.com
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[3 Dooms of America]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/3-dooms-of-america/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[3 Dooms of America - A free audiobook by Eugene Fairfield]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/3-dooms-of-america/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>3 Dooms of America by Eugene Fairfield</h1><p>'Prophecy is not a prediction of tomorrow. It is a description of the doom contained within today.'Three stories of the end of American society, from one Tuesday, the 11th of September into the near future.Shock & Awe: 'At the end of this story, a baby will be born, and touch off an insurrection. Before that, a woman makes breakfast.'The Greening of Blue England: 'It took three-quarters of a ton of plastique to get rid of all the box stores in Taft Corners.'Spider's Dreams:...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[7th Son: 7 Days (Prequel Anthology)]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/7th-son-7-days/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[7th Son: 7 Days (Prequel Anthology) - A free audiobook by J.C. Hutchins]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/7th-son-7-days/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>7th Son: 7 Days (Prequel Anthology) by J.C. Hutchins</h1><p>7th Son: 7 Days is a audio prequel anthology to J.C. Hutchins' thriller novel, 7th Son: Descent. Set two weeks before Descents extraordinary events, the series reveals the lives of seven seemingly unrelated men, and their everyday challenges.In the world of 7th Son, 'everyday challenges' are far from ordinary. Each of these seven stories stars a unique John Michael Smith. Witness criminal profiler Dr. Mike's quest to hunt an unstoppable serial killer. Watch blue-collar musician John...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[7th Son: Book One - Descent (The Beta Version)]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/7th-son-book-one---descent/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[7th Son: Book One - Descent (The Beta Version) - A free audiobook by J.C. Hutchins]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/7th-son-book-one---descent/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>7th Son: Book One - Descent (The Beta Version) by J.C. Hutchins</h1><p><a href='http://parsecawards.com' target='_blank'><img class='donation' src='http://www.podiobooks.com/images/parsec120.gif'  width='120' height='80' hspace=10 vspace=10 align=right border=0/></a>AUTHOR'S NOTE: This is 'The Beta Version' of this podiobook. 7th Son: Descent is now available as a print novel from St. Martin's Press. During the editorial process, significant changes and improvements were made to Descent's print manuscript. Character names were changed, and events at the end...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[7th Son: Book Three - Destruction (The Beta Version)]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/7S3-Destruction/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[7th Son: Book Three - Destruction (The Beta Version) - A free audiobook by J. C. Hutchins]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/7S3-Destruction/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>7th Son: Book Three - Destruction (The Beta Version) by J. C. Hutchins</h1><p>AUTHOR'S NOTE: This is 'The Beta Version' of this podiobook. 7th Son: Descent is now available as a print novel from St. Martin's Press. During the editorial process, significant changes and improvements were made to Descent's print manuscript. Character names were changed, and events at the end of the print novel were modified in ways that will impact the rest of the print trilogy. The print novel represents an official reboot of the 7th Son series.Due to these changes, this 'Beta...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[7th Son: Book Two - Deceit (The Beta Version)]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/7th-son-book-two---deceit/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[7th Son: Book Two - Deceit (The Beta Version) - A free audiobook by J.C. Hutchins]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/7th-son-book-two---deceit/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>7th Son: Book Two - Deceit (The Beta Version) by J.C. Hutchins</h1><p><a href='http://parsecawards.com/2007Finalists' target='_blank'><img src='http://farm2.static.flickr.com/1398/1224364836_1d5a4b70ac_o.gif' width='80' height='99' alt='Parsec-Seal-2007-Nominee' align='right' hspace='5' /></a>AUTHOR'S NOTE: This is 'The Beta Version' of this podiobook. 7th Son: Descent is now available as a print novel from St. Martin's Press. During the editorial process, significant changes and improvements were made to Descent's print manuscript. Character names were...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[A Different Point of View]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/a-different-point-of-view/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[A Different Point of View - A free audiobook by TD-0013]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/a-different-point-of-view/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>A Different Point of View by TD-0013</h1><p>Recently re-mastered with all around better quality sound and production!! Originally aired as a segment for <a href='http://michaelandevo.com'>Michael and Evo's Wingin' It! podcast</a>, <i>A Different Point of View</i> is a series of essays about the Star Wars Universe as seen through the eyes of lowly sandtrooper, TD-0013. It takes everything you thought you knew about the Star Wars saga and flips it around to expose the ugly underbelly of the Rebellion, The Jedi, and everything else....</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Alibi Jones]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/alibi-jones/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Alibi Jones - A free audiobook by Mike Luoma]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/alibi-jones/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Alibi Jones by Mike Luoma</h1><p>Science Fiction Adventure in the year 2135! Alibi Jones, a Mediator for the Solar Alliance, is on the trail of alien kidnappers. He'll soon discover that dangers thought long-dead are still very much ALIVE!This stand-alone sequel (of sorts) to The VATICAN ASSASSIN Trilogy takes place 23 years after the events in VATICAN ABDICATOR.  New readers will have no trouble jumping in, while those who enjoyed the first trilogy will meet old friends, new characters, and new alien races and...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Aliens and Satanic Creatures Wanted: Humans Need Not Apply]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/aliens-and-satanic-creatures-wanted-humans-need-no/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Aliens and Satanic Creatures Wanted: Humans Need Not Apply - A free audiobook by Tony Ruggiero]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/aliens-and-satanic-creatures-wanted-humans-need-no/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Aliens and Satanic Creatures Wanted: Humans Need Not Apply by Tony Ruggiero</h1><p>Do you think its easy being an alien, a satanic creature or anything else not considered part of the Homo sapiens only club? They have tough days just like humans do and their frustration is growing. Don't believe it? Well, what about Lucifer, the prince of darkness, who runs a car dealership--what about his feelings when he is faced with that impossible sale and he can't get that signature on form 666, the standard soul contract? Or maybe you wondered about how an extremely vain alien copes...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[AmerIndian 2192]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/amerindian-2192/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[AmerIndian 2192 - A free audiobook by J. Scott Garibay]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/amerindian-2192/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>AmerIndian 2192 by J. Scott Garibay</h1><p>AmerIndian 2192 is a science-fiction novel that explores the intriguing possibilities of Native Americans in mankind's star flung future. AmerIndian 2192 presents the story of two brothers, Wovoka and Keokuk, restoring the Native American people to a Homeland where their vibrant culture can thrive. Lodge ships, Cybershaman rituals and Tsimshian high technology are all elements in this action-oriented tale of interstellar politics and personal struggles.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Anon Time]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/anon-time/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Anon Time - A free audiobook by Craig Robertson]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/anon-time/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Anon Time by Craig Robertson</h1><p>What if you weren't who you thought you were, what others saw you to be?  What if the structure of time depended on you to keep it steady.  What if unseen forces, both good and evil, surrounded you, effecting your life in way's you could not begin to imagine?  Well, if that were the case, you'd be Mark De Martel, unobtrusive advertising agent in Los Angeles.  Or would you?  Possibly you were a Mark, but possibly you would be a powerful warrior, using skills such as the manipulation of gravity...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Badge Of Infamy]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/badge-of-infamy/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Badge Of Infamy - A free audiobook by Lester Del Rey]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/badge-of-infamy/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Badge Of Infamy by Lester Del Rey</h1><p><a href='http://parsecawards.com/2007Finalists' target='_blank'><img src='http://farm2.static.flickr.com/1398/1224364836_1d5a4b70ac_o.gif' width='80' height='99' alt='Parsec-Seal-2007-Nominee' align='right' hspace='5' /></a>Daniel Feldman was a doctor once.  He made the mistake of saving a friend's life in violation of Medical Lobby rules.  Now, he's a pariah, shunned by all, forbidden to touch another patient.But things are more loose on Mars. There, Doc Feldman is welcomed by the...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Beautiful Red]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/beautiful-red/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Beautiful Red - A free audiobook by M. Darusha Wehm]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/beautiful-red/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Beautiful Red by M. Darusha Wehm</h1><p>The future is boring. Technology has solved the world's most pressing problems, leaving people with tedious work and mundane play. Jack is a Security Officer Class 5, which sounds important, but isn't. However, her banal life as a cubicle worker by day and tinkerer by night is interrupted when she discovers that her employer's computer system has been invaded.Jack enlists the help of her only friends  her co-worker, Gilles and Adrian, an online friend she's never met  to help her track...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Black Shadow]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/black-shadow/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Black Shadow - A free audiobook by Steve Saylor]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/black-shadow/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Black Shadow by Steve Saylor</h1><p>In a world where evil walks the earth, where super villains are taken over by demonic beings . They all want one thing, and one thing only. To take over the world. There is only one man who can stop them. One man with the powers and abilities to kick some serious demon ass. In a race against time to stop a portal that opens to Hell itself. One man, one hero, one sonofabitch you don't want to mess with.He is faceless,He is fearless,He is... Black Shadow.From the mind of debut...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Black Star Passes]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/black-star-passes/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Black Star Passes - A free audiobook by John W. Campbell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/black-star-passes/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Black Star Passes by John W. Campbell</h1><p>Follow along with Arcot, Morey, and Wade as they discover a revolutionary form of propulsion, visit our neighboring planets, and go up against aliens from a rogue solar system that passes close to our own.  These three stories (Piracy Preferred, Solarite, and The Black Star Passes) were originally published as a serial in Amazing Stories magazine.Read by <a href='http://www.scottfarquhar.com' target='_new'>Scott D. Farquhar</a> of <a href='http://www.prometheusradiotheatre.com'...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Borrowed Time]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/borrowed-time/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Borrowed Time - A free audiobook by Keith Hughes]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/borrowed-time/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Borrowed Time by Keith Hughes</h1><p>Ness Relevant is living on borrowed time. Molecular implosion, cellular degeneration, and dangerous men are but a few of the perils faced by the friendly and unassuming forensic photographer.His quiet bachelorhood is interrupted when he receives an innocent looking device in the mail from a friend and former college professor. Ness unexpectedly finds himself embroiled in events driven by his friend's success.This device is the focal point of a struggle that could overturn the whole...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Captains Share]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/captains-share/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Captains Share - A free audiobook by Nathan Lowell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/captains-share/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Captains Share by Nathan Lowell</h1><p><a href='http://www.podiobooks.com/blog/2010/01/05/2009-founders-choice-awards/'><img src='http://farm5.static.flickr.com/4026/4249613583_1c731dc0dd_o.gif' align='right' hspace='10' vspace='10' /></a>A Trader's Tale from the Golden Age of the Solar ClipperA shuffling of cabins puts Ishmael Horatio Wang in command of the worst ship in the fleet. He learns that being Captain doesn't make you infallible and that life in the Captain's Cabin is filled with new kinds of challenge as he tries to...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Cell U.R.]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/cellur/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Cell U.R. - A free audiobook by Mark Plimsoll]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/cellur/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Cell U.R. by Mark Plimsoll</h1><p>Vampires dance with Goths around campfires far from the rainy Metroplex- as the Central Computer says in Cell U.R. 'Most entertainment consists of beautiful people on sexy adventures without kids, because real life is the opposite.'  Imagine a near future, when nanotechnology allows doctors to install speakerphones on the inside of everyone's ears, a microphone in their throat, and scanners that record through the eyes. All citizens enjoy a permanent connection to the internet. One human...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Children of the Old Stars]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/children-old-stars/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Children of the Old Stars - A free audiobook by David Lee Summers]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/children-old-stars/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Children of the Old Stars by David Lee Summers</h1><p>The Cluster is a vast alien machine that destroys starships indiscriminately in its quest for something or someone.  Commander John Mark Ellis, disgraced and booted out of the service when he fails to save a merchant ship, believes the key to stopping the Cluster is communication.  His mother, Suki Firebrandt Ellis is a historian who believes the very leaders of the galaxy are withholding information about the Cluster.  Clyde McClintlock believes the Cluster is God incarnate, seeking...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Collapse at Hidden Verse Three Three Two]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/collapse-at-hidden-verse-three-three-two/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Collapse at Hidden Verse Three Three Two - A free audiobook by Brian Holtz]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/collapse-at-hidden-verse-three-three-two/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Collapse at Hidden Verse Three Three Two by Brian Holtz</h1><p>The Multiverse Generator is failing.  Dimensions threaten to collapse and entire populations will cease to exist unless it is reset.  One being from each of more than five thousand verses has been acquired, and their DNA verified.  Only one remains.  His name is Timothy Rayburn and he is a resident of Earth.  The Consolidation of Organized Systems has sent a ship to retrieve him. Timothy is a teenager failing speech class due to a paralyzing fear of public speaking. He soon learns that...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Crescent]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/crescent/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Crescent - A free audiobook by Phil Rossi]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/crescent/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Crescent by Phil Rossi</h1><p>Crescent is the last stop at the intergalactic crossroads of gritty sci-fi and pucker-inducing horror. --Scott Sigler, New York Times bestselling author of ContagiousCrescent is the ultimate sci-fi / horror mashup. It's a wicked blend of the claustrophobia seen in Ridley Scott's Alien, and the viral demonology of Carpenter's Prince Of Darkness with the hard-drinkin' bad attitude of Battlestar Galactica added for good measure. The future has never been so frightening. Phil Rossi brings it....</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Dead Mech]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/dead-mech/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Dead Mech - A free audiobook by Jake Bible]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/dead-mech/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Dead Mech by Jake Bible</h1><p>After the zombie apocalypse decimates the world, human civilization tries to put itself back together again. Their secret weapon: the Mechs. But what happens when a mech pilot dies in his mech and becomes a zombie? Hell on earth is unleashed...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Discovered Country]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/discovered-country/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Discovered Country - A free audiobook by Nora Fleischer]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/discovered-country/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Discovered Country by Nora Fleischer</h1><p>Far from home...Rosemary Halpern, a mild-mannered librarian from Boston, found herself trapped hundreds of years in the future.  A future that faced a new Ice Age. A future where ghouls walked the Earth, ravenous for human flesh.A world where she was drawn to a man who was already dead...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Doctor Janeway]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/doctor-janeways-plague/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Doctor Janeway - A free audiobook by John Farrell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/doctor-janeways-plague/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Doctor Janeway by John Farrell</h1><p>A science-fiction thriller about an astronomer who discovers a source of cosmic rays which may be the origin of an ancient plague reviving once again.A young woman reaches Cambridge in search of a distant relative whom she believes has lived longer than any other human being.An astronomer discovers a strange, point-like source of cosmic rays coming from the constellation of the Unicorn.A retiring professor discovers documents from Puritan times about a series of strange deaths and...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Double Share]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/double-share/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Double Share - A free audiobook by Nathan Lowell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/double-share/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Double Share by Nathan Lowell</h1><p><a href='http://www.podiobooks.com/blog/2008/12/30/2008-founders-choice-awards/'><img src='http://farm5.static.flickr.com/4030/4285895645_98147f8aee_o.gif' align='right' hspace='10' vspace='10' /></a><a href='http://parsecawards.com/node/861'><img src='http://farm4.static.flickr.com/3574/3773548318_0f024bb111_o.jpg' align='right' hspace='5' border='0' /></a>A Trader's Tale from the Golden Age of the Solar Clipper : Book 4When he graduates from the Academy at Port Newmar, Ishmael Horatio...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Down and Out in the Magic Kingdom]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/down-and-out-in-the-magic-kingdom/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Down and Out in the Magic Kingdom - A free audiobook by Cory Doctorow]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/down-and-out-in-the-magic-kingdom/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Down and Out in the Magic Kingdom by Cory Doctorow</h1><p>Jules is a young man, barely a century old. He's lived long enough to see the cure for death and the end of scarcity, to learn ten languages and compose three symphonies...and to realize his boyhood dream of taking up residence in Disney World.Disney World! The greatest achievement of the long-ago twentieth century. Now in the keeping of a network of 'ad-hocs' who keep the classic attractions running as they always have, enhanced with only the smallest high-tech touches.Now, though,...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Dreams and Wings (A Searcher and Stallion story)]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/searcher-and-stallion-dreams-and-wings/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Dreams and Wings (A Searcher and Stallion story) - A free audiobook by Scott Howard]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/searcher-and-stallion-dreams-and-wings/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Dreams and Wings (A Searcher and Stallion story) by Scott Howard</h1><p>One Man, One Machine, One Destiny.Searcher awoke, alone on a laboratory table, with an ageless body and no knowledge of his past in a post apocalyptic world. Now in his exoskel, a powered suit of armor, he roams the galaxy with his robotic companion Stallion, seeking clues about his unknown origins. Meanwhile, His existence threatens to destroy balance among the ageless ones, a group of never dying humanoids that secretly run all aspects of human society in the shadows of the surviving...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Duel of the Fates, Tournament 2]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/duel-of-the-fates-tournament-2/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Duel of the Fates, Tournament 2 - A free audiobook by Jack Mangan]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/duel-of-the-fates-tournament-2/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Duel of the Fates, Tournament 2 by Jack Mangan</h1><p>Author Jack Mangan (Spherical Tomi) is back with Duel of the Fates 2! As originally heard on the Dragon Page Wingin' It! Podcast: Duel of the Fates 2 assembles highly diverse, iconic combatants from across the wide universe of speculative fiction and pits them head-to-head in comparative contests of 5 monumentally important categories. 1) Dr. Evil (Austin Powers)2) Six Million Dollar Man3) TD-0013 (A Diff'rent Point of View)4) The Mighty Thor5) Ash (Evil Dead)6) Starbuck from...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Earthcore]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/earthcore/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Earthcore - A free audiobook by Scott Sigler]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/earthcore/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Earthcore by Scott Sigler</h1><p>Deep below a desolate Utah mountain lays the largest platinum deposit ever discovered. A billion-dollar find, it waits for any company that can drill a world's record, three-mile-deep mine shaft.EarthCore is the company with the technology, the resources and the guts to go after the mother lode. Young executive Connell Kirkland is the company's driving force, pushing himself and those around him to uncover the massive treasure.But Kirkland and EarthCore are not the first to find this...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Eastern Standard Tribe]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/eastern-standard-tribe/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Eastern Standard Tribe - A free audiobook by Cory Doctorow]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/eastern-standard-tribe/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Eastern Standard Tribe by Cory Doctorow</h1><p>Art is an up-and-coming interface designer, working on the management of data flow along the Massachusetts Turnpike. He's doing the best work of his career and can guarantee that the system will be, without question, the most counterintuitive, user-hostile piece of software ever pushed forth into the world.Why? Because Art is an industrial saboteur. He may live in London and work for an EU telecommunications megacorp, but Art's real home is the Eastern Standard Tribe.The comm --...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Eden]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/eden/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Eden - A free audiobook by Phil Rossi]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/eden/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Eden by Phil Rossi</h1><p><a href='http://parsecawards.com/node/861'><img src='http://farm4.static.flickr.com/3574/3773548318_0f024bb111_o.jpg' align='right' hspace='5' border='0' /></a>The tree is beautiful and they call her Eden.  Her branches reach for the stars.  She is like all other trees on planet Earth save for her enormous size. Still, she has leaves and she has bark. She turns sunlight into life. But this tree does not sprout from the dirt. Eden fills the sky, high in orbit above the blue expanse of Uranus....</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Editing Reality]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/editing-reality/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Editing Reality - A free audiobook by Micah Dubinko]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/editing-reality/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Editing Reality by Micah Dubinko</h1><p>Editing Reality is both the name of a novel-in-progress and a podcast about the reality of editing. Host Micah Dubinko tackles a new editing topic each week, and puts it into practice against an installment of his novel. If you're curious about the process of editing fiction, or just in the mood for a satirical story about a mad scientist, a mentally unbalanced gangster, a superhero wannabe, and a gang of cyberpirates, come have a listen.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Flatland: A Romance of Many Dimensions]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/flatland/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Flatland: A Romance of Many Dimensions - A free audiobook by A Square (Edwin Abbott Abbott)]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/flatland/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Flatland: A Romance of Many Dimensions by A Square (Edwin Abbott Abbott)</h1><p>Math.  Geometry.  Physics.  Violence?  Is this the same book I read in school?  Yep.One of the joys of rediscovering old books is that they still have the ability to surprise, even shock.'If my poor Flatland friend retained the vigour of mind which he enjoyed when he began to compose these Memoirs, I should not now need to represent him in this preface, in which he desires, fully, to return his thanks to his readers and critics in Spaceland ... But he is not the Square he once was....</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Fractured Horizon]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/fractured-horizon/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Fractured Horizon - A free audiobook by H.E. Roulo]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/fractured-horizon/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Fractured Horizon by H.E. Roulo</h1><p><a href='http://parsecawards.com/node/861'><img src='http://farm4.static.flickr.com/3574/3773548318_0f024bb111_o.jpg' align='right' hspace='5' border='0' /></a>Katherine Downs sets off to find her mysterious fatherand awakens hundreds of years later into a world guided by visionary Royals.  But Kay inadvertently blinds their power. Hunted, she joins the rebel Adams, bioengineered warriors who rely on banned technology for a precarious foothold on the fading world.  Will they destroy Kay...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Full Share]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/full-share/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Full Share - A free audiobook by Nathan Lowell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/full-share/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Full Share by Nathan Lowell</h1><p>A Trader's Tale from the Golden Age of the Solar Clipper : Book 3The Lois McKendrick runs headlong into trouble when a routine in-system transit goes bad. Ishmael and the rest of the crew must scramble to figure out what went wrong and how to fix it in order to keep the ship alive. Learn more about the officers and crew of the Lois McKendrick as they struggle to keep their ship and discover how Ishmael finds out how wrong he's been about what it means to be a spacer in this latest...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Greater Good]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/greater-good/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Greater Good - A free audiobook by Nathan P. Butler]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/greater-good/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Greater Good by Nathan P. Butler</h1><p>In the world of tomorrow, the American Regime dominates our hemisphere, ruled by a new nobility: telepaths. While this powerful new minority rules over the normal human majority, society enjoys stability and security. However, with this new world comes new prejudices and oppression.Now, a powerful telepathic killer from the future has come to our present to eliminate this new world - a serial killer today, a genocide for tomorrow. It is up to a law enforcement officer from the future and...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Grey]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/grey/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Grey - A free audiobook by Jon Armstrong]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/grey/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Grey by Jon Armstrong</h1><p>High fashion, corporate malfeasance, celebrity culture, and an obsessed media collide with exuberant violence and volatile intensity in Grey, the explosive debut novel by Jon Armstrong.For Michael Rivers, life is perfect. Michael has everything; tall, handsome, and famous, he is worshipped by billions of fans around the globe. He is wealthy beyond measure, the heir apparent to RiverGroup, one of the handful of high-tech corporations that controls the world. He is fashionable, setting...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Half Share]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/half-share/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Half Share - A free audiobook by Nathan Lowell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/half-share/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Half Share by Nathan Lowell</h1><p>A Trader's Tale from the Golden Age of the Solar Clipper : Book 2After Ishmael Wang is promoted to the environmental section, he's caught in a swirl of mystery, doubt, belief, lust and a really nice fitting pair of jeans. He has to come to grips with what it means to be a spacer while he's still trying to figure out what it means to be a man. Join Ishmael, Brillo, Pip, and the rest of the crew of the Lois McKendrick as they help the newest member of the crew adjust to life in the Deep...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Heirs of the New Earth]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/heirs-of-the-new-earth/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Heirs of the New Earth - A free audiobook by David Lee Summers]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/heirs-of-the-new-earth/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Heirs of the New Earth by David Lee Summers</h1><p>The Earth has gone silent. John Mark Ellis and the crew of the Sanson are sent to investigate. When they arrive, they find vast alien machines known as Clusters in orbit. Fearing the worst, they land and discover that the once overcrowded, polluted Earth has become a paradise of sorts. The problem is over half the population is dead or missing and the planet's leaders don't seem to care. As Ellis works to unravel the mystery, sudden gravitational shifts from the galaxy's center indicate...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Homesick]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/homesick/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Homesick - A free audiobook by Paul J. Joseph]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/homesick/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Homesick by Paul J. Joseph</h1><p>The mission to New Ontario, is not going as planned.  The first landing ends in disaster when the American astronaut, Scott Anderson, goes down alone and dissappears.  Captain Sally Buds, Ian Merryfield, Vladamir Coronov must put aside their personal differences and attempt an umarmed rescue unsure of what awaits them below.  On the surface, they find only the remnants of a civilization.  Buildings are rotting and the remains of human-like bodies are scattered around what may once have...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Ida]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/ida/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Ida - A free audiobook by Tim Callahan]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/ida/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Ida by Tim Callahan</h1><p>Ida, one of the largest Asteroid in the belt between Mars and Jupiter, has finally been colonized. A group of engineers lead by John McVey, Craig Osborn, Gail Trabor, Andrew Dee and Jennifer McGee, occupy the largest space station every built to plan the future of the tiny colony. Sent there by Kennedy Lacombe, the richest man in the world, their only task is to find ways to mine the asteroid as efficiently as possible. John, however, has grandiose plans including riding a comet around the...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Iron Dragons: Book 1 - The Saramond Quests]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/iron-dragons/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Iron Dragons: Book 1 - The Saramond Quests - A free audiobook by Derek Gilbert]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/iron-dragons/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Iron Dragons: Book 1 - The Saramond Quests by Derek Gilbert</h1><p><a href='http://www.podiobooks.com/blog/2008/12/30/2008-founders-choice-awards/'><img src='http://farm5.static.flickr.com/4030/4285895645_98147f8aee_o.gif' align='right' hspace='10' vspace='10' /></a>Dragon pee really stinks.With that bit of cautionary advice, master dragonslayer Davian begins his tale.Davian is a Third Level Master of The Order, a group of men who alone have the power to battle the most fearsome creatures on all of Saramond. For thousands of years, the brothers of...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Kronos]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/kronos/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Kronos - A free audiobook by Jeremy Robinson]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/kronos/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Kronos by Jeremy Robinson</h1><p>Two years after his wife's death, oceanographer and former navy SEAL, Atticus Young, attempts to reconcile with his rebellious daughter, Giona, by taking her on the scuba dive of a lifetime-swimming with a pod of peaceful humpback whales in the Gulf of Maine.  But the beauty of the sea belies a terror from the deep-a horrific creature as immense as it is ancient. There is no blood, no scream, no fight. Giona is swallowed whole by the massive jaws. Only Atticus remains to suffer the shame of...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Loner In Space]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/loner-in-space/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Loner In Space - A free audiobook by Steve Simons]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/loner-in-space/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Loner In Space by Steve Simons</h1><p>This book was written originally for children,  but the adults in Steve's test audience also enjoyed it.   The book tells the story of a boy who is a bit of a loner at school and in life.  His home life is also a bit in tatters since his mum died.  The book takes up the story when he discovers something in the woods, near where he lives,  little does he know where his discovery will take him, but the title of the book gives you an idea, what will he find there?  Will he still be...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Marker Stone]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/marker-stone/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Marker Stone - A free audiobook by Paul J. Joseph]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/marker-stone/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Marker Stone by Paul J. Joseph</h1><p>Theres trouble on CMC-6 and its been brewing for a long time.  The golden age of space travel and asteroid mining has ended almost before it began and the bean counters have taken over.  Sally Buds patients are all suffering from low-gravity syndrome because the Canadian Mining Consortium wont spring for gravity generators and the miners wont exercise.  On top of this the station might be facing hard times.  An expensive mining robot disappeared while surveying a region of space known...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Mr. Dead Eyes]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/mr-dead-eyes/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Mr. Dead Eyes - A free audiobook by Roberto Scarlato]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/mr-dead-eyes/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Mr. Dead Eyes by Roberto Scarlato</h1><p>Strange things happen when the lights go down in the shady setting of the Roseville Hospital. Unexplained sightings of a man resembling that of a doctor is known to walk the hallways in search of patients he has yet to help. His name was Derek R. Schillar, M.D. He was a complicated man with a desire to help people, but felt that he didn't do enough. Now, his friend has betrayed him, his wife thinks he's dead, a mysterious detective is on his trail, and the medical staff is perplexed at the...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Playing for Keeps]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/playing-for-keeps/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Playing for Keeps - A free audiobook by Mur Lafferty]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/playing-for-keeps/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Playing for Keeps by Mur Lafferty</h1><p><a href='http://www.podiobooks.com/blog/2008/12/30/2008-founders-choice-awards/'><img src='http://farm5.static.flickr.com/4030/4285895645_98147f8aee_o.gif' align='right' hspace='10' vspace='10' /></a>Playing for Keeps tells the story of Keepsie Branson, a bar owner in the shining metropolis of Seventh City: birthplace of super powers. Keepsie and her friends live among egotistical heroes and manipulative villains, and manage to fall directly in the middle as people with powers, but who just...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Predestination and Other Games of Chance: Book One of The Antithesis Progression]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/predestination-and-other-games-of-chance/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Predestination and Other Games of Chance: Book One of The Antithesis Progression - A free audiobook by J. Daniel Sawyer]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/predestination-and-other-games-of-chance/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Predestination and Other Games of Chance: Book One of The Antithesis Progression by J. Daniel Sawyer</h1><p><a href='http://parsecawards.com/node/861'><img src='http://farm4.static.flickr.com/3574/3773548318_0f024bb111_o.jpg' align='right' hspace='5' border='0' /></a>In the Port of Call bar on Space Station Sidon a man sits at a card game. Hes ruthless, hes unforgiving, and he almost never loses. His name is Alex Hart, and he is waiting for someone.Reuben Briggs never could play nice with others. As a professor he couldnt stay out of trouble. As the National Security Advisor he couldnt...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Quarter Share]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/quarter-share/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Quarter Share - A free audiobook by Nathan Lowell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/quarter-share/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Quarter Share by Nathan Lowell</h1><p>A Trader's Tale from the Golden Age of the Solar Clipper : Book 1When Ishmael Wang is orphaned by a flitter crash, he must make some hard decisions about how to survive in a Company-owned universe. With limited time and fewer options, he lands a job as the newest hand on the Solar Clipper Lois McKendrick and learns there's more to life than making coffee. Join Ish, Pip, Big Bad Bev, and the rest of the Lois McKendrick's crew as they sail the galaxy in search of profitable trade.For more...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Rebels of the Red Planet]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/rebels-of-the-red-planet/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Rebels of the Red Planet - A free audiobook by Charles L. Fontenay]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/rebels-of-the-red-planet/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Rebels of the Red Planet by Charles L. Fontenay</h1><p>First published by Ace Books in 1961.This reading is from the text available through the Project Gutenberg.MARS FOR THE MARTIANS!Dark Kensington had been dead for twenty-five years. It was a fact; everyone knew it. Then suddenly he reappeared, youthful, brilliant, ready to take over the Phoenix, the rebel group that worked to overthrow the tyranny that gripped the settlers on Mars.The Phoenix had been destroyed not once, not twice, but three times! But this time the...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Regenis 4 Chronicles (Book 1)]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/regenis-4-chronicles/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Regenis 4 Chronicles (Book 1) - A free audiobook by Steve Simons]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/regenis-4-chronicles/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Regenis 4 Chronicles (Book 1) by Steve Simons</h1><p>This book is the story of two young men, well they are not exactly boys being 16 and 18.  They make a discovery, that seems to indicate a plot to do serious harm, but harm to whom and by who? There is not a lot to go on.  Just as they are deep into their research their father discovers what they are up to and surprisingly volunteers his services to help out with their investigation, but then he disappears.  Where did he go, when he left home and is he still alive?  Can a 16 and 18 year old...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Regenis 4 Chronicles Book 2 - The Invisible Foe]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/regenis-4-chronicles-2/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Regenis 4 Chronicles Book 2 - The Invisible Foe - A free audiobook by Steve Simons]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/regenis-4-chronicles-2/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Regenis 4 Chronicles Book 2 - The Invisible Foe by Steve Simons</h1><p>Space craft start disappearing, but the authorities can't figure out why, who or what is behind this. There is much fear in the Glaceons family, especially as the eldest son is now a qualified interstellar pilot and regularly traveling through space. Ed and Paul are once again thrown into the thick of things, what is it with these two and disappearances, last time it was their dad. Can they solve the mystery and even more important can they save the lives of those who disappeared along with...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Roadworks]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/roadworks/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Roadworks - A free audiobook by Gerard Readett]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/roadworks/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Roadworks by Gerard Readett</h1><p>Traffic Jam Buster! Come to Brussels, a congestion-free city in 2022, but avoid the day of 'Roadworks', when Akila Kama, an African terrorist takes the city and many foreign heads of state hostage. His demands are simple, either the greatest humanitarian aid package is sent to Africa by the nations of the West, or their leaders die.In a city where all rail, road and underground traffic is computerised, Hugh Ryan, a Transport Authority controller, realises that while all traffic inside the...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Self Made]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/self-made/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Self Made - A free audiobook by M. Darusha Wehm]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/self-made/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Self Made by M. Darusha Wehm</h1><p>Ever wish things were different?Ivy Velasquez did, so she became someone else. In the 3D virtual world Marionette City, you can be anything you want  but everyone still knows who you are. Driven by her desire for a new life, Ivy takes her future in her hands when she makes another identity for herself. A brilliant designer, Ivy works for one of the huge firms which control the online system the world relies upon for both business and pleasure. But one day, Ivy discovers that her...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Singularity]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/singularity/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Singularity - A free audiobook by Bill DeSmedt]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/singularity/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Singularity by Bill DeSmedt</h1><p><a href='http://parsecawards.com/2007Finalists' target='_blank'><img src='http://farm2.static.flickr.com/1398/1224364836_1d5a4b70ac_o.gif' width='80' height='99' alt='Parsec-Seal-2007-Nominee' align='right' hspace='5' /></a><b>What if</b> the cataclysmic Tunguska explosion of 1908 was caused, not by a meteor or a comet, but by a microscopic black hole?<b>What if</b>  that fantastic object - smaller than an atom, older than the stars, heavier than a mountain - is still down there,...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Sonic Fiction]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/sonic-fiction/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Sonic Fiction - A free audiobook by Jeff Kafer (Editor)]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/sonic-fiction/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Sonic Fiction by Jeff Kafer (Editor)</h1><p>Sonic Fiction features an eclectic mix of authors from a range of ages and backgrounds. This collection of short stories is a true potpourri of genres. From fantasy to noir, to modern-day struggles with relationships, this book spans the gamut of human emotions and experiences, from the ancient past to the far-off future. Featuring works of Science fiction, gritty war tales, murder and intrigue, comedy and farce, this is a book for any fan of short fiction. Let us tell you a story!...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[South Coast]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/south-coast/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[South Coast - A free audiobook by Nathan Lowell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/south-coast/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>South Coast by Nathan Lowell</h1><p>A Shaman's Tale from the Golden Age of the Solar Clipper : Volume 1 Otto is Richard Krugg's only son and heir to the Shaman's gift. The only problem is Otto doesn't want it. He wants to be a fisherman. When company policies force unwelcome changes onto his life and threaten even the security of the village, Otto discovers that being a shaman isn't optional.Jimmy Pirano is caught between the devil and the deep green sea when new production quotas are handed down from corporate...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Space Casey]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/space-casey/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Space Casey - A free audiobook by Christiana Ellis]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/space-casey/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Space Casey by Christiana Ellis</h1><p><a href='http://www.podiobooks.com/blog/2008/12/30/2008-founders-choice-awards/'><img src='http://farm5.static.flickr.com/4030/4285895645_98147f8aee_o.gif' align='right' hspace='10' vspace='10' /></a><a href='http://www.greatnorthernaudio.com/MarkTime/MarkTime-winners.html' target='_blank'><img src='http://lh6.ggpht.com/thisisevo/SGBCWBkBRzI/AAAAAAAAABs/H_tr4-MNV4Y/s144/MarkTime-logo.gif'   width='120' hspace='10' vspace='10' align='right' border=0/></a>Some heroines will steal your...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Sparkling Death]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/sparkling-death/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Sparkling Death - A free audiobook by Mark Butler]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/sparkling-death/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Sparkling Death by Mark Butler</h1><p>Mankind has conquered the stars, spreading out to populate the galaxy. Despite technological advancements the human desire for greed and profit at the expense of others still remains. What is the secret on Altruis 4? It is a secret that keeps its people in virtual slavery, a secret that millions will die for.Vance Slater and his team careen from the shark-infested depths of Ligos to the pleasure palaces of Nuvo and into the limitless depths of space in an effort to find an answer. As the...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Spherical Tomi: A Novel of Despair]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/spherical-tomi-a-novel-of-despair/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Spherical Tomi: A Novel of Despair - A free audiobook by Jack Mangan]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/spherical-tomi-a-novel-of-despair/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Spherical Tomi: A Novel of Despair by Jack Mangan</h1><p>  'Star Wars is over.  Star Trek is dead.  In Spherical Tomi, Jack Mangan has opened up a new frontier.'- Ernest Hogan, author of Smoking Mirror BluesA top-secret AI project.A deadly power struggle between warlords.Tomi was once lead combat programmer for the Shogun Ryogi, on the front lines of his conflict against President William the Black of Cerberus. When she failed to prevent William from killing the samurai she loved, she abandoned all sides, all loyalties, all hope. In...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Star Surgeon]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/star-surgeon/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Star Surgeon - A free audiobook by Alan E. Nourse]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/star-surgeon/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Star Surgeon by Alan E. Nourse</h1><p>Dal Timgar always wanted to be a doctor.  As a Garvian and the first non-human to study medicine on Hospital Earth, he must face enormous adversity from classmates, professors, and some of the highest ranking physicians on all of Earth.  Will his efforts be enough to earn him the Silver Star of a Star Surgeon.<u>Star Surgeon</u> is the 1959 novel by <a href='http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alan_E._Nourse' target='_new'>Alan E. Nourse</a> (1928-1992) and is currently <a...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Taken Liberty - A Tale from the Arbiter Chronicles]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/taken-liberty---a-tale-from-the-arbiter-chronicles/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Taken Liberty - A Tale from the Arbiter Chronicles - A free audiobook by Steven H. Wilson]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/taken-liberty---a-tale-from-the-arbiter-chronicles/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Taken Liberty - A Tale from the Arbiter Chronicles by Steven H. Wilson</h1><p><a href='http://parsecawards.com/2007Finalists' target='_blank'><img src='http://farm2.static.flickr.com/1398/1224364836_1d5a4b70ac_o.gif' width='80' height='99' alt='Parsec-Seal-2007-Nominee' align='right' hspace='5' /></a>Aer'La only wants to be free...The Confederated Worlds are unparalleled as a society of free people, yet, somehow, slavery still manages to exist. Aer'La, a non-human, was bred to serve as a pleasure slave. Years ago, she escaped her masters and masqueraded as a...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Tannis Island]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/tannis-island/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Tannis Island - A free audiobook by Gavin L. Lowe]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/tannis-island/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Tannis Island by Gavin L. Lowe</h1><p>Debra Karin Hillgrave is faced with a dilemma; she has first hand experienced an epic discovery, and one greater than any other in mans history, but something has gone very wrong. The world of man is now in grave danger. Debra is not a skilled writer, and she knows it, but she must tell her story to the world. Her tale is hap-hazard, and confusing at first, but she knows this story may save the world from destruction, or possibly it will guarantee it.  Debra must reveal everything in her...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Arwen]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-arwen/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Arwen - A free audiobook by Timothy Callahan]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-arwen/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Arwen by Timothy Callahan</h1><p><a href='http://parsecawards.com/node/234' target='_blank'><img src='http://farm2.static.flickr.com/1361/1330033199_79dc70a26b_o.gif' width='99' alt='Parsec-Seal-2007-Winner' align='right' hspace='5' /></a>When a comet the size of a small moon threatens the remote world of Regal the Earth Alliance assigns the most decorated ship in the fleet, the Arwen, to destroy it.   Its Captain, Marjorie Cook, sees this as an opportunity to redeem herself after a tragic mistake in her past causes the...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Arwen, Season 2: Ulliam]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/arwen-2/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Arwen, Season 2: Ulliam - A free audiobook by Tim Callahan]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/arwen-2/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Arwen, Season 2: Ulliam by Tim Callahan</h1><p>The Gyssyc ship is in orbit above Ulliam; the Taskforce sent to meet them has been destroyed.  Captain Cook fears the worst, the Gyssyc has declared war on the Ulliam.  The crew of the Arwen must figure out what happened before a second fleet arrives, the fate of three races rests in their hands.The Arwen Season 2: Ulliam is the sequel to th Parsec award winning novella The Arwen Season 1: Regal.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Arwen, Season 3: Armada]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/arwen-3/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Arwen, Season 3: Armada - A free audiobook by Timothy Callahan]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/arwen-3/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Arwen, Season 3: Armada by Timothy Callahan</h1><p>The Earth Alliance prepares itself for a new war.  Two old enemy's have allied themselves with Regal, the planet the Arwen saved two years earlier, to build a massive Armada assigned to destroy Earth. Vice Admiral Payton Cook must defend the planet against insurmountable odds while Captain Cook does battle to save Ulliam from a deadly surprise attack.The Arwen: Season 3 is the final chapter of the Gyssyc trilogy which started with the Parsec award winning novella, the Arwen: Season one...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Chameleon Chronicles: Colors of Fate]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-chameleon-chronicles/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Chameleon Chronicles: Colors of Fate - A free audiobook by Andrew S. Leiter]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-chameleon-chronicles/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Chameleon Chronicles: Colors of Fate by Andrew S. Leiter</h1><p>Andrew Webbur's journey of Fate begins when he is confronted by his long time nemesis, Jason Vanzant.  Jason accuses Andrew of stealing his girlfriend and confronts him with violent repercussions.Mr. Spieker, the principal of Calumet Bay High, also seems to be on the warpath with Andrew in his sights.  Neither Mr. Spieker nor Jason Vanzant compare to the butterflies in Andrew's stomach, as he wrestles with his feelings for Bethany Mogg.As if Andrew didn't have enough problems, he...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Chameleon Chronicles: Prisoner of Time]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-chameleon-chronicles-prisoner-of-time/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Chameleon Chronicles: Prisoner of Time - A free audiobook by Andrew S. Leiter]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-chameleon-chronicles-prisoner-of-time/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Chameleon Chronicles: Prisoner of Time by Andrew S. Leiter</h1><p>Andrew Webbur and his friends must serve their Saturday detention the day after the big homecoming dance.  Intent on finding Brians parents, Andrew and Brian must sneak out of school without Mr. Spieker discovering their absence.  The Chameleon discovers more than he bargained for when he finds a hidden island full of powerful Izmite terrorists.Jodi Webburs powers began failing, when reality begins crumbling around her and she cant decipher if she is living in the past, present, or...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Colorado Sequence]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-colorado-sequence/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Colorado Sequence - A free audiobook by Stacey Cochran, narrated by Owen Daly]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-colorado-sequence/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Colorado Sequence by Stacey Cochran, narrated by Owen Daly</h1><p>Physicist Dr. Amy Levine has discovered a mathematical sequence--the Colorado Sequence--that describes an underlying pattern and a guiding force within the very fabric of reality. Now she's on the verge of an astonishing breakthrough, and the U.S. government wants to know how she has done it. How has Dr. Levine learned to accurately predict the future? And they're willing to kill her to find out. Levine and a group of friends escape to Colorado to unravel the mystery of the sequence, but...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Crypt Book 01: The Crew]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-crypt-01/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Crypt Book 01: The Crew - A free audiobook by Scott Sigler]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-crypt-01/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Crypt Book 01: The Crew by Scott Sigler</h1><p>A far-future military/scifi endeavor from New York Times best-selling author Scott Sigler. It is the best-kept and worst-kept secret in the Planetary Union navy. The PUV James Keeling, a warship that does things that no other ship can do. It is a weapon, and a liability. The rumor is that eighty percent of the people assigned to the Keeling die before their two-year stint is up. That rumor is the reason for the ship's nickname -- The Crypt, a vessel full of the dead.Those with a...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Failed Cities Monologues]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-failed-cities-monologues/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Failed Cities Monologues - A free audiobook by Matt Wallace]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-failed-cities-monologues/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Failed Cities Monologues by Matt Wallace</h1><p><a href='http://parsecawards.com/2007Finalists' target='_blank'><img src='http://farm2.static.flickr.com/1398/1224364836_1d5a4b70ac_o.gif' width='80' height='99' alt='Parsec-Seal-2007-Nominee' align='right' hspace='5' /></a>In a hardboiled dystopian future, one major American city has been divided in two. Separated by much more than a river, one side is an unfinished technological marvel populated by mega-skyscrapers where the wealthy live, work, and play. The other is a forsaken...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The HeavenField - Book One]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-heavenfield-1/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The HeavenField - Book One - A free audiobook by Ian G Hulme]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-heavenfield-1/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The HeavenField - Book One by Ian G Hulme</h1><p><a href='http://www.podiobooks.com/blog/2010/01/05/2009-founders-choice-awards/'><img src='http://farm5.static.flickr.com/4026/4249613583_1c731dc0dd_o.gif' align='right' hspace='10' vspace='10' /></a>...The world has changed forever; we have opened the door to something which we dont understand, and that door cannot be closed. I only hope we can change with the world. The man had a fevered stare, and Thomas found himself mesmerised by his words, obscure as they were.The man suddenly...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The HeavenField - Book Two]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-heavenfield-2/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The HeavenField - Book Two - A free audiobook by I G Hulme]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-heavenfield-2/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The HeavenField - Book Two by I G Hulme</h1><p>The Second installment of The HeavenField novel - a fast-paced science-fiction thriller set within a British experimental Scientific Research Facility....The world has changed forever; we have opened the door to something which we dont understand, and that door cannot be closed. I only hope we can change with the world. The man had a fevered stare, and Thomas found himself mesmerised by his words, obscure as they were.The man suddenly stiffened, as if hearing a distant noise, then...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Immortals]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-immortals/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Immortals - A free audiobook by Tracy Hickman]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-immortals/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Immortals by Tracy Hickman</h1><p><a href='http://parsecawards.com/node/234' target='_blank'><img src='http://farm2.static.flickr.com/1361/1330033199_79dc70a26b_o.gif' width='99' alt='Parsec-Seal-2007-Winner' align='right' hspace='5' /></a><b>Podiobooks.com in association with <a href='http://www.dragonhearthproductions.com/'>Dragonhearth Productions</a>, presents New York Times Best Selling Author Tracy Hickman's cautionary tale... The Immortals.</b>The future story of United States Internment Camps ... of the dreams...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Jovian Gate Chronicles]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/jovian-gate-chronicles/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Jovian Gate Chronicles - A free audiobook by Ron Vitale]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/jovian-gate-chronicles/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Jovian Gate Chronicles by Ron Vitale</h1><p>What happens when humans, ruled by the Catholic Church and the Confederacy, cross paths with intelligent aliens that claim to be prophets from God? Find out in this short science fiction short story series that consists of four episodes (total length of the collection is 142 minutes) that tell individual stories of the Jovian Gate. Partake on a journey to learn who opened the gate, question whether aliens truly are communicating with God and learn what humanity's ultimate destiny will be.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Lamp Post Motel]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/lamp-post-motel/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Lamp Post Motel - A free audiobook by Joe Gold]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/lamp-post-motel/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Lamp Post Motel by Joe Gold</h1><p>Are UFOs graduate students from the future, researching their past?Students from the University of the Rings are doing field research in sexual anthropologyat the Lamp Post Motel.Elmo Skinner prefers logical circuits to unpredictable people. He owns the motel and watches his customers on hidden camerasuntil the time travelers drop Elmo's mind into the people he's watching.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Pirates of Sufiro]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-pirates-of-sufiro/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Pirates of Sufiro - A free audiobook by David Lee Summers]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-pirates-of-sufiro/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Pirates of Sufiro by David Lee Summers</h1><p>The story of a planet and its people -- of Ellison Firebrandt the pirate captain living in exile; of Espedie Raton, the con-man looking to make a fresh start for himself and his wife on a new world; of Peter Stone, the ruthless bank executive who discovers a fortune and will do anything to keep it; and of the lawman, Edmund Ray Swan who travels to Sufiro seeking the quiet life but finds a dark secret.  It is the story of privateers, farmers, miners, entrepreneurs, and soldiers -- all caught...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Plitone Revisionist]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-plitone-revisionist/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Plitone Revisionist - A free audiobook by Paul S. Jenkins]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-plitone-revisionist/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Plitone Revisionist by Paul S. Jenkins</h1><p>Will Captain Paola Mackie, independent space courier, thrown out of  her home ten years previously, escape the unsavory clutches of the  man who thinks she can lead him to the notorious Revisionist  mothership secretly orbiting within the Lutrana system and plotting  to destabilize its economy, its culture, its very way of life?Will Paola be reconciled with her estranged and aged father before  it's too late for him to pass on his onerous legacy to her? And will  she finally get it...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Rookie: Remastered MATURE AUDIENCES Edition]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-rookie/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Rookie: Remastered MATURE AUDIENCES Edition - A free audiobook by Scott Sigler]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-rookie/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Rookie: Remastered MATURE AUDIENCES Edition by Scott Sigler</h1><p><a href='http://parsecawards.com/2007Finalists'><img src='http://farm2.static.flickr.com/1398/1224364836_1d5a4b70ac_o.gif' hspace='10' vspace='10' align='right'/></a>Scott Sigler's thrilling novel which combines intense football action, space opera, and the criminal underworld has now been professionally remastered. This engaging story is most often described as a hybrid of Star Wars, The Godfather, and Any Given Sunday.The Rookie is set amongst a lethal pro football league 700 years in...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book One: Invasion ]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/secret-world-chronicle-book-one/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book One: Invasion  - A free audiobook by Mercedes Lackey and Steve Libbey]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/secret-world-chronicle-book-one/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Secret World Chronicle, Book One: Invasion  by Mercedes Lackey and Steve Libbey</h1><p>Emerging mysteriously during World War II, metahumans became icons of the best - and worst - humanity had to offer. Yet sixty years later, the world still suffers from war, greed and madness. Worse, man's nadir of systematic cruelty returns with bizarre new weapons. The metahumans of Earth must find a way to defeat this powerful foe and discover what lurks behind the scenes - a secret world hidden from our own. Mercedes Lackey, one of fantasy's most beloved voices, and new talent Steve Libbey...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book Three: World Well Lost]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-secret-world-chronicle-book-three-world-well-lost/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book Three: World Well Lost - A free audiobook by Mercedes Lackey]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-secret-world-chronicle-book-three-world-well-lost/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Secret World Chronicle, Book Three: World Well Lost by Mercedes Lackey</h1><p>Continuing the action and intrigue of the first two books, World Well Lost joins the ensemble cast of metahuman characters as they struggle against the growing powers of the Thule Society as well as Echo's own waning popularity. Famed fantasy and sci-fi author Mercedes Lackey and newcomers Dennis Lee and Cody Martin bring this superhero-themed braided novel podcast series to life with characters such as the Seraphym, Victoria Victrix, John Murdock, and Red Djinni, with stories read by...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book Two: The Hunt]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/secret-world-chronicle-book-two/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book Two: The Hunt - A free audiobook by Mercedes Lackey and Steve Libbey]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/secret-world-chronicle-book-two/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Secret World Chronicle, Book Two: The Hunt by Mercedes Lackey and Steve Libbey</h1><p>The Hunt portrays the frenzied aftermath of the devastating Thule Society attacks. Famed fantasy and sci-fi author Mercedes Lackey and newcomer Steve Libbey have joined forces to create a superhero-themed braided novel podcast series called The Secret World Chronicle. The series depicts an ensemble cast of metahuman characters coping with worldwide attacks by a mysterious, technologically advanced Nazi secret society, and the ensuing chaos.  The Secret World is a meeting ground for pulpy...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Silk Code]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-silk-code/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Silk Code - A free audiobook by Paul Levinson]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-silk-code/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Silk Code by Paul Levinson</h1><p>Phil D'Amato, New York City forensic detective, is caught in an ongoing struggle that dates all the way back to the dawn of humanity on earth--and one of his best friends is a recent casualty. Unless Phil can unravel the genetic puzzle of the Silk Code, he'll soon be just as dead.Praise for The Silk Code:'Forensic detective Phil D'Amato is one of my favorite characters, and the puzzles he solves are always imaginative, ingenious, and addictive, but Paul Levinson really outdoes himself...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Sphere Of Time]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-sphere-of-time/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Sphere Of Time - A free audiobook by Steve Simons]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-sphere-of-time/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Sphere Of Time by Steve Simons</h1><p>This is a science fiction story that is suitable for children and adults alike. It tells the story of John Latham a scientist and Engineer, who thinks he has found a way to travel through time, space or even another dimension. However, he is not sure unless he can test out his ideas. John is lucky enough to come across a wealthy man who puts up the money to try out John's idea. But the crux of this book is, if he succeeds in getting there, wherever there actually is, what will he find when he...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Sphere Of Travel (TSOT2)]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-sphere-of-travel/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Sphere Of Travel (TSOT2) - A free audiobook by Steve Simons]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-sphere-of-travel/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Sphere Of Travel (TSOT2) by Steve Simons</h1><p>This story is rated 12 as there is a romantic theme and also death, but nothing explicit, it's still a clean story.We find the team of David and John set to  adventure out again. This time in an improved sphere and both of them are going to travel together.  A new member is introduced to the team, Debbie Gill.  Debbie takes over David's role, predicting the location of the black holes.The trip does not go according to plan, but oh no,don't look to me to spill the beans as to what...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Worldwrights]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-worldwrights/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Worldwrights - A free audiobook by Max Grant]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/the-worldwrights/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Worldwrights by Max Grant</h1><p>Kalukan awakens from millenia of cold sleep to find his companions dead. He has been charged by the long-dead Worldwrights to protect their creation from its out-of-control Overseer.As Kalukan prepares for his final quest against the Overseer, now named the Ghala, he begins to learn that the World's purpose is not that which he was taught. With a frayed sense of faith in his purpose, Kalukan sets out to reach the inexplicable construction known as the Skylock, where history tells him a...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Theme and Variations]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/theme-and-variations/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Theme and Variations - A free audiobook by Michelle M. Welch, editor]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/theme-and-variations/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Theme and Variations by Michelle M. Welch, editor</h1><p>A podcast anthology of speculative fiction with music as a theme.  Science fiction, fantasy, and slipstream tales include stories of a future world where music has been lost, office workers whose embedded soundtracks direct their lives, the Martian superstar who doesn't want to play anymore, singers who can compel men to kill with the sound of their voices, and more.The eight episodes present short stories by Keyan Bowes, Ernest Hogan, Elaine Isaak, Lejon A. Johnson, Jack Mangan, Rick...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Time Crime]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/time-crime/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Time Crime - A free audiobook by H. Beam Piper]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/time-crime/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Time Crime by H. Beam Piper</h1><p>From Astounding Tales Published February and March 1955The Paratime Police had a real headache this time! Tracing one man in a population of millions is easycompared to finding one gang hiding out on one of billions of probability lines!This story from 1955 has rocket ships, time travel, slaves, post-hypnotic suggestions, drugged citizens, and a complete disregard for human rights. And those are the good guys. As a look back in time at 'classic' science fiction, it's an interesting...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Time Crystal]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/time-crystal/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Time Crystal - A free audiobook by Wyken Seagrave]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/time-crystal/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Time Crystal by Wyken Seagrave</h1><p>The cosmic monopole has been wandering the Universe since the Big Bang. When it is finally trapped in CERN it triggers a disaster which will take fourteen-year-old Catriona OBrien on an adventure back to the Big Bang and beyond in a desperate attempt to save the Universe from destruction.Encompassing the whole history of the Universe and most branches of science, Time Crystal is an epic adventure story and romance that will hold you enthralled and show you new worlds both great and small...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Time Crystal 2]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/time-crystal-2/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Time Crystal 2 - A free audiobook by Wyken Seagrave]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/time-crystal-2/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Time Crystal 2 by Wyken Seagrave</h1><p>The story so far: When Irish school teacher Sam Fitzpatrick and CERN scientist Michael Zhang are absorbed by a black hole, they find themselves outside the Universe on a planet populated by gigantic insect-like Entroilians and Argolaths. The Universe is merely part of their elaborate lifecycle. Michael breaks the crystal machinery surrounding it and fragments fall into the Universe where time stops everywhere except near these crystals. Sam can talk to people who hold crystal, and the...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Time Zone]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/time-zone/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Time Zone - A free audiobook by Tom Lichtenberg]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/time-zone/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Time Zone by Tom Lichtenberg</h1><p>This is not your father's time travel. There's no machine, there is no dial. There's no telling where or when you'll go. The only thing that can change is you. It will make you what it needs to make you, to fit you in, to make it work. And when you come back, that is if you come back, it won't be the same you at all. You're messing with the nature of things, and the nature of things does not like to be messed with, as Garrett Ronson and his friends find out, the hard way.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Traitor, Book 1 of The Turner Chronicles]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/traitor/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Traitor, Book 1 of The Turner Chronicles - A free audiobook by Mark Eller]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/traitor/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Traitor, Book 1 of The Turner Chronicles by Mark Eller</h1><p>Last Chance - a small town set on the edge of the far frontier. It is a place of gentle manners and common civility. After all, it should be since more than three quarters of its residents are women. However times change when a Talent Master runs rampant, savages threaten war, and an illegal militia from an alternate universe plans invasion and empire. A hero is needed. A Savior. Meet Aaron Turner, the small unassuming man who runs the Last Chance General Store. He is this town's--this...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Tumbler]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/tumbler/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Tumbler - A free audiobook by Brand Gamblin]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/tumbler/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Tumbler by Brand Gamblin</h1><p>Libby Carter wanted to get away from it all, so she took a job mining asteroids as far out into the inky blackness as possible. However, her escape turned into a trap, leaving her stuck in indentured servitude, living on a tiny rock in space. As she tries to dig herself out, she gains friends and finds adventure. Cave-in rescues, planetary collisions, and other mishaps keep her new family fighting to stay alive.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Untrue Tales... Book One]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/UTFBFRoaAP1/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Untrue Tales... Book One - A free audiobook by Teel McClanahan III]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/UTFBFRoaAP1/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Untrue Tales... Book One by Teel McClanahan III</h1><p>FULL TITLE: Untrue Tales From Beyond Fiction - Recollections of an Alternate Past, Book One:An Introduction to Dodgeball -or- Conception and Induction -or- How To Begin An Apocalypse -- Contains mature content not suitable for all readers. Book One is the introduction to this series of books which take place in a world where magic and psychic-like powers exist but are overlooked by most people, and centers on a teenage boy of remarkable magical and mental powers as he is introduced to a...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Untrue Tales... Book Three]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/UTFBFRoaAP3/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Untrue Tales... Book Three - A free audiobook by Teel McClanahan III]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/UTFBFRoaAP3/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Untrue Tales... Book Three by Teel McClanahan III</h1><p>FULL TITLE: Untrue Tales From Beyond Fiction - Recollections of an Alternate Past, Book Three: Escape From Exile -or- Confusion and Contraction -or- How To Get Out Of Hell. -- Contains mature content not suitable for all readers. Book Three picks up from the same instant that Book Two left off: in Hell. It is primarily concerned with the boy's attempts to free his companions from eternal damnation, but has a few twists and turns that will leave you wondering what really happened. This is the...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Untrue Tales... Book Two]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/UTFBFRoaAP2/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Untrue Tales... Book Two - A free audiobook by Teel McClanahan III]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/UTFBFRoaAP2/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Untrue Tales... Book Two by Teel McClanahan III</h1><p>FULL TITLE: Untrue Tales From Beyond Fiction - Recollections of an Alternate Past, Book Two:The Twofold Invasion -or- Penetration and Destruction -or- How To Make Love With Twins -- Contains mature content not suitable for all readers. Book Two continues the boys story from a few months after where Book One leaves off, primarily following his quest to save the life of his unborn child as he finds himself further and further from the life he knew before.  This is the second book of the...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[V and A Shipping]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/v-and-a-shipping/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[V and A Shipping - A free audiobook by J.R. Murdock]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/v-and-a-shipping/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>V and A Shipping by J.R. Murdock</h1><p>Vic and Argmon are just trying to make a simple delivery, albeit while being chased by the local fuzz. They pick up an unexpected stowaway on their planet to planet run.Joey, the unwitting stowaway, is thrust into space and must deal with not only being in space, but with all the alien creatures aboard the SS Acid Rat.Once the delivery is complete, Vic, Argmon, and their new crewmate Joey, are offered a double or nothing gamble to pick up a second delivey for the celebration party....</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Vatican Abdicator]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/vatican-abdicator/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Vatican Abdicator - A free audiobook by Mike Luoma]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/vatican-abdicator/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Vatican Abdicator by Mike Luoma</h1><p>This is it! The SHOCKING CONCLUSION to the VATICAN ASSASSIN TRILOGY! Bernard Campion, 'BC', has been an Assassin for the Pope - The Vatican's Ambassador to Lunar Prime - CEO of The Project - Head of the UTZ Council - and now he's the Pope of the New catholic Church, the NcC. But the mantle sits uneasily on BC. The Universal Trade Zone (UTZ) and The Universal Islamic Nation (UIN) are now forced to work together in the face of dual threats: The alien race, The Eldred and the recently revived...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Vatican Ambassador]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/vatican-ambassador/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Vatican Ambassador - A free audiobook by Mike Luoma]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/vatican-ambassador/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Vatican Ambassador by Mike Luoma</h1><p>This is the second book in a series. Start with Vatican Assassin, also available on our website.BERNARD CAMPION has killed for the Pope as an agent of the Office of Papal Operations, the OPO. But the old pope is dead, and Pope Linus the Second is no friend of the OPO! The adventures of Bernard Campion, the Vatican Assassin, continue. BC has helped Governor Marc Edwards rebuild Lunar Prime, but can he help build peace between The Universal Islamic Nation (UIN), The Universal Trade Zone...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Vatican Assassin (orginal)]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/vatican-assassin/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Vatican Assassin (orginal) - A free audiobook by Mike Luoma]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/vatican-assassin/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Vatican Assassin (orginal) by Mike Luoma</h1><p>BERNARD CAMPION'S friends call him 'BC'. Not that he has a lot of friends. You don't make a lot of friends when you're an assassin. His mission: eliminate the governor of Luna Prime, Meredith McEntyre. His bosses, The Office of Papal Operations: The OPO, tell him she's been sympathizing with the enemy, the Universal Islamic Nation (UIN). His boss? BC works for the Pope. It's 2109, a time of war. BC is 'officially' assigned as PR man to the Vatican Mission on Luna Prime, the major city on The...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Vatican Assassin - Remastered]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/vatican-assassin-remastered/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Vatican Assassin - Remastered - A free audiobook by Mike Luoma]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/vatican-assassin-remastered/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Vatican Assassin - Remastered by Mike Luoma</h1><p>The First Book of The Vatican Assassin Science Fiction Trilogy. Remastered in July 2009.Bernard Campion, aka 'BC', is an assassin for the Pope, struggling with his work's inherent contradictions while trying to take care of business during  an out of control interplanetary religious war in 2109. BC is a killer disguised as a priest of the New catholic Church. His current assignment? Eliminate the Governor of Lunar Prime, the free state on the Moon. BC has no idea this latest assignment...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Voices: New Media Fiction]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/voices-new-media-fiction/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Voices: New Media Fiction - A free audiobook by Mur Lafferty (editor)]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com//title/voices-new-media-fiction/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Voices: New Media Fiction by Mur Lafferty (editor)</h1><p><a href='http://parsecawards.com' target='_blank'><img class='donation' src='http://www.podiobooks.com/images/parsec120part.gif'  width='120' height='80' hspace=10 vspace=10 align=right border=0/></a>Voices: New Media Fiction brings together the pioneer short fiction podcasters. Experimenting from putting short-short fiction to novellas over their podcasts, these writers were the first to test the new medium for storytelling. Some wrote specifically for podcasts, some read previously...</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
