<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			Thriller&appos;s podcast novels &ndash; prensented by: podiobooks.com
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Acts of Desperation]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/acts-of-desperation/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Acts of Desperation - A free audiobook by Tim Dodge]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/acts-of-desperation/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Acts of Desperation by Tim Dodge</h1><p>Ray Davis is newly divorced, going nowhere at a dead-end job in a warehouse, and has almost worked off the debts his ex-wife rang up. Then his underinsured brother's need for a liver transplant forces Ray to come up with a lot of money, fast. When he attempts to recover the profit he made with an old business partner, Ray discovers that the partner is dead and his investment has fallen into the hands of a drug dealer. The dealer has used the cash to buy a large supply of cocaine; he and his...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Confederate Gold]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/confederate-gold/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Confederate Gold - A free audiobook by George Vassallo]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/confederate-gold/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Confederate Gold by George Vassallo</h1><p>Richard L. Cornwell, a Nashville preacher, is stunned when he hears a deathbed confession from one of his parishioners. The man tells Cornwell an amazing story that reveals the location of the lost gold of the Confederate State of America.  But the gold is only the beginning.  Buried along with it are two priceless Greek statues that will unite ancient Greece and the lost Southern aristocracy.  This will be a dangerous mission.  Fortunately, Cornwell knows one dependable man who is always...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Corporate Warfare]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/corporate-warfare/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Corporate Warfare - A free audiobook by Kris Davis]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/corporate-warfare/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Corporate Warfare by Kris Davis</h1><p>Romance underlines Corporate Warfare  a fast paced novel that deals with corporations bidding on a US proposal. A scheming foreign conglomerate has other intentions. With their international genetic patents secured, Project Abacus' success now hinges on the exploitation of the proposal to realize a unique human identification system. A genetic social security number. And corporate espionage entangles the love triangles. But with Anthony's hands tied will fate prevail?</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Heart Of Diamonds]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/heart-of-diamonds/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Heart Of Diamonds - A free audiobook by Dave Donelson]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/heart-of-diamonds/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Heart Of Diamonds by Dave Donelson</h1><p>Corruption at the highest levels of government, greed in the church, and brutality among warring factions make the Congo a very dangerous place for television journalist Valerie Grey.  Amid the bloody violence of that country's endless civil war, Grey uncovers a deadly diamond-smuggling scheme that reaches from the heart of the Congo to the White House by way of a famous American televangelist.  Aided by an altruistic doctor, Grey is pursued by the soldiers of the country's dictator, the...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[New World Orders]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/new-world-orders/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[New World Orders - A free audiobook by Edward G. Talbot]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/new-world-orders/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>New World Orders by Edward G. Talbot</h1><p>In the nineteen-sixties, a group of wealthy men concludes that it's already too late to stop global warming from destroying the planet. But they have a plan to save themselves.Twenty years later, Jack Crowley and Jim Patterson stumble onto the conspiracy, and every answer they find is accompanied by more questions - and more deaths.Jack is a former idealist, turned cynical by his years working as a New York tabloid editor. But his enthusiasm returns as he looks into the work of a NASA...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[One Fall]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/one-fall/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[One Fall - A free audiobook by Spencer Baum]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/one-fall/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>One Fall by Spencer Baum</h1><p>With one kick, Joey Hamilton has sent the world of professional wrestling into chaos. In his first World Title match, on national television, Joey botched a simple maneuver, turning a scripted wrestling match into a nightmarish reality.Now the World Champion is injured and the locker room is in tatters. With the top spot open, veteran wrestlers are jockeying for position, hoping to become the next megastar, and Joey is their target.With a unique look behind the scenes at America's...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Personal Effects: Sword of Blood]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/personal-effects-sword-of-blood/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Personal Effects: Sword of Blood - A free audiobook by J.C. Hutchins]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/personal-effects-sword-of-blood/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Personal Effects: Sword of Blood by J.C. Hutchins</h1><p><a href='http://www.podiobooks.com/blog/2010/01/05/2009-founders-choice-awards/'><img src='http://farm5.static.flickr.com/4026/4249613583_1c731dc0dd_o.gif' align='right' hspace='10' vspace='10' /></a>Brinkvale Psychiatric Hospital art therapist Zach Taylor is endlessly curious, perhaps to a fault. When his cheerful elderly patient Gertrude Spindle Spindler completes her latest quilt and informs Zach that a 30-year-old 'grand design of nine' has just concluded, Zachs curiosity is piqued ......</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The God Conspiracy]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-god-conspiracy/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The God Conspiracy - A free audiobook by Derek Gilbert]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-god-conspiracy/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The God Conspiracy by Derek Gilbert</h1><p>One e-mail. Five lines. 4,000 dead.And it is only just beginningWhen a small boy in Iowa forwards a mysterious email from God to a small group of friends, he unwittingly releases a trigger that sends blood pouring throughout his farming community.Thousands more are dead across the country in dozens of simultaneous terror attacks and the government blames fundamentalists who want to trigger the Apocalypse.FBI Agent Joe Unes reluctantly teams with reclusive Internet radio...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Mariner's Secret, a Matt and Heather Thriller]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-mariners-secret/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Mariner's Secret, a Matt and Heather Thriller - A free audiobook by Mary TomasiDubois]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-mariners-secret/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Mariner's Secret, a Matt and Heather Thriller by Mary TomasiDubois</h1><p>Thugs, chases through the streets of San Francisco, scientific discoveries, and other mysteries abound!Matt and Heather Townsend, orphaned when their bioscientist parents are killed in the 1989 Loma Prieta earthquake, become wards of their Great Aunt Estelle.  Her stately old house in the Marina District holds intrigue, and a secret.  Fortunately, Matt discovers the secret on his thirteenth birthday, and not too soon.  He was about to go stark raving mad with boredom.Years earlier and...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Theft of the Master]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/theft-of-the-master/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Theft of the Master - A free audiobook by Edwin Alexander]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/theft-of-the-master/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Theft of the Master by Edwin Alexander</h1><p>Theft of the Master has been described as the Boys from Brazil meets The Da Vinci Code KirkusPrivate Investigator Al Hershey takes the reader across the globe in his search for a young woman's killer.  Hired by the girl's parents to look into her 'accidental' death Al finds he is in the middle of a more than a murder investigation.Modern day Nazis and a stolen renaissance sculpture all play a part in this intricate character driven tale of promises and deceit.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Virtual Vice - a new technology crime novel  based on true events]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/virtual-vice/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Virtual Vice - a new technology crime novel  based on true events - A free audiobook by Jason M. Kays]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/virtual-vice/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Virtual Vice - a new technology crime novel  based on true events by Jason M. Kays</h1><p>In Virtual Vice by Jason M. Kays, readers follow disillusioned entertainment attorney Ian McKenzie as his professional life takes a decided turn for the questionable when he is hired by the charismatic and dangerous Scott White to represent Scotts interests in his cutting edge Internet startup, Metropoleis Multimedia. Unfortunately for Ian, Scott has more in common with Scarfaces Tony Montana than Apples Steve Jobs, and things go from questionable to deadly in no time flat. As Scotts...</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
