<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			Young Adult&appos;s podcast novels &ndash; prensented by: podiobooks.com
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Amber Page and the Legend of the Coral Stone]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/amber-page-and-the-legend-of-the-coral-stone/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Amber Page and the Legend of the Coral Stone - A free audiobook by Stacey Cochran]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/amber-page-and-the-legend-of-the-coral-stone/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Amber Page and the Legend of the Coral Stone by Stacey Cochran</h1><p>On the island of Maui, a sixteen-year-old international spy named Rio Kayenta discovers a two-thousand-year-old coral stone. Legend has it that the stone is meant for a girl named Amber and that with it, she can stop the evil S.H.R.O.U.D. organization. Amber Page lives in the Arizona desert and wants one thing more than anything else in the world: to see her mom and dad back together again. Amber's mom is a school bus driver who has split with her dad, but Amber believes the two still love...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Dragons' Truth]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/dragons-truth/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Dragons' Truth - A free audiobook by Teel McClanahan III]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/dragons-truth/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Dragons' Truth by Teel McClanahan III</h1><p>When two young boys decide to skip school and seek adventure one day, they end up finding much more than they ever bargained for. More than the dragon and the mountain of riches they see at first, one of the boys finds the entire course of his life changed.That boy, Larry, finds himself at the center of an adventure bigger than anything he'd ever dreamed of. And when Larry's continuing adventure begins to effect his schoolwork, and then his teachers and his entire school, Larry's not sure...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Grizelda]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/grizelda/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Grizelda - A free audiobook by Margaret R. Taylor]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/grizelda/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Grizelda by Margaret R. Taylor</h1><p>In the Republic of Corvain, anybody who has a hint of magical power is rounded up and thrown into prison.  Theyre doing it to defend the new nation, says the revolutionary government  defend it from the sorcerers and sorceresses who used to be the lackeys of the man-eating Auks in the bad old days of the monarcy.  When Grizelda, a young seamstress from the poorer part of the capitol city, suddenly finds herself the governments target, she fears she is done for.But in prison she meets a...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Max Quick 1: The Pocket and the Pendant]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-pocket-and-the-pendant/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Max Quick 1: The Pocket and the Pendant - A free audiobook by Mark Jeffrey]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-pocket-and-the-pendant/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Max Quick 1: The Pocket and the Pendant by Mark Jeffrey</h1><p>WHEN TIME mysteriously stops, young Max Quick must travel across America to find the source of this 'temporal disaster'... Along the way, he and his companions encounter ancient mysteries, quantum Books, and clues to the riddle of stopped Time. But the more Max learns, the more it seems that his own true identity is not what he once believed...'driven -- and driven well -- by good old-fashioned sci-fi storytelling.' - Kirkus Reviews ForeWord Magazine 'Book of the Year' Finalist 2005</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Max Quick 2: The Two Travelers]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-two-travelers/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Max Quick 2: The Two Travelers - A free audiobook by Mark Jeffrey]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-two-travelers/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Max Quick 2: The Two Travelers by Mark Jeffrey</h1><p>Five quiet years have passed in Starland, California since the the time of the Pocket. But when a crazed old man shows up with a warning, Max, Casey, Ian and Sasha suddenly find themselves on the run. Max and Ian go through an Arch back to 1912, where a mysterious Machine is under construction that seems connected to Maxs unremembered secret. Meanwhile, Casey and Sasha follow the old man to the strange town of Arturo Gyp.But there is more afoot than meets the eye: the enemies of Mr. E -...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Noggle Stones]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/noggle-stones/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Noggle Stones - A free audiobook by Wil Radcliffe]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/noggle-stones/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Noggle Stones by Wil Radcliffe</h1><p>Shunned by his people and tormented by nightmare visions, Bugbear, the mad goblin scholar, ventures into the wilderness with his ne'er-do-well cousin, Tudmire, to seek out an ancient ruin and the lost wisdom it holds.Soon the cousins find themselves embroiled in cosmic events as their magical world of Annwfn is merged with 19th Century Earth after an accident concerning a mysterious scroll Tudmire acquires in a crooked game of Noggle Stones. While fleeing the enraged ogres they cheated,...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Round Red Stone]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-round-red-stone/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Round Red Stone - A free audiobook by Jeff Burton]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-round-red-stone/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Round Red Stone by Jeff Burton</h1><p>This tale concerns a lad of twelve, who sets off unwillingly on a journey with his uncle. In the course of his adventures, he obtains a stone, whose ultimate meaning is tied up with the fate of a war between two cities. As commonly happens with boys, he finds himself at the center of the conflict. Can he divine the stones purpose in time? Even more importantly, can he even hang on  to it?The story includes a mystery, long journeys, prisons, adventure, and living out-of-doors.  There is...</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[There's No Such Thing!]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/theres-no-such-thing/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[There's No Such Thing! - A free audiobook by Jeanette Cottrell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/theres-no-such-thing/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>There's No Such Thing! by Jeanette Cottrell</h1><p>Have you been losing things lately? Is your dog chasing his tail, your cell phone acting up, or your best friend acting strangely? Well, I've got news for you. A Wisky Wasky did it! Unfortunately, no one's giving him the recognition he needs. Let me tell you, that is a BIG mistake. Our Wisky Wasky's a very excitable fellow. He calls in a dragon to help him get noticed. But there's a problem with being a Wisky Wasky or a dragon in this technological world:  there's no such thing!</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[T'Aragam: the Max Ransome Chronicles, Book One]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/taragam-book-one/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[T'Aragam: the Max Ransome Chronicles, Book One - A free audiobook by Jack W. Regan]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/taragam-book-one/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>T'Aragam: the Max Ransome Chronicles, Book One by Jack W. Regan</h1><p>Young Max Ransome watched his father die, killed by marauding phantors as they swept through T'Aragam at the bidding of the evil wizard Zadok. Barely escaping with his own life, Max is thrust into a whirlwind journey as he races against time to save T'Aragam, the world he loves, from a dark dominion. Can Max overcome the horror of his father's death and save T'Aragam from the grasping talons of its enemies? Woven with a charming mix of zany humor and genuine danger, 'T'Aragam' immerses the...</p>]]>" />
	</body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Demon Queen and The Locksmith]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-demon-queen-and-the-locksmith/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Demon Queen and The Locksmith - A free audiobook by Spencer Baum]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-demon-queen-and-the-locksmith/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Demon Queen and The Locksmith</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Spencer Baum</h3><p>&quot;Ordinary teens become extraordinary in this thrilling tale of good versus evil...Skillfully written, this novel will captivate teens, including reluctant readers.&quot;  -- Publishers Weekly.The Demon Queen and The Locksmith is a 2010 Amazon Breakthrough Novel Award Semifinalist.Kevin panicked when his ears began to buzz.&nbsp; He couldn&apos;t be a Hearer.&nbsp; The Hearers were the town freaks.&nbsp; Worse, his dad was one of them, and Kevin&apos;s greatest fear was that one day he might turn into his father.In Turquoise, New Mexico, some people believe that the mountain north of town emits a constant, resonant hum that is audible only to a chosen few.&nbsp; They are called Hearers, and fourteen-year-old Kevin Brown has never trusted them.&nbsp; But when a carefree afternoon with his friends comes to a surprise finish at the spot where Kevin spread his mother&apos;s ashes only a year before, a place where the open air seems to resonate in kevin&apos;s ears, he realizes he might be a Hearer too, and &quot;The Turquoise Hum&quot; might be much more than a sound.</p>]]>" />
</opml>
