<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<opml version="1.1">
  <head>
				<title>My Podiobooks Subscriptions</title>
	</head>
  <body>
	<outline title="Podiobooks.com: Fresh Kills by Basil Sands and The Authors of The Killzone Blog" text="Podiobooks.com: Fresh Kills by Basil Sands and The Authors of The Killzone Blog" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/502/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=502" description="Fresh Kills is a podcast collection of original short stories by the authors of &lt;a href=&quot;http://killzoneauthors.blogspot.com&quot;&gt;the popular literary blog The Kill Zone&lt;/a&gt;.Reminiscent of the Twilight Zone, these killer tales vary from the paranormal to the chilling to the just plain scary. Each delivers a finely crafted tale that will keep you clicking through the pages. Contributors to the podcast version include these award winning and best selling authors: John Gilstrap, Michelle Gagnon, James Scott Bell, Kathryn Lilley, John Ramsey Miller, Clare Langley-Hawthorne, Joe Moore and Basil Sands. Originally posted as an ebook at Amazon and Smashwords, the podcast version includes 3 extra stories, not available in print including one by award winning podcast author and narrator Basil Sands.So pop on the ear phones and buckle your seatbelt for a trip to the edge of sanity....it's going to be a wild ride." />
<outline title="Podiobooks.com: The Ballad of Iron Percy by Edward Clark" text="Podiobooks.com: The Ballad of Iron Percy by Edward Clark" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/506/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=506" description="It has been twenty years since the island nation of Great Hale conquered the New World and became an empire. Lord Percival Wilmore, the Hero of Naruna Isle, has been the governor of the New Jucata since the war’s end, and it has been his life’s work to make the colony a peaceful and prosperous part of the Halan Empire. By all accounts, he has succeeded. The city-states of Old Jucata have been dominated utterly, the old religion has been completely supplanted by the Halan faith of the White Veil, and Jucatan goods have made Great Hale the envy of the world. He is beloved by the people, and he has ensured that this Halan colony is built to last.But New Jucata’s future is not as secure as it seems. As the head of state for the colony, Lord Wilmore is the highest legal authority in the land, and he is called upon to try a most curious prisoner. The events and outcome of this interrogation threaten to tear Halan Rule of Law apart and bring anarchy to the region.Pandemona stands accused of being a Pak Shar - a dangerous and seductive demon previously seen only in Veil mythology. With her scarlet skin, lithe tail, and dainty set of horns, she certainly looks the part. Her way with words and alluring demeanor only serve to underscore this perception. Under Halan law, the punishment for being a demon is death by fire at the stake, but Pandemona is entitled to a fair trial by Lord Wilmore and the colony’s Curate before she can be convicted and executed. This interrogation is her only chance to escape. She must use all of her wit and guile to survive.Is Pandemona really what she appears to be? What is she here to accomplish? Is she an evil and subversive creature, sent from the Abyss to torment mankind? Or is she simply disfigured and misunderstood? Whatever the truth may be, her presence is not a good omen.The Ballad of Iron Percy is a song of glorious triumph, written to honor Lord Wilmore’s victory against overwhelming odds in the Conquest War. It is an iconic tune in New Jucata. The specifics of the verses vary in each separate rendition, but the overall tone is one of bravery, achievement, and joy.Unfortunately for Iron Percy, his Ballad is not yet over…" />
<outline title="Podiobooks.com: Dead Hunt by Kenn Crawford" text="Podiobooks.com: Dead Hunt by Kenn Crawford" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/496/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=496" description="Off the coast of Nova Scotia on a remote island, a lonely scientist, a powerful computer, a simple mistake. Unleashes a new threat, somewhere in the hills of Margaree. &quot;Dead Hunt&quot; is Kenn Crawford’s chilling tale of a desperate father’s undying love, a daughter frozen in time, and the small group of teens trapped in the aftermath. &quot;Everyone makes mistakes. Some are small, some are bigger. My father’s mistake, born of an innocent heart and fueled by sadness, was the greatest mistake. Some thought the death of his little girl drove him to the point of insanity; some thought he was trying to be God. But, this is not how it happened. The truth is, he wanted to save me. To give me life. And, in doing so, everyone was doomed.&quot; ~RobinDead Hunt is narrated by R.E. Chambliss (Dreaming of Deliverance), and features the voice talents of: Kimi Alexandre, Brian Brown, Ry Stevenson, Melissa Bartell, Erk and Kim Butler with special guest appearances by Andrew Ball, Arlene Radasky, Judy, Kristopher Lamont, Lindsey Burns, Lisa Tobias, Neil Stringer, Nobilis Reed, Randall Carruthers, Tom Storms and Featuring Rick Stringer of Variant Frequencies as the voice of Professor Patrick Heslin, and introducing “Robin” as herself.&quot;I was positively terrified while reading Dead Hunt.&quot;-Holly Christine, the Pittsburgh Books Examiner&quot;I found Dead Hunt to be an imaginative, enjoyable read with a clever twist at its conclusion.&quot;-Claude Bouchard, Author of Vigilante&quot;Your dialog’s natural and well done.&quot;-Winslow Eliot, Author of The Bright Face of Danger " />
<outline title="Podiobooks.com: Into the Woods by David Wood" text="Podiobooks.com: Into the Woods by David Wood" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/505/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=505" description="Set against the backdrop of colonial America, Into the Woods is the story of pioneer and patriot Jonathan Wood. Straining against the bonds of Tidewater society and tempted by an ancient legent, Jonathan's sense of adventure leads him over the mountains of southwest Virginia. Perils abound for this brave pioneer, who must face threats from the native tribes, the British, and even more sinister enemies, while fighting for the woman he loves, and the land that will not let go of his heart. Based on a true story, Into the Woods is a tale of adventure, danger, love, and the triumph of the human spirit.PRAISE FOR INTO THE WOODS:&quot;David Wood has crafted a gem of a story laced with action, villainy, revenge, and reconciliation. Adventure, loyalty- sometimes strained and split- love and sacrifice resonate within the pages of this historical fiction tale.&quot; Terry W. Ervin II, author of Flank Hawk&quot;Into the Woods is an amazing historical adventure, and a powerful testament to the power of family.&quot; Sean Ellis, author of The Shroud of Heaven&quot;David Wood has written an entertaining historical adventure.&quot; Megalith Book ReviewsPRAISE FOR DAVID WOOD:&quot;Cibola by David Wood is a page-turning yarn blending high action, Biblical speculation, ancient secrets, and nasty creatures. Indiana Jones better watch his back!&quot; Jeremy Robinson, author of Instinct and Beneath&quot;With the thoroughly enjoyable way Mr. Wood has mixed speculative history with our modern day pursuit of truth, he has created a story that thrills and makes one think beyond the boundaries of mere fiction and enter the world of 'why not'?&quot; David Golemon, author of Leviathan and Ancients&quot;Ancient cave paintings? Cities of gold? Secret scrolls? Sign me up! Cibola is a twisty tale of adventure and intrigue that never lets up and never lets go!&quot; Robert Masello, author of Bestiary and Blood and Ice&quot;History is turned on its head in this gripping tale of sects, secrets, and double-crosses. With mesmerizing treasures in beautiful locations, beautiful women and rugged heroes, mysticism and mystery, Wood spins a yarn that keeps the pages turning.&quot; Alan Baxter, author of RealmShift and MageSign" />
<outline title="Podiobooks.com: Dead Mech by Jake Bible" text="Podiobooks.com: Dead Mech by Jake Bible" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/495/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=495" description="After the zombie apocalypse decimates the world, human civilization tries to put itself back together again. Their secret weapon: the Mechs. But what happens when a mech pilot dies in his mech and becomes a zombie? Hell on earth is unleashed..." />
<outline title="Podiobooks.com: Closet Treats by Paul Elard Cooley" text="Podiobooks.com: Closet Treats by Paul Elard Cooley" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/488/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=488" description="Reality is a slippery slope for Trey Leger.  He's managed to carve out a somewhat normal existence in spite of his mental illness.  But when an ice cream truck starts making the rounds of his neighborhood, Trey can no longer tell reality from his delusions." />
<outline title="Podiobooks.com: Dreaming of Deliverance by R.E. Chambliss " text="Podiobooks.com: Dreaming of Deliverance by R.E. Chambliss " type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/448/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=448" description="Five years ago when Lindsay Paulson, a naive college student and talented distance runner, was 18, she was convicted of drug smuggling. Now, halfway through a 10-year prison sentence, she begins having what seem to be dreams, in which she leaves her cell in the night and visits another reality called Trae. Dreaming of Deliverance tells of Lindsay’s experiences both in Trae, where she finds herself among people enslaved by terrifying creatures, and in prison where she tries to make sense of what’s happening in her sleep: Is she actually escaping from prison somehow or is she losing her mind?" />
<outline title="Podiobooks.com: Time Crystal 2 by Wyken Seagrave" text="Podiobooks.com: Time Crystal 2 by Wyken Seagrave" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/484/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=484" description="The story so far: When Irish school teacher Sam Fitzpatrick and CERN scientist Michael Zhang are absorbed by a black hole, they find themselves outside the Universe on a planet populated by gigantic insect-like Entroilians and Argolaths. The Universe is merely part of their elaborate lifecycle. Michael breaks the crystal machinery surrounding it and fragments fall into the Universe where time stops everywhere except near these crystals. Sam can talk to people who hold crystal, and the insects think they can fix the machinery and restart time, so he tells his step-daughter Catriona O’Brien to collect all the fragments and bring them down the time tunnel. But handsome Hungarian entrepreneur Alex Karolyi knows that firefighter George Gabor will not allow crystals to be removed from CERN. When George tries to catch them Alex flees and Catriona tries to fly into the Time Tunnel.So begins an epic adventure that will take Catriona on a journey back through the whole history of the Universe. Time Crystal is a timeless adventure-romance including domains both great and small you have never experienced before. Few works of fiction have ever encompassed such a range of ideas and environments, such sheer imaginative scale. " />
<outline title="Podiobooks.com: Paraffin Winter by Peter Chowney" text="Podiobooks.com: Paraffin Winter by Peter Chowney" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/482/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=482" description="The winter of 1963 was the coldest winter of the century in the UK, at a time when post-war austerity and social class divisions made for a miserable life for many people.  These were the days of back boilers, bubble and squeak, paraffin oil stoves, gas works, steam trains, and starting handles.  The 1960s technological and social revolution hadn’t happened yet.Ronnie and Jenny Delaney live in the south coast town of Poole, close by the gas works.  They get by - Jenny works in the local pottery and Ronnie runs a paraffin delivery round, helping to keep his grateful customers warm.  But then something unexpected turns up on the paraffin round: an eyeball.  It doesn't take Ronnie long to work out that it's got something to do with his past as a small-time crook, back in the East End of London.  Someone's messing him about.  He can handle it.  Or so he thinks.  But things start to get complicated, and he quickly finds himself way out of his depth.  It's going to take someone cleverer than Ronnie to get to the bottom of this one.  And that someone is closer than he could ever have imagined ...  " />
<outline title="Podiobooks.com: The Secret World Chronicle, Book Three: World Well Lost by Mercedes Lackey" text="Podiobooks.com: The Secret World Chronicle, Book Three: World Well Lost by Mercedes Lackey" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/478/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=478" description="Continuing the action and intrigue of the first two books, World Well Lost joins the ensemble cast of metahuman characters as they struggle against the growing powers of the Thule Society as well as Echo's own waning popularity. Famed fantasy and sci-fi author Mercedes Lackey and newcomers Dennis Lee and Cody Martin bring this superhero-themed braided novel podcast series to life with characters such as the Seraphym, Victoria Victrix, John Murdock, and Red Djinni, with stories read by Veronica Giguere." />
<outline title="Podiobooks.com: Some Other Scotland by Mick Bordet" text="Podiobooks.com: Some Other Scotland by Mick Bordet" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/415/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=415" description="Gravestones across Scotland are being defaced. An ancient advanced civilisation is discovered under the remains of Skara Brae.  Bonnie Prince Charlie returns to Scotland, two hundred years after his death.  Edinburgh police unearth a mysterious surveillance operation on the Queen's residence and the Scottish Parliament.    All these events take place in a Scotland which is both familiar and yet slightly twisted.Detective Jim Sykes' investigation into hidden cameras and a long-dead pretender to the throne uncovers a sinister plot that dates back centuries before the term 'terrorism' was coined.  Archaeologist Erica Wallis digs up more than she bargained for when she encounters an underground civilisation that has existed since before the pyramids of Egypt were built.  When one of their misplaced, but deadly artifacts falls into the hands of young street-poet 'Razer', he is launched into the middle of a clan war that has been waged across the World for millenia.Events triggered thousands of years ago are about to reach a climax that not only threatens Scotland, but could finally hand the modern World the tools of its own destruction." />
<outline title="Podiobooks.com: A Dance With Demons by Jeff Offringa" text="Podiobooks.com: A Dance With Demons by Jeff Offringa" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/466/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=466" description="Tarn Nohmal doesn't want much out of life. Food on the table, a roof over his head, and privacy. But when his old commander shows up and needs someone to track a band of orcs, what should be a simple mission turns out to become an endeavor to stop disaster from spreading across the entire realm of Averim.Not only is the kingdom threatened from within by a civil war, but the lack of troops on the eastern border seems to be making the orcs bolder. And to top it off, a demon is slaughtering orcs and humans alike. And it's up to Tarn and his companions; Nyla, a half-elven wizard, and Logan, a human priest raised by dwarves, to stop it before it comes to their home town and slaughters everyone there.But will there be a home town to return to? The Earl keeps calling troops west to support him in the civil war. The orcs can't be that big a threat... right?Step into the world of Aromathus, the creation of author Jeff Offringa, and experience swords and sorcery, military maneuvers, and political intrigue in a place where magic abounds, knights charge gloriously into battle, and the orcs may not be as stupid as they appear..." />
<outline title="Podiobooks.com: The Sorcerer\'s Secret by J. A. Areces" text="Podiobooks.com: The Sorcerer\'s Secret by J. A. Areces" type="rss" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/bookfeed/29127/450/book.xml" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/podiobooks/book.php?ID=450" description="Book 3 of the Salem Concord begins where The Secret Society of Seven Sorcerers left off.  In the Sorcerer's Secret, Jesse ventures deeper into the wizarding world and discovers that the Wizardry must live a secret.   A secret that history altered.  A secret that FOLK must never learn.  It's up to Jesse and the secret wizard agent Ch-U-Ch to stop the forces that are trying to breach the Salem Concord and cause another Witch War.  Meanwhile, Andrew and Brendan are learning that being a wizard in a FOLK world has its consequences.  As their secret is revealed, they learn that they're placing their friends lives in danger.  It's up to them and Chief Fabiano to stop Lord Alex from obtaining two of the most powerful magical items in the world.  Time is running out, and on Halloween, one cry will be heard throughout the land, &quot;The Witches are Coming!&quot;" />
</body>
</opml>	
