<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			Arts &amp; Literature&apos; podcast novels.&nbsp; Presented by: LibriVox.org
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Wuthering Heights (Version 2) by Brontë, Emily]]>" xmlUrl="http://librivox.org/bookfeeds/wuthering-heights-by-emily-bronte-2.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Wuthering Heights (Version 2) by Brontë, Emily]]>" htmlUrl="http://librivox.org/wuthering-heights-by-emily-bronte-2/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>http://librivox.org/wuthering-heights-by-emily-bronte-2/</h1>Emily Brontë&apos;s only novel, published in 1847 under the pseudonym Ellis Bell, tells the tale of the all-encompassing and passionate, yet thwarted, love between Heathcliff and Catherine Earnshaw, and how this unresolved passion eventually destroys them and many around them.</p><p>Now considered a classic of English literature, Wuthering Heights met with mixed reviews by critics when it first appeared, with many horrified by the stark depictions of mental and physical cruelty.&nbsp; Though Charlotte Brontë&apos;s Jane Eyre was originally considered the best of the Brontë sisters&apos; works, many subsequent critics of Wuthering Heights argued that its originality and achievement made it superior. (Summary by Wikipedia)]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Enchanted April, The by Arnim, Elizabeth von]]>" xmlUrl="http://librivox.org/bookfeeds/the-enchanted-april-by-elizabeth-von-arnim.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Enchanted April, The by Arnim, Elizabeth von]]>" htmlUrl="http://librivox.org/the-enchanted-april-by-elizabeth-von-arnim/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>http://librivox.org/the-enchanted-april-by-elizabeth-von-arnim/</h1>It&apos;s a dreary February in post-World War I London when Mrs. Wilkins spots an advertisement in The Times for a small Italian castle for rent in April. She sees another member of her women&apos;s club, Mrs. Arbuthnot, reading the same advertisement and manages to convince her that the two of them should rent it. Both are miserable and lonely in their marriages. They can&apos;t afford the cost of the villa, San Salvatore, on their own and must advertise for two others, eventually recruiting an elderly widow named Mrs. Fisher, and Lady Caroline Dester, a beautiful young socialite desperate to escape from  London and society. The four journey to Italy where San Salvatore works its magic separately on each of them, changing their lives in unexpected ways. (Summary by Diana Kiesners)]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Midsummer Night's Dream, A by Shakespeare, William]]>" xmlUrl="http://librivox.org/bookfeeds/a-midsummer-nights-dream-by-william-shakespeare.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Midsummer Night's Dream, A by Shakespeare, William]]>" htmlUrl="http://librivox.org/a-midsummer-nights-dream-by-william-shakespeare/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>http://librivox.org/a-midsummer-nights-dream-by-william-shakespeare/</h1>Magic, fairies, young lovers chasing each other through a forest, a man with a donkey&apos;s head, and impish Puck wreaking havoc right and left.&nbsp; What&apos;s going on here?&nbsp; It&apos;s  A Midsummer Night&apos;s Dream , Shakespeare at his most fanciful.&nbsp; The play opens with Theseus, Duke of Athens, preparing for his wedding.&nbsp; Egeus complains to Theseus that his daughter Hermia refuses to marry Demetrius.&nbsp; When Hermia is given the choice between marriage to Demetrius or life as a nun, she and her true love Lysander flee into the forest.&nbsp; Demetrius follows them; and Helena, who loves Demetrius, follows  him .  Also in the forest are Oberon and Titania, king and queen of the fairies, at odds with one another.&nbsp; At Oberon&apos;s behest, Puck causes Demetrius to fall in love with Helena -- oops, he missed, that was Lysander instead.&nbsp; Mayhem ensues.&nbsp; In the meantime, a group of bumbling craftsmen rehearses a play.&nbsp; Puck gives one of them, Bottom, the head of an ass and makes Titania fall in love with him.&nbsp; Further hilarity results as Bottom sees nothing at all odd about this.&nbsp; Eventually everything is straightened out, Bottom and the rest &quot;perform&quot; their play, there is a triple wedding, and Puck assures us the whole thing has been a dream.&nbsp; Number of quotes you know: 5 (what fools these mortals be).  Useful insults: 19.  (Summary by Laurie Anne Walden)]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>

