<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>LibriVox.org Public Domain Sci-Fi podcasts, audio dramas, &amp; podcast novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Sky Is Falling by Lester del Rey]]>" xmlUrl="http://librivox.org/rss/3780" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Librivox: Sky Is Falling, The by del Rey, Lester]]>" htmlUrl="http://librivox.org/the-sky-is-falling-by-lester-del-rey/" description="<![CDATA[<p>After dying in a terrible accident at a building site, Dave Hanson finds himself being brought back to life in a world where magic is real, and where the sky is breaking apart and falling.&nbsp; And he is expected to put it back together again.&nbsp; Will he be able to save this strange world, and his own new life?&nbsp; (Summary by Karen Savage)</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Badge of Infamy by Lester Del Rey]]>" xmlUrl="http://librivox.org/bookfeeds/badge-of-infamy-by-lester-del-rey.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Librivox: Badge of Infamy by Del Rey, Lester]]>" htmlUrl="http://librivox.org/badge-of-infamy-by-lester-del-rey" description="<![CDATA[<p>Daniel Feldman was a doctor once.&nbsp; He made the mistake of saving a friend's life in violation of Medical Lobby rules.&nbsp; Now, he's a pariah, shunned by all, forbidden to touch another patient.&nbsp; But things are more loose on Mars.&nbsp; There, Doc Feldman is welcomed by the colonists, even as he's hunted by the authorities.&nbsp; But, when he discovers a Martian plague may soon wipe out humanity on two planets, Feldman finds himself a pivotal figure.&nbsp; War erupts.&nbsp; Earth is poised to wipe out the Mars colony utterly.&nbsp; A cure to the plague is the price of peace, and only Feldman can find it.&nbsp; (summary by Steven H.&nbsp; Wilson)</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Star Surgeon by Alan Edward Nourse]]>" xmlUrl="http://librivox.org/bookfeeds/star-surgeon-by-alan-edward-nourse.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Librivox: Star Surgeon by Nourse, Alan Edward]]>" htmlUrl="http://librivox.org/star-surgeon-by-alan-edward-nourse/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Dal Timgar had always wanted to be a doctor. As a Garvian and the first non-human to study medicine on Hospital Earth, he must face enormous adversity from classmates, professors, and some of the highest ranking physicians on all of Earth. Will his efforts be enough to earn him the Silver Star of a Star Surgeon? (Summary by Scott D. Farquhar)</p>]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[&apos;s audio dramas]]>" url="" type="link" text="<![CDATA[Podcast audio dramas from ]]>" description="<![CDATA[Podcast audio dramas from ]]>" />-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast audio drama from ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by .  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
	</body>
</opml>
