<?xml version="-1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Polyamory, BDSM, kink, and other alternative lifestyle podcasts</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Kink On Tap]]>" xmlUrl="http://KinkOnTap.com/?feed=podcast" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Kink On Tap]]>" htmlUrl="http://KinkOnTap.com/?cat=3" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Kink On Tap</h1><p>The smart sexuality netcast for the kinkily inclined.&nbsp; Tired of the pulp eroticization of sexuality?&nbsp; Annoyed by the self-aggrandizement of sex bloggers?&nbsp; Want a more thoughtful, heartier, smarter approach to sexuality, society, culture, feminism, and queer activism?&nbsp; These are the droids you&#039;re looking for.&nbsp; Tune in live every Sunday at 8 PM Eastern, 5 PM Pacific.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Kinky and the Geek]]>" xmlUrl="http://kinkyandthegeek.podbean.com/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Kinky and the Geek - hosted by Fleshvine and MightyBill]]]>" htmlUrl="http://KinkyandtheGeek.wordpress.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Kinky and the Geek</h1><h3>hosted by Fleshvine and MightyBill</h3><p><a href='mailto:kinkyandthegeek@gmail.com'>kinkyandthegeek@gmail.com</a></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[DungeonPlace - Home of the DungeonPlace FetishCast Podcast]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/dungeonplace/jiih" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[DungeonPlace - Home of the DungeonPlace FetishCast Podcast]]>" htmlUrl="http://dungeonplace.com/hole" description="<![CDATA[<h1>DungeonPlace - Home of the DungeonPlace FetishCast Podcast</h1><p>BDSM in a kinky, fun, fetishy wrapper!&nbsp; Let us put Consensual Pain in Your Pocket!&nbsp; Call us at 951.GOT.KINK</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Erotic Awakening Podcast]]>" xmlUrl="http://eroticawakening.libsyn.com/rss" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Erotic Awakening Podcast]]>" htmlUrl="http://eroticawakeninglibsyn.com" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Erotic Awakening Podcast</h1><p>Welcome to Erotic Awakening with Dan and dawn, an informative and entertaining exploration of all things erotic.&nbsp; From sacred sexuality to fetishes, BDSM to erotic spirituality, non standard relationships to alternative love styles, as well as simply fun kink.</p><p>Each week we present an aspect of erotic life - from how to sessions by well known instructors; interviews with highly regarded experts and presenters; event reviews from around the nation; to erotic products and kink media.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Polyamory Weekly]]>" xmlUrl="http://polyweekly.libsyn.com/rss" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Polyamory Weekly]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.polyweekly.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Polyamory Weekly</h1><p><h3>Tales from the front of responsible non-monogamy from a pansexual, kink-friendly point of view.&nbsp; For the full PW blog, visit <a href='http://www.polyweekly.com/'>www.polyweekly.com</a><h3>Minx and her listeners discuss loving more and polyamory, the lifestyle of being involved in more than one commited, long-term, loving relationship with the full knowledge and consent of all parties involved.&nbsp; In this community-driven show, each week Minx talks sex, relationships, communication, family, erotica, psychology, orgasms and anything else that comes up in the ins and outs of the daily polyamorous lifestyle.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[youngandkinky's Podcast]]>" xmlUrl="http://youngandkinky.libsyn.com/rss" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[youngandkinky's Podcast]]>" htmlUrl="http://youngandkinky.blogspot.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>youngandkinky's Podcast</h1><p>Young and Kinky is a youthful look at the kink and BDSM world intended for people 18 to 35 from the perspective of a kinky couple in their 20s and their views on BDSM, kink, and sex.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Libidacoria: The Late Night Talk Show]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.blogtalkradio.com/shadesofk.rss" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Libidacoria: The Late Night Talk Show | Blog Talk Radio Feed]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.blogtalkradio.com/shadesofk" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Libidacoria: The Late Night Talk Show</h1><h3>Blog Talk Radio Feed</h3><p>K--, host of the Chronicles of Libidacoria podcast, brings on some very interesting co-hosts to explore the topic of sex in every way imaginable.&nbsp; With biting sarcasm, this is perhaps the most smart-assiest sex show ever!  (Don&apos;t forget to disable your safe search!)Learn more about all within the empire of Libidacoria at www.libidacoria.com.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Shades of K--: Chronicles of Libidacoria]]>" xmlUrl="http://shadesofk.podbean.com/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Shades of K--: Chronicles of Libidacoria]]>" htmlUrl="http://shadesofk.podbean.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Shades of K--: Chronicles of Libidacoria</h1><p>Home of the Shades of K--: Chronicles of Libidacoria podcast as well as the Libidacoria: The Late Night Talk Show.&nbsp; Mature literature and discussion for the sexual intellectual.&nbsp; This podcast chronicles an independent woman's sexual journey in the modern world.&nbsp; Here you will get a glimpse into the mind of K--, author of Libidacoria: In a Plain Brown Wrapper, the new highly controversial poetry book.  ** Mature language and sexual explicit material. **</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Prurient Lifestyle Show]]>" xmlUrl="http://prurient.podbean.com/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Prurient Lifestyle Show]]>" htmlUrl="http://prurient.podbean.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Prurient Lifestyle Show</h1><p>Xena invite you to listen to news and views from our members.&nbsp; Prurient Lifestyle is a sex positive podcast hosted by Xena and her team on The Prurient Couples Social Network.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Dark Side]]>" xmlUrl="http://thedarksidepodcast.podbean.com/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Dark Side]]>" htmlUrl="http://thedarksidepodcast.podbean.com//" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Dark Side</h1><p>The Dark Side is an Adult, alternative lifestyle discussion podcast - involving discussion on Relationships, play, sex, and open communication.</p>]]>" />
		<!-- <outline title="<![CDATA[The Dark Side]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/podbean/ghzQ" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Dark Side]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.get-teased.ca/darkside.html/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Dark Side</h1><p>The Dark Side is an Adult, alternative lifestyle discussion podcast - involving discussion on Relationships, play, sex, and open communication.</p>]]>" /> -->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Masocast]]>" xmlUrl="http://masocast.com/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Masocast]]>" htmlUrl="http://masocast.com" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Masocast</h1><p>Interviews with kinky people about BDSM, sex, kink, fetish, dominance and submission.&bsp; A sexuality podcast featuring interviews about BDSM, Fetish, Kink and good ol&#039; sex.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Graydancer&apos;s Ropecast]]>" xmlUrl="http://graydancer.libsyn.com/rss" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Graydancer&apos;s Ropecast]]>" htmlUrl="http://graydancer.libsyn.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Graydancer&apos;s Ropecast</h1><p><p>The longest-running kinky sex podcast on the web.&nbsp; Rope bondage, BDSM, and more!&nbsp; Got rope?&nbsp; Graydancer talks about all things kinky, including sex education, current events in the BDSM scene, and lots of juicy bondage-related stuff.</p><p>The Ropecast had its humble beginnings in February of 2005, as the Premier Rope Bondage Podcast known as &quot;Rope Weekly.&quot; Hosted by Graydancer, with a steady stream of guest appearances by popular sexual performers, activists, and educators from around the globe.</p><p>While the focus is on the enjoyment of rope bondage, covering safety, techniques, art, and how to build connections with your partners, Graydancer has covered many other aspects of the kinky lifestyle including photography, sex education, and the political and social climate surrounding consenting adults doing what they like to do.</p><p>With a friendly, conversational style and a lot of humor (with the occasional bad pun) the Ropecast is a great way to share in the joys of rope and other knotty subjects...</p></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Mistress Matisse's Podcast]]>" xmlUrl="http://mistressmatisse.libsyn.com/rss" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Mistress Matisse's Podcast]]>" htmlUrl="http://mistressmatisse.libsyn.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Mistress Matisse's Podcast</h1><p>Mistress Matisse, Seattle sex columnist and professional dominatrix talks about BDSM, polyamory, sex work, and her life as a sexual outlaw.&nbsp; Adults only!<p>More About Me</p><p><a href='http://mistressmatisse.blogspot.com/'>Read My Blog</a></p><p><a href='http://www.thestranger.com/seattle/Author?oid=9386'>Read My Sex Columns In Seattle Alt-Weekly Paper <em>The Stranger</em></a></p><p><a href='http://www.mistressmatisse.com/'>My Professional Domination Website</a></p><p><a href='http://www.thestrangerlustlab.com/matisse/'>Other Articles By Me: The Lustlab Archives</a></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Dart's Domain]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/DartsDomain" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Dart's Domain]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.dartsdomain.com/dart.xml" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Dart's Domain</h1><p>Sir Dart's ongoing discussions around leather, kink, and the BDSM lifestyle.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
