<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			Sex-Positive podcasts
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Sex is Fun]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/GSGPodcasts" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Sex is Fun]]>" htmlUrl="http://sexisfunradioshow.blogspot.com//" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Sex is Fun</h1><p>Dedicated to the rational discussion of human sexuality from the apporoach of fun, enjoyment and pleasure.&nbsp; Each episode features a different topic that will discuss how to maximize sexual enjoyment while avoiding all the dangers of sex.&nbsp; Sex is Fun features human sexuality guru Kidder Kaper, sex educator Laura Rad, HIV/AIDS educator Gay Rick, and their sound engineer Coochie.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Audio Smut]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/AudioSmut/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Audio Smut - Sex Positive Podcasts For Perverts]]]>" htmlUrl="http://audiosmut.ca/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Audio Smut</h1><h3>Sex Positive Podcasts For Perverts</h3><p>Audio Smut is committed to challenging notions of decency.&nbsp; We are here to talk out of our ass, shake things up, moan in your ears and provoke your inner pervert.&nbsp; Audio Smut originally airs on CKUT 90.3 FM community radio.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Galore Podcast]]>" xmlUrl="http://galorepodcast.libsyn.com/rss" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Galore Podcast]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.galorepodcast.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Galore Podcast</h1><p>4he award winning, premier Seattle based internet show, Galore Podcast (http://www.galorepodcast.com).  For nearly 3 years we have provided an entertaining look at LGBT life in Seattle and around the world through interviews and discussions.&nbsp; Our goal for the show is to be very community based.&nbsp; We look at Galore as an excellent way to connect people all over our community and provide a voice in the often technologically dominated realm of internet entertainment.<a href='http://www.galorepodcast.com/'>WWW.Galorepodcast.com</a></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Oh Team!]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.theohteam.com/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Oh Team!]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.theohteam.com" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Oh Team!</h1><p>The Best in Adult radio!</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Taste of Sex - Reality Audio: A Reality Audio Show on Life in an Orgasm-Based Community]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/RealityAudio" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Taste of Sex - Reality Audio: A Reality Audio Show on Life in an Orgasm-Based Community]]>" htmlUrl="http://personallifemedia.com/podcasts/215-taste-of-sex-reality-audio/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Taste of Sex - Reality Audio: A Reality Audio Show on Life in an Orgasm-Based Community</h1><p>Recently the subject of a feature article in the New York  Times, the OneTaste community explores what it means to be an everyday person  living an extraordinary life.&nbsp; Found at the intersection between mindfulness and  sexuality, community and private experience, practice and play, the 40+  residents extend the philosophy for an intimate life by including you in on the  experience.&amp;nbsp; With candor, humor,  vulnerability, feel for yourself how the tapestry of real life is richer than  any fiction.&amp;nbsp; In a community where the  basic philosophy is that we all want the same things; to love and be loved, to  see and be seen, to know purpose and feel connection, take a peek inside and  feel it for yourself.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
