<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Sex advice &amp; educators podcasts</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Savage Love Podcast]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.thestranger.com/stranger/savage" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Savage Love Podcast]]>" htmlUrl="http://podcasts.thestranger.com/savagelove/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Savage Love Podcast</h1><p>Dan Savage, America's only advice columnist, answers your sex questions on the Internets. To record a question for Dan to be answered in a later podcast, call 206-201-2720.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[open source sex]]>" xmlUrl="http://violetblue.libsyn.com/rss" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[open source sex]]>" htmlUrl="http://violetblue.libsyn.com/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>open source sex</h1><p><h2>open source sex --- erotica, sex ed and more with sex educator Violet Blue</h2></p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Expanded Lovemaking: Sex, Love, and Consciousness]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/Expanded_Lovemaking" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Expanded Lovemaking: Sex, Love, and Consciousness]]>" htmlUrl="http://personallifemedia.com/podcasts/230-expanded-lovemaking/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Expanded Lovemaking: Sex, Love, and Consciousness</h1><p>Enjoy juicy and informative interviews with the acclaimed author Dr.&nbsp; Patti Taylor of ExpandedLovemaking.com and the Expand Her Orgasm Tonight System - 21 Day Program for Partners, as she talks with world-renowned experts on sex, sensuality and real-life practitioners of the art and science of orgasm!&nbsp; Expanded Lovemaking is a fusion of ancient erotic wisdom and modern practices and insights, where you learn to share ever-expanding bliss with your partner.&nbsp; Email Dr.&nbsp; Patti at patti@personallifemedia.com.</p><p>Expanded Lovemaking is a profound, fun, and rewarding path for those seeking prolonged orgasmic bliss with all the intimacy, and spiritual, mental, and physical connection you desire.</p><p>Learn how to expand your capacity to receive mind-blowing pleasure, extend your orgasm from minutes to hours, use erotic fantasies and stories to spice up your love life, and get expert advice on tantric sexual positions.&nbsp; The show&apos;s material ranges from exploring how we can link lovemaking to God and spirituality, to the erotic art of the strip tease, and the details of men and women&apos;s health, hormones, Viagra, and extended pleasure. </p><p>Discover the endless depth, variety, and connection available in intercourse and how to master finding your lover&apos;s hot spots and sensing his or her orgasmic energy.&nbsp; Learn playful and effective seduction strategies too.</p><p>Dr.&nbsp; Patti solicits expert advice on the best toys, games, and educational videos, special techniques for using self-pleasuring to be a better lover, and the intricate details of prostate massage and stroking your lover&apos;s genitals.</p><p>Together, let&apos;s investigate compassionate non-violent communication, the mastery of sharing Taoist chi energy and Kundalini, goddess worship, and the use of chakras in tantra.&nbsp; Explore the use of breathwork, whole body massage, and the magic of g-spot healing and female ejaculation.</p><p>Discover skills to delay premature ejaculation, and prolong erection.&nbsp; Learn the value of supplements and look at the benefits of bio-identical estrogen and testosterone for peak sexual performance. </p><p>Expanded Lovemaking interviews Spiritual Teachers in Hinduism, Taoism, Buddhism, Shamanism, and Christianity.&nbsp; We discuss how to free up Love and Sexual Energy for Planetary Awareness, Peace, and the Evolution of Consciousness.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Just For Women: Dating, Relationships and Sex with Alissa Kriteman]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/JustForWomen" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Just For Women: Dating, Relationships and Sex with Alissa Kriteman]]>" htmlUrl="http://personallifemedia.com/podcasts/229-just-for-women/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Just For Women: Dating, Relationships and Sex with Alissa Kriteman</h1><p>Are you ready to find out what you can do to have the deep, beautifully fulfilling love you want in your life? Are you ready to find out how to live the outrageously fun and full life and you know you were meant to be living? Have you been searching for more intimacy in your relationships but are at a loss as to how to create it?</p><p>Well, tune in and listen as host Alissa Kriteman of ABC’s "How to Get the Guy" and author of "Alissa’s Four Cornerstones for Living Your Dreams" explores these topics with today’s top love, sex and relationship experts!  From ancient Buddhist teachings to modern day sexilogical bodyworkers, listeners can boldly adventure into the myriad of alternatives and choices now available to women.</p><p>On each show, Alissa offers keen insight from her vast background as an author, coach, and workshop leader. Open yourself to provocative, cutting edge, experimental ideas on loving yourself more, healing relationships, understanding men, attracting what you desire, the new art of seduction and the evolution of love that will radically shift the way you date and relate. Brought to you by Personal Life Media, Inc.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>

