<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title> podcast novels from podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Beautiful Red » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/beautiful-red/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Beautiful Red - A free podcast novel by M. Darusha Wehm.  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/beautiful-red/" description="<![CDATA[The future is boring.&nbsp; Technology has solved the world&apos;s most pressing problems, leaving people with tedious work and mundane play.&nbsp; Jack is a Security Officer Class 5, which sounds important, but isn&apos;t.&nbsp; However, her banal life as a cubicle worker by day and tinkerer by night is interrupted when she discovers that her employer&apos;s computer system has been invaded.Jack enlists the help of her only friends - her co-worker, Gilles and Adrian, an online friend she&apos;s never met - to help her track down the source of the invasion.&nbsp; Her investigation leads her to a shadowy group called the Red, where Jack learns that not everyone lives a life of quiet servitude.Even though she believes that the Red are responsible for a series of gruesome attacks, Jack begins to become attracted to their worldview.&nbsp; In her search for the people responsible for the attacks, she confronts the leaders of the group as well as her own burgeoning sense of self-awareness.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Self Made » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/self-made/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/self-made/" text="<![CDATA[Self Made - a podcast novel by M. Darusha Wehm.  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[<p><i>Ever wish things were different?</i></p><p>Ivy Velasquez did, so she became someone else. In the 3D virtual world Marionette City, you can be anything you want — but everyone still knows who you are. Driven by her desire for a new life, Ivy takes her future in her hands when she makes another identity for herself. A brilliant designer, Ivy works for one of the huge firms which control the online system the world relies upon for both business and pleasure. But one day, Ivy discovers that her alternate self, Reuben Cobalt, had been murdered.</p><p>Since alternate identities are forbidden by the firms which control access to the nets and to M City, Ivy has nowhere to turn — until she finds Andersson Dexter. Part private eye, part vigilante and part cop, Dex sets out to uncover Reuben’s killer. Since the firms control almost every aspect of life, including law and order, justice for average people comes only at the hands of the outlaw organization to which Dex belongs.</p><p>Self Made is a murder mystery set in a vision of a future that seems to lurk just over the horizon. But above all, it is a story of how people strive to control their own destinies, and how that desire affects them and the people around them in ways they could never imagine.</p>]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?/" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
