<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>&apos;s audio dramas &amp; podcast novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[&apos;s audio dramas]]>" url="" type="link" text="<![CDATA[Podcast audio dramas from ]]>" description="<![CDATA[Podcast audio dramas from ]]>" />-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Corridor]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-corridor/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Corridor - A free podcast novel by Zan]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-corridor/" description="<![CDATA[The Corridor is a fantasy/horror story about Stuart Morrow, a man who has lost all hope and reason to live.&nbsp; However, a strange coincidence brings him unexpectedly into contact with a multitude of worlds beyond our own.&nbsp; Hunted by a despot who rules over countless alternate realities, Stuart&apos;s only hope is to seek help amongst the assortment of bizarre and grotesque characters who await him in the Corridor.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Bloodblaths]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/bloodbaths/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Bloodbaths  - A free podcast novel by Steve Libbey]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/bloodbaths/" description="<![CDATA[The Bloodbaths is the first book of Steve Libbey&apos;s new Aqua Pura Trilogy, a sword and sandal fantasy featuring a plumber on an epic quest to win back his beloved.&nbsp; Mercedes Lackey says: &quot;Steve Libbey gives the &apos;sword-and-sandal&apos; epic a kick in the tunic and  propels it into the gestalt of the 21st century, with an everyman hero whose brains triumph over brawn.&quot;  Crixus Oraan is a water artesan, an engineer who builds aqueducts and piping for bathhouses and mansions in the empire of Rond (which bears a resemblance to our own Roman Empire).&nbsp; His guild has entrusted him with a large sum of gold to establish a branch in the up-and-coming coastal town of Restia.&nbsp; In a misguided effort to win enough gold to buy a lavish house for his new fiancé Kharrina, he loses the guild&apos;s gold in a card game.&nbsp; A shady sea captain present at the game-and possibly responsible for fleecing him-offers to sneak him off to the wild and mysterious continent of Minq.&nbsp; Afraid to lose his status in society for his crime, he agrees, hoping to gain back the gold he lost and compensate the guild back in Rond.&nbsp; In this first volume in the bold new Aqua Pura Trilogy, Crixus finds employment with the Lamiae of Nistru, a cruel society where those at the top bathe in the lifeblood of those on the bottom.&nbsp; Will his conscience allow him to finish the job?&nbsp; By turns dark, comedic, erotic and thrilling, The Bloodbaths is a book that transcends genre to stand on its own.&nbsp; This podcast is read by SWC&apos;s own Veronica Giguere.]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast audio drama from ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by .  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
	</body>
</opml>
