<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Fantasy podcast novels from Podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" type="link" text="<![CDATA[]]>" url="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Legon Awakening]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/legon-awakening/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Legon Awakening - A free podcast novel by yn jen]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/legon-awakening/" description="<![CDATA[Set in a world that is not our own, Legon Awakening takes you through an epic journey into a land full of imagination and innovation.Join Legon and his sister, Sasha, search to understand their true heritage, confused at the possibility that of being part human and part elf.&nbsp; Surrounded by elves, the newly introduced Iumenta race, Dragons and Humans; Legon and Sasha&#039;s lives are filled with adventure and fantasy on their search for answers as they begin an epic journey of discovery; not to mention the incredible battle scenes which will be surely to capture your imagination!]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The WorldWrights]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-worldwrights/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The WorldWrights - a free podcast novel by Max Grant]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-worldwrights/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Kalukan awakens from millenia of cold sleep to find his companions dead. He has been charged by the long-dead Worldwrights to protect their creation from its out-of-control Overseer.</p><p>As Kalukan prepares for his final quest against the Overseer, now named the Ghala, he begins to learn that the World's purpose is not that which he was taught. With a frayed sense of faith in his purpose, Kalukan sets out to reach the inexplicable construction known as the Skylock, where history tells him a city will be built to stand against the Ghala, a final bastion of civilization. Kalukan hopes but cannot believe that he is the hero they imagine he is.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Outcast]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/outcast/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Outcast - a free podcast novel by Chris Hvidston]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/outcast/" description="<![CDATA[<h3>Dalan Kalamar had it all.</h3><p>An life of luxury, a loving family, and intended bride, and a destiny that would one day see him assume the Eldership of his Clan.</p><p>Then, on a dark night in his 12th year of life, four would-be assassins changed all that. Charged by his father with protecting a sacred artifact, Dalan was left for dead by his attackers, and the artifact subsequently stolen.</p><p>One year later, Dalan awakens from a comatose state not only to find his body healed, but also to the fact that his family has disowned him. Humiliated before his peers, the would-be heir to the Tiger’s Paw Clan is cast out to live amongst the lowest of the low in Bengalan society:</p><h3>The exiles.</h3><p>Outcasts from the Clans, the exiles are a society unto themselves, shunned by all and forced to live in secret. They move through the secular, non-Clan world under the cover of assumed identities, taking jobs where strong backs are favored over questionable pasts. Through an elaborate underground network known as The Foundation, many exiles have found some glimmer of hope in a world committed to rooting them out and exterminating them like so much vermin.</p><p>It is into this world that a 13-year old Dalan is thrust. With no money and only a tiny bit of martial arts training, the young tiger begins his journey through the dark underbelly of Bengalan society. His eyes are quickly opened to the true brutality of the Clans, as he bears witness to an act so horrifying that he begins to question all he’d been brought up to believe.</p><p>Hope does exist for the young tiger, however…in the form of a mysterious trainer who extends an offer to him. The offer is to train Dalan in an ancient fighting form…one that will transform him from a desperate, fearful exile into a beast to be feared and respected by all. The young tiger accepts, and before long finds himself on a journey towards a destiny that will challenge all he’s ever known and believed, and make him see the world in a new, cold light.</p><p>He also finds hope in the loving arms of a fellow exile, one from a far off land running from an alleged curse put on her by those who cast her out. As their love for each other grows, Dalan soon finds himself faced with a choice: Devote his life to his newfound love and abandon any hope of regaining his honor…</p><p>Or risk losing everything for one chance at bloody, unforgiving vengeance</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Ninth Avatar]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-ninth-avatar/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Ninth Avatar - a free podcast novel by Todd Newton]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-ninth-avatar/" description="<![CDATA[<center>Nine Pillars, Eight Avatars</center><p>For Starka, an outcast accused of incest, life is about as simple as one could hope. A prophecy of the ascension of the Avatar of Darkness changed that. Starka, protected by the mysterious warrior DaVille, tries desperately to prevent the disturbing prophecy from becoming a reality.</p><p>The world is thrown into chaos as the Carrion Army comes to power, destroying the rival nations of Brong and Rochelle. Wan Du and Mayrah are drawn into the conflict when their homes are destroyed and Cairos, a wizard from the betrayed city of Illiadora, likewise seeks revenge for his fallen comrades.</p><p>As the leader of the Carrion army seeks to cover the world in death and darkness to become a living embodiment of magic, these uncertain allies battle against an inevitable conclusion.</p><center>The Ninth Avatar is coming.</center>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[KIRINS: The Spell of No&#039;an]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/kirins-the-spell-of-noan/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[KIRINS: The Spell of No&#039;an - a free podcast novel by James D. Priest]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/kirins-the-spell-of-noan/" description="<![CDATA[<p>A race of tiny, magical beings lives on Earth today. They dwell in elaborate tree homes and mysterious underground sanctuaries. Because of an ancient dispute, however, humans are unaware of their hidden civilization.</p><p>They are kirins.</p><p>For thousands of years they lived in peace. But a deadly menace now threatens their existence. A party of daring explorers, led by the wise magician Speckarin, is sent on trained ravens to destroy an evil lurking a continent and an ocean away. Failure of this mission would mean death to the voyagers and the entire kirin race. But their success will depend on aid from a truly unexpected source, human beings.</p><p>Fly with these adventurers and witness today's world as it has never before been seen. You'll find yourself looking to the skies for this mystical race of beings, because maybe, just maybe...</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Dark Fever]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/darkfever/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Darkfever - A free podcast novel by Karin Marie Moning]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/darkfever/" description="<![CDATA[MacKayla Lane&#039;s life is good. She has great friends, a decent job, and a car that breaks down only every other week or so. In other words, she&#039;s your perfectly ordinary twenty-first-century woman. Or so she thinks...until something extraordinary happens.When her sister is murdered, leaving a single clue to her death-a cryptic message on Mac&#039;s cell phone-Mac journeys to Ireland in search of answers. The quest to find her sister&#039;s killer draws her into a shadowy realm where nothing is as it seems, where good and evil wear the same treacherously seductive mask. She is soon faced with an even greater challenge: staying alive long enough to learn how to handle a power she had no idea she possessed-a gift that allows her to see beyond the world of man, into the dangerous realm of the Fae....As Mac delves deeper into the mystery of her sister&#039;s death, her every move is shadowed by the dark, mysterious Jericho, a man with no past and only mockery for a future. As she begins to close in on the truth, the ruthless Vlane-an alpha Fae who makes sex an addiction for human women-closes in on her. And as the boundary between worlds begins to crumble, Mac&#039;s true mission becomes clear: find the elusive Sinsar Dubh before someone else claims the all-powerful Dark Book-because whoever gets to it first holds nothing less than complete control of the very fabric of both worlds in their hands....]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
