<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>&apos;s audio dramas &amp; podcast novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[&apos;s audio dramas]]>" url="" type="link" text="<![CDATA[Podcast audio dramas from ]]>" description="<![CDATA[Podcast audio dramas from ]]>" />-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Noggle Stones]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/noggle-stones/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Noggle Stones - A free podcast novel by Wil Radcliff]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/noggle-stones/" description="<![CDATA[Shunned by his people and tormented by nightmare visions, Bugbear, the mad goblin scholar, ventures into the wilderness with his ne&apos;er-do-well cousin, Tudmire, to seek out an ancient ruin and the lost wisdom it holds.&nbsp; Soon the cousins find themselves embroiled in cosmic events as their magical world of Annwfn is merged with 19th Century Earth after an accident concerning a mysterious scroll Tudmire acquires in a crooked game of Noggle Stones.&nbsp; While fleeing the enraged ogres they cheated, Bugbear and Tudmire happen upon Martin Manchester, who appears to be a creature of mythology known as a human.&nbsp; Bugbear takes Manchester as his apprentice, agreeing to teach him the empowering ways of Non-Logical Thought.&nbsp; The trio soon discovers that dark forces have aligned against them, and the two worlds may have been merged only to be destroyed!]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[KIRINS: The Spell of No'an]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/kirins-the-spell-of-noan/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[KIRINS: The Spell of No&apos;an - a free podcast novel by James D. Priest]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/kirins-the-spell-of-noan/" description="<![CDATA[<p>A race of tiny, magical beings lives on Earth today. They dwell in elaborate tree homes and mysterious underground sanctuaries. Because of an ancient dispute, however, humans are unaware of their hidden civilization.</p><p>They are kirins.</p><p>For thousands of years they lived in peace. But a deadly menace now threatens their existence. A party of daring explorers, led by the wise magician Speckarin, is sent on trained ravens to destroy an evil lurking a continent and an ocean away. Failure of this mission would mean death to the voyagers and the entire kirin race. But their success will depend on aid from a truly unexpected source, human beings.</p><p>Fly with these adventurers and witness today&apos;s world as it has never before been seen. You&apos;ll find yourself looking to the skies for this mystical race of beings, because maybe, just maybe...</p>]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast audio drama from ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by .  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
	</body>
</opml>
