<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			NGO/Non-prophit &amp; Political podcast novels.&nbsp; Presented by: podiobooks.com
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[A Coffee Crusade]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/a-coffee-crusade/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[A Coffee Crusade - A free audiobook by Theodore Isaac Erski]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/a-coffee-crusade/" description="<![CDATA[Bridget Hall is a driven &amp; successful entrepreneur running a non-profit company named the Coffee Exchange Alliance. She's working to establish a fair-trade business presence on the Caribbean island of Salavandra, but must overcome the corrupt Minister of Agriculture, Rafael Gallegos, who profits by marginalizing the island's farmers and smuggling their coffee to Jamaica.  Bridget tackles personal &amp; professional challenges on Salavandra that ultimately shake her belief in the choices she&apos;s made in life as well as in her self-appointed role as savior of the island's coffee farmers.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Judge Fogg]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/judge-fogg/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Judge Fogg - A free audiobook by Randy O'Brien]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/judge-fogg/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Judge Fogg</h1><h3>by Randy O&apos;Brien</h3><p>Charles Fogg is the first African-American criminal court judge inNashville history.&nbsp; But his climb up the ladder of jurisprudence isn&apos;t aneasy one.&nbsp; The system that brought him from poverty to the police forceto law school and the bench is also his eventual downfall.&nbsp; Filled withheartfelt characters and extraordinary plot twists, this story willdelight every reader.&nbsp; Sexy, provocative, controversial...this story willclamp onto your soul and never let go.&nbsp; You will be forever changed afterreading Judge Fogg.&nbsp; Rated R for language, sex, violence and theme.&nbsp; Notfor young readers.&nbsp; Available for download and soon in paperback print-on-demand atwww.&nbsp; literaryroad.&nbsp; com.&quot;I&apos;ve been a fan of Randy O&apos;Brien&apos;s work for years, and with thepublication of &quot;Judge Fogg,&quot; I think he&apos;s finally going to get therecognition and readership he deserves. &quot;Judge Fogg&quot; is compelling andengaging and I guarantee you, if you&apos;ll just read the first chapter, youwon&apos;t be able to put it down.&nbsp; It rings true and authentic.&nbsp; It&apos;s not onlya page-turner, but a page-turner that makes you think and moves youprofoundly.&nbsp; You&apos;ll carry &quot;Judge Fogg&quot; around with you for a long timeafter you finish it....&quot;Steven Womack, Edgar Award-winning author of &quot;Dead Folks Blues.&quot; </p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Best Laid Plans]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-best-laid-plans/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Best Laid Plans - A free audiobook by Terry Fallis]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-best-laid-plans/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Best Laid Plans</h1><h3>by Terry Fallis</h3><p>&quot;The Best Laid Plans&quot; is a satirical novel of Canadian politics written by Terry Fallis.&nbsp; It recounts the unlikely and amusing alliance between a 30-something burnt out, jaded political staffer, and an older, cantankerous, engineering professor.&nbsp; Driven by a federal election and the life of the resulting minority conservative government, the novel moves between the small town of Cumberland, Ontario on the shores of the Ottawa River, and the nation&apos;s capital.&nbsp; While the characters and their exploits are often comical, serious ideas on politics and democracy underlie the fun.&nbsp; For more information on the novel and author, visit <a href='http://www.terryfallis.com/'>www.terryfallis.com</a>.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>

