<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			Real Life inspired Fiction podcast novels.
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Infamy]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/infamy/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Infamy - A free audiobook by Squid Varilekova]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/infamy/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Infamy</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Squid Varilekova</h3><p>Infamy is a difficult thing to live with.&nbsp; It removes privacy, infects every aspect of daily life, and even causes the people it encounters casually to run and hide.&nbsp; Very few know how to deal with it well, but others can make the infamous lifestyle an art form.&nbsp; Join a university professor as he overcomes a slight brush with infamy, grabs life by the horns, and takes charge of his once fearful existence.&nbsp; Join a successful executive as he regains a life lost to an infamous woman.&nbsp; And join a graduate student researching the length and breadth of what infamy can do to a soul.&nbsp; This is a story of three men grappling with the ingloriousness of human existence.&nbsp; Throw in a little adventure, stir up a little romance, and add a mythical trip to the afterlife, and you will have &quot;Infamy,&quot; the first podiobook by Squid Varilekova.&nbsp; Plug in your headphones, download a few tracks, and explore your own infamous lifestyle.&nbsp; Infamy is waiting for you.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Scars]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-scars/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Scars - A free audiobook by William Tennant]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-scars/" description="<![CDATA[Peter Everett is a man stained with grief, his life becomes a struggle of decisions as he watches the lives of the people around him dissolve and burn.&nbsp; Mags Donne is a damaged, bruised young girl, reaching out into the darkness, trying to take control of her life.&nbsp; Their Scars are what begin to unite them, with the people that surround them.&nbsp; The Scars is a novel of difficulty, hatred, love, intrigue, kidnap, wrongdoing, abuse, laughter and beauty.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Squatter With a Lexus]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/squatter-with-a-lexus/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Squatter With a Lexus - A free audiobook by Tom Lichtenberg]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/squatter-with-a-lexus/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Squatter With a Lexus</h1><h3>by Tom Lichtenberg</h3><p>Pearson Holmes disappeared a long time ago, leaving behind a potentially valuable safety deposit box. Freddy the Freegan is the first to stumble across the mystery, but soon a whole cast of characters are out to find the key and claim the treasure before time runs out and the contents are forfeit to the state. Who will solve the riddle of the Squatter with a Lexus?</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Resurrecting Randi]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/resurrecting-randi/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Resurrecting Randi - A free audiobook by David Shepherd]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/resurrecting-randi/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Resurrecting Randi</h1><h3>by David Shepherd</h3><p>When college professor Travis Harrison meets the copper-headed seductress, Layla Sommers, the two are drawn together with a fierce attraction - a desperate need as impossible as it is inevitable.&nbsp; Layla reminds Travis of his deceased daughter, Randi, and after Layla attempts suicide, he brings her into his home.&nbsp; There, despite her wild mood swings and overt seductiveness, there also come moments of remarkable love and compassion which help Travis come to terms with the truth surrounding his daughter&apos;s death.&nbsp; Ultimately, however, Layla&apos;s volatile behavior costs Travis his career and his marriage; she even frames him with a murder.&nbsp; The novel opens - and closes - with Travis parked on the side of a cold and desolate highway.&nbsp; He hasn&apos;t seen Layla for a year and is waiting for her to emerge from a remote psychiatric center.&nbsp; He holds a gun in his hand...</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>

