<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Humor &amp; Comedy podcast novels from Podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Greg Crites&#039; Website]]>" url="http:///" type="link" text="<![CDATA[Greg Crites&#039; Website]]>" description="<![CDATA[The homepage &amp; website for Greg Crites the way to funny autor.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Fried Green Zombies]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/fried-green-zombies/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/fried-green-zombies/" text="<![CDATA[Fried Green Zombies - A free podcast novel by John Allen]]>" description="<![CDATA[<p>Chett and Harry are two recently unemployed construction workers on their way to a weekend of beer, Southern Comfort, and frog gigging at their musty-rusted 1970's RV parked at their favorite hunting camp when they stumble on Bob, the mysterious, busty, burqa-clad, non-English speaking beauty just standing in the middle of nowhere on the side of dusty Nine Mile Cutoff in rural Bovina, Mississippi.</p><p>Then all hell breaks loose. Their favorite pond is missing. They're being chased by truck driving zombies, dirty cops, UFOs and other ne'er-do-wells. Someone stole Chett's jacked up Scottsdale four-by-four. Zombies are traipsing around their trailer, and crazy Uncle Crank is trying to feed them zombie chicken for dinner.</p><p>Aided by a classic computer nerd, a crazy man wielding a frying pan, and a space babe who gets nekkid any time someone turns out the lights, follow Chett and Harry as they battle their way across the rural countryside and ultimately save the world.</p><p>Why is their pond missing, and why did the Dodge of Death spring from the muddy crater left in its center? Who is Bob and why is she so good with shotguns? Why are they being chased by two really skinny, pale, bald, goatee-clad wierdos? What is the dirty county sheriff hiding? And will Chett and Harry ever make it out alive?</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Crusade]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/crusade/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Crusade]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/crusade/" description="<![CDATA[A drug-fueled crusade by two deranged journalists assigned to look into the morass of organized religion. Cornholery, snake handlers, faith healers, serial killers, sarcasm, blasphemy-good, clean, American fun.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Dunkin the Vampire Slayer]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/dunkin-the-vampire-slayer/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Dunkin the Vampire Slayer]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/dunkin-the-vampire-slayer/" description="<![CDATA[What could possibly bring together a 450 pound vampire slayer, a drunken, acid-tongued detective, a good natured carpenter, bureaucratic vampires, giant anacondas, mutant vampire bats, Ho Hos, Twinkies and more one-liners than a night at the comedy club? Dunkin, the vampire slayer blends all this discordance and more into a hilarious adventure that moves from the muggy heat of Florida to the muggier heat of the Amazon. ....If Carl Hiaasson, Tim Dorsey and Dave Barry collaborated on a vampire story, it may have turned out like this absurd romp....]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Devlin, Abnormal Investigation]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/devlin-hell-hermit/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/devlin-hell-hermit/" text="<![CDATA[Devlin, Abnormal Investigations Case File: THE HELL HERMIT - A free audiobook by Greg Crites]]>" description="<![CDATA[<h3>Devlin, Abnormal Investigations Case File: THE HELL HERMIT</h3><p>This is a spin off of the character, Devlin, from the Dunkin, the Vampire Slayer trilogy of novels. It's a rip off of X-Files, featuring a near indestructible alcoholic vampire, with few socially redeeming qualities. His friends, including a wolf and a chimp are all smarter than he is, but he does excel at drinking and mayhem.</p><p>Here, he takes the case of a strange entity called the Hell hermit, who has lost the Key of Death. This could be bad news for humanity, but Devlin doesn't care as long as it doesn't interfere with his drinking. When innocents get hurt, he battles a giant hegdeapple, and singlehandedly attempts to cure the lust problem in the middle east.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Dunkin the Vampire Slayer II: Death Rides A Pale, Pink, Porcine Horse]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/dunkin-the-vampire-slayer-two/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Dunkin the Vampire Slayer II: Death Rides A Pale, Pink, Porcine Horse]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/dunkin-the-vampire-slayer-two/" description="<![CDATA[From the Smoky mountains of America, to Nepal, France, Australia, Italy, these three are on a quest that spans the globe. A quest to rid the earth of the bloodsuckers and find a cure for that nasty vampire blood. Many things stand in their way, high council vampires, hit men, ninjas, ancient  prophecies, and an unspeakable horror unleashed on the world by desperate vampires. And worst of all, Devlin&#039;s having serious anger issues as he comes to grips with being more powerful and more of a jackass than anything on earth.... oh, and more jokes, one-liners, and wiseass comments than should be allowed in any single novel.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Hard Boiled Headline]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/hard-boiled-headline/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Hard Boiled Headline - A free audiobook by Greg Crites]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/hard-boiled-headline/" description="<![CDATA[And what is this novel about you ask? Is this more nonsense? Uh, no... yeah... maybe. Heh!  If you are looking for Dunkin, or Devlin, or Gabe-this is not it. This book borders on serious. I think I was out of liquor when I wrote it-but I can&#0039;t remember.When you own a media outlet, you have a responsibility. A responsibility to safe guard the citizenry from their government. But how far do you go?This is a story about the small town newspaper business. A look at how one professional newsman uses the fourth estate exactly how it is NOT meant to be used. When you lower journalism to high comedy, is it still journalism? Who knows. But in this book, &quot;Hard Boiled Headline&quot;, a gang of unusual newspaper hacks accept a large cash payment to start a newspaper during election season. There&#0039;s only one string attached to the cash-use the paper to unseat an entire county&#0039;s crooked officials.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Odd Jobs]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/odd-jobs/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/odd-jobs/" text="<![CDATA[Odd Jobs - A free podcast novel by Karl Meade]]>" description="<![CDATA[Odd Jobs is a comic caper love story about Mountie women and layabout men, house and family, script-writers and cat-burglars. A modern tale of movie magic in the wrong hands: the Big Lebowski meets Elmore Leonard's niece.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Curious Education of Epitome Quirkstandard]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-curious-education-of-epitome-quirkstandard/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-curious-education-of-epitome-quirkstandard/" text="<![CDATA[<p>The Curious Education of Epitome Quirkstandard - A free podcast novel by A. F. Harold]]>" description="<![CDATA[</p><p>This peculiar comic novel concerns two men and a woman and looks at how they came to be where they were when they met and the effect that meeting had upon them.</p><p>One man is Epitome Quirkstandard, a benighted aristocrat in the Wodehousian tradition whose staff have abandoned him to go and fight in the First World War and who discovers the taste for learning - especially when he attempts to make his own breakfast.</p><p>The other man is Mr. Crepuscular, a man who has written a multitude of educative pamphlets that he kindly rents out to Quirkstandard. As an illiterate scamp he ran away to join the circus, but through a series of unlikely adventures he ends up as a wise quasi-Buddhist who understands that sometimes the circus just isn't the right place to be.</p><p>And the woman is Quirkstandard's aunt, Penelope Penultimate, a beautiful but severe lady of mature years who spent the majority of her life abroad taking parties of teenage girls on adventure holidays, with no insurance.</p><p>The story comes to a head when she issues an invitation to the men to come to her cottage in the country for the weekend. When they do so all manner of storylines come together, leading to unexpected revelations, arguments, jealousies, tensions, parlour games, picnics and nudity. Oh, it's so exciting.</p><p>Along the way the book is filled with historical and biographical asides as it covers the broad sweep of life from the sawdust circuses of the 1860s, through the Amazon Basin of the 1890s, right up to the ultra-modern trench-warfare of the 1910s. It is discursive and meandering in a way that makes it a particularly diminutive descendant of Tristram Shandy or Three Men In A Boat or something akin to Douglas Adams without the science-fiction. Some people like this sort of thing.</p><p>The author, A.F. Harrold, is a prize-winning performance poet, comedian and Englishman. More can be discovered at: <a href='http://www.afharrold.co.uk/>www.afharrold.co.uk</a>.</p>]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - A free podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>

