<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			Humorous podcasts novels.&nbsp; Brought to you by: podiobooks.com
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Curious Education of Epitome Quirkstandard]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-curious-education-of-epitome-quirkstandard/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-curious-education-of-epitome-quirkstandard/" text="<![CDATA[<p>The Curious Education of Epitome Quirkstandard - A free podcast novel by A. F. Harold]]>" description="<![CDATA[</p><p>This peculiar comic novel concerns two men and a woman and looks at how they came to be where they were when they met and the effect that meeting had upon them.</p><p>One man is Epitome Quirkstandard, a benighted aristocrat in the Wodehousian tradition whose staff have abandoned him to go and fight in the First World War and who discovers the taste for learning - especially when he attempts to make his own breakfast.</p><p>The other man is Mr. Crepuscular, a man who has written a multitude of educative pamphlets that he kindly rents out to Quirkstandard. As an illiterate scamp he ran away to join the circus, but through a series of unlikely adventures he ends up as a wise quasi-Buddhist who understands that sometimes the circus just isn't the right place to be.</p><p>And the woman is Quirkstandard's aunt, Penelope Penultimate, a beautiful but severe lady of mature years who spent the majority of her life abroad taking parties of teenage girls on adventure holidays, with no insurance.</p><p>The story comes to a head when she issues an invitation to the men to come to her cottage in the country for the weekend. When they do so all manner of storylines come together, leading to unexpected revelations, arguments, jealousies, tensions, parlour games, picnics and nudity. Oh, it's so exciting.</p><p>Along the way the book is filled with historical and biographical asides as it covers the broad sweep of life from the sawdust circuses of the 1860s, through the Amazon Basin of the 1890s, right up to the ultra-modern trench-warfare of the 1910s. It is discursive and meandering in a way that makes it a particularly diminutive descendant of Tristram Shandy or Three Men In A Boat or something akin to Douglas Adams without the science-fiction. Some people like this sort of thing.</p><p>The author, A.F. Harrold, is a prize-winning performance poet, comedian and Englishman. More can be discovered at: <a href='http://www.afharrold.co.uk/>www.afharrold.co.uk</a>.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[I Sold The Moon! (A True Story)]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/i-sold-the-moon/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[I Sold The Moon! (A True Story) - A free audiobook by Barry McArdle]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/i-sold-the-moon/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>I Sold The Moon! (A True Story)</h1><h3>by Barry McArdle</h3><p>Just because it happened, doesn&apos;t mean you&apos;ll believe it.&nbsp; Take a rollicking ride through the 1970s with the original Moon Man, Barry McArdle, a silver-suited street performer and comic philosopher who spent ten years crisscrossing America selling lunar real estate (transportation not provided). As told by the author,  I Sold the Moon!&nbsp; explores how a young man, fresh out of college, could get the idea that he could claim the moon, and then sell it.&nbsp; Exactly what drugs was he on?&nbsp; Well??..Moon Man&apos;s adventures are paralleled throughout by a more earthly concern: his romance with a young woman as adventurous as he, in the turbulent days of sex, drugs and rock &apos;n&apos; roll.&nbsp; The story of this &quot;first love&quot; is threaded from the opening chapter until the final page.&nbsp; I Sold The Moon!&nbsp; is for anyone who believes in following their dreams and searching for true love.&nbsp; It&apos;s cosmic, perceptive, passionate and fun.&nbsp; Mostly fun.&nbsp; Hear it here from the one, the only, the original Moon Man.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[8810]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/8810/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[8810 - A free audiobook by Nicholas Taylor]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/8810/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>8810</h1><h3>by Nicholas Taylor</h3><p>Join Bill Morison on his journey through corporate America, as he learns about auditing insurance and just how irritating people can be.&nbsp; This podcast contains office related humor, inspired by the author&apos;s experiences in navigating through corporate life.&nbsp; If you&apos;ve ever worked in an office with coworkers you just couldn&apos;t understand, you will find yourself reminiscing about that weird guy that always hung out at the water cooler.&nbsp; WARNING: The characters, names, and events in this podcast novel are purely fictional.&nbsp; Any reference to real people is purely coincidental.&nbsp; Should you think that you are represented in this podcast novel and have worked with the author, please see above.&nbsp; That being said, if you still having a nagging suspicion that you are depicted in this podcast novel and don&apos;t like your how your character is portrayed, think about how bad it must have been for the author working around you.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Fried Green Zombies]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/fried-green-zombies/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/fried-green-zombies/" text="<![CDATA[Fried Green Zombies - A free podcast novel by John Allen]]>" description="<![CDATA[<p>Chett and Harry are two recently unemployed construction workers on their way to a weekend of beer, Southern Comfort, and frog gigging at their musty-rusted 1970's RV parked at their favorite hunting camp when they stumble on Bob, the mysterious, busty, burqa-clad, non-English speaking beauty just standing in the middle of nowhere on the side of dusty Nine Mile Cutoff in rural Bovina, Mississippi.</p><p>Then all hell breaks loose. Their favorite pond is missing. They're being chased by truck driving zombies, dirty cops, UFOs and other ne'er-do-wells. Someone stole Chett's jacked up Scottsdale four-by-four. Zombies are traipsing around their trailer, and crazy Uncle Crank is trying to feed them zombie chicken for dinner.</p><p>Aided by a classic computer nerd, a crazy man wielding a frying pan, and a space babe who gets nekkid any time someone turns out the lights, follow Chett and Harry as they battle their way across the rural countryside and ultimately save the world.</p><p>Why is their pond missing, and why did the Dodge of Death spring from the muddy crater left in its center? Who is Bob and why is she so good with shotguns? Why are they being chased by two really skinny, pale, bald, goatee-clad wierdos? What is the dirty county sheriff hiding? And will Chett and Harry ever make it out alive?</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Odd Jobs]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/odd-jobs/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/odd-jobs/" text="<![CDATA[Odd Jobs - A free podcast novel by Karl Meade]]>" description="<![CDATA[Odd Jobs is a comic caper love story about Mountie women and layabout men, house and family, script-writers and cat-burglars. A modern tale of movie magic in the wrong hands: the Big Lebowski meets Elmore Leonard's niece.]]>"/>
	</body>
</opml>

