<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			Humorous podcasts novels.&nbsp; Brought to you by: podiobooks.com
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Fiddle and Burn]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/fiddle-and-burn-vol-1---the-adventures-of-coyote/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Fiddle and Burn, Vol. 1 - The Adventures of Coyote Man - A free audiobook by Jason Pomerantz]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/fiddle-and-burn-vol-1---the-adventures-of-coyote/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Fiddle and Burn</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Jason Pomerantz</h3><p>Part comedy.&nbsp; Part soap opera.&nbsp; A fiction blog.&nbsp; A serialized sit-com.&nbsp; A daily comic strip in prose.When Rantz takes a job as Circulation Director of Fiddle and Burn: Guide to Fandom Magazine, he hauls his family to a new home.&nbsp; None of them realizes that this will lead to one bizarre adventure after another.There&apos;s an epic struggle to throw away an old garbage can.There are embarrassing incidents involving a very rude laptop computer.There&apos;s a heroic quest to overcome parental objections and acquire an upgraded version of a violent computer game.There are profound metaphysical breakthroughs revealed in the dentist&apos;s chair.And, running through all the story lines, there&apos;s the strange figure of Coyote Man - Is he a noble superhero who defends the suburbs from vicious villains?&nbsp; Or is he a sad old man who lives in a dream world inside his head?&nbsp; It&apos;s a tale both comic and tragic, inspiring and pathetic.&nbsp; Some might even say...  quixotic.Whether it&apos;s comic book and science fiction fandom, the publishing industry or modern American family life, Fiddle and Burn squeezes out the humor and delivers it in easily digestible bite sized doses.Podcast Special:  Now including 75% more silly voices performed by the author!</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Fried Green Zombies]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/fried-green-zombies/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/fried-green-zombies/" text="<![CDATA[Fried Green Zombies - A free podcast novel by John Allen]]>" description="<![CDATA[<p>Chett and Harry are two recently unemployed construction workers on their way to a weekend of beer, Southern Comfort, and frog gigging at their musty-rusted 1970's RV parked at their favorite hunting camp when they stumble on Bob, the mysterious, busty, burqa-clad, non-English speaking beauty just standing in the middle of nowhere on the side of dusty Nine Mile Cutoff in rural Bovina, Mississippi.</p><p>Then all hell breaks loose. Their favorite pond is missing. They're being chased by truck driving zombies, dirty cops, UFOs and other ne'er-do-wells. Someone stole Chett's jacked up Scottsdale four-by-four. Zombies are traipsing around their trailer, and crazy Uncle Crank is trying to feed them zombie chicken for dinner.</p><p>Aided by a classic computer nerd, a crazy man wielding a frying pan, and a space babe who gets nekkid any time someone turns out the lights, follow Chett and Harry as they battle their way across the rural countryside and ultimately save the world.</p><p>Why is their pond missing, and why did the Dodge of Death spring from the muddy crater left in its center? Who is Bob and why is she so good with shotguns? Why are they being chased by two really skinny, pale, bald, goatee-clad wierdos? What is the dirty county sheriff hiding? And will Chett and Harry ever make it out alive?</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Odd Jobs]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/odd-jobs/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/odd-jobs/" text="<![CDATA[Odd Jobs - A free podcast novel by Karl Meade]]>" description="<![CDATA[Odd Jobs is a comic caper love story about Mountie women and layabout men, house and family, script-writers and cat-burglars. A modern tale of movie magic in the wrong hands: the Big Lebowski meets Elmore Leonard's niece.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Curious Education of Epitome Quirkstandard]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-curious-education-of-epitome-quirkstandard/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-curious-education-of-epitome-quirkstandard/" text="<![CDATA[<p>The Curious Education of Epitome Quirkstandard - A free podcast novel by A. F. Harold]]>" description="<![CDATA[</p><p>This peculiar comic novel concerns two men and a woman and looks at how they came to be where they were when they met and the effect that meeting had upon them.</p><p>One man is Epitome Quirkstandard, a benighted aristocrat in the Wodehousian tradition whose staff have abandoned him to go and fight in the First World War and who discovers the taste for learning - especially when he attempts to make his own breakfast.</p><p>The other man is Mr. Crepuscular, a man who has written a multitude of educative pamphlets that he kindly rents out to Quirkstandard. As an illiterate scamp he ran away to join the circus, but through a series of unlikely adventures he ends up as a wise quasi-Buddhist who understands that sometimes the circus just isn't the right place to be.</p><p>And the woman is Quirkstandard's aunt, Penelope Penultimate, a beautiful but severe lady of mature years who spent the majority of her life abroad taking parties of teenage girls on adventure holidays, with no insurance.</p><p>The story comes to a head when she issues an invitation to the men to come to her cottage in the country for the weekend. When they do so all manner of storylines come together, leading to unexpected revelations, arguments, jealousies, tensions, parlour games, picnics and nudity. Oh, it's so exciting.</p><p>Along the way the book is filled with historical and biographical asides as it covers the broad sweep of life from the sawdust circuses of the 1860s, through the Amazon Basin of the 1890s, right up to the ultra-modern trench-warfare of the 1910s. It is discursive and meandering in a way that makes it a particularly diminutive descendant of Tristram Shandy or Three Men In A Boat or something akin to Douglas Adams without the science-fiction. Some people like this sort of thing.</p><p>The author, A.F. Harrold, is a prize-winning performance poet, comedian and Englishman. More can be discovered at: <a href='http://www.afharrold.co.uk/>www.afharrold.co.uk</a>.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Wacky Misadventures of Warble McGorkle]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-wacky-misadventures-of-warble-mcgorkle/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Wacky Misadventures of Warble McGorkle - A free audiobook by Blackbird Crow Raven]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-wacky-misadventures-of-warble-mcgorkle/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Wacky Misadventures of Warble McGorkle</h1><h3>by Blackbird Crow Raven</h3><p>&quot;The Wacky Misadventures of Warble McGorkle&quot; is a picaresque satire that, through the protagonist&apos;s zany antics, pokes fun at the &apos;get rich quick&apos; and &apos;get rich by any means possible&apos; philosophies prevalent in today&apos;s society.Warble McGorkle considers himself a genius.&nbsp; In reality, he is a jumble-headed, paranoid megalomaniac.&nbsp; My novel is the (somewhat darkly) humorous account of his meteoric rise from drifter to President of the United States.&nbsp; Warble and his wife Mary crisscross the U.S.A.&nbsp; at breakneck speed, as Warble endeavors to stay one step ahead of pursuers (most of them imaginary). Everywhere he and Mary go, Warble concocts a cockamamie scheme to get fabulously rich and to propel himself to the pinnacle of society, where his fame--so he reasons, anyway--will make him safe from the forces supposedly arrayed against him.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Zany Time Travels of Warble McGorkle]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-zany-time-travels-of-warble-mcgorkle/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Zany Time Travels of Warble McGorkle - A free audiobook by Blackbird Crow Raven]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-zany-time-travels-of-warble-mcgorkle/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Zany Time Travels of Warble McGorkle</h1><h3>by Blackbird Crow Raven</h3><p>In &apos;The Zany Time Travels of Warble McGorkle&apos; (book II of a trilogy, and the first one recorded), Warble Poundcake McGorkle and his entourage (wife, employees, a sales team, and a canine) travel back in time to revise history.&nbsp; Their meddling in events during American Revolutionary War Times, at Custer&apos;s Last Stand, the Alamo, Woodstock, and  many other pivotal events--as well as a detour to 1st Century Jerusalem to kidnap Jesus (or Judas)--leads to catastrophic consequences for those living in modern times.&nbsp; Among the things Warble and his gang perpetrate are:1. Banishing George Washington to England for inventing the peanut (and thus being responsible for &apos;Peanut Envy&apos;)2. &apos;Helping out&apos; at the Alamo, so that it&apos;s the Mexicans who ultimately get &apos;saddled&apos; with Texas3. Originating Pre-emptive Strikes (umpires calling strikes before the ball is thrown)4. Changing song lyrics at Woodstock to influence the politics and modify the personalities of the concert-goers These are just a few of the outrageous shenanigans that culminate in a climactic scene as the protagonists return to the  present and see what their changes have wrought.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>

