<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>
			Humorous short-stories anthology podcasts.&nbsp; Brought to you by: podiobooks.com
		</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Fiddle and Burn]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/fiddle-and-burn-vol-1---the-adventures-of-coyote/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Fiddle and Burn, Vol. 1 - The Adventures of Coyote Man - A free audiobook by Jason Pomerantz]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/fiddle-and-burn-vol-1---the-adventures-of-coyote/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Fiddle and Burn</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Jason Pomerantz</h3><p>Part comedy.&nbsp; Part soap opera.&nbsp; A fiction blog.&nbsp; A serialized sit-com.&nbsp; A daily comic strip in prose.When Rantz takes a job as Circulation Director of Fiddle and Burn: Guide to Fandom Magazine, he hauls his family to a new home.&nbsp; None of them realizes that this will lead to one bizarre adventure after another.There&apos;s an epic struggle to throw away an old garbage can.There are embarrassing incidents involving a very rude laptop computer.There&apos;s a heroic quest to overcome parental objections and acquire an upgraded version of a violent computer game.There are profound metaphysical breakthroughs revealed in the dentist&apos;s chair.And, running through all the story lines, there&apos;s the strange figure of Coyote Man - Is he a noble superhero who defends the suburbs from vicious villains?&nbsp; Or is he a sad old man who lives in a dream world inside his head?&nbsp; It&apos;s a tale both comic and tragic, inspiring and pathetic.&nbsp; Some might even say...  quixotic.Whether it&apos;s comic book and science fiction fandom, the publishing industry or modern American family life, Fiddle and Burn squeezes out the humor and delivers it in easily digestible bite sized doses.Podcast Special:  Now including 75% more silly voices performed by the author!</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[A Brief Conversation with My Hair]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/a-brief-conversation-with-my-hair/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[A Brief Conversation with My Hair - A free audiobook by Russell Bradbury-Carlin]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/a-brief-conversation-with-my-hair/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>A Brief Conversation with My Hair</h1><h3>by Russell Bradbury-Carlin</h3><p>A Brief Conversation with My Hair is a collection of short literary humor pieces that have been previously featured on such websites at McSweeney&apos;s, Yankee Pot Roast, The Big Jewel, Opium Magazine, and The Science Creative Quarterly.&nbsp; Some of the titles (which may give you an idea of the content) are: &quot;The Calls of Cthulu&quot;, &quot;All I Need to Learn, I Learned From Kindergarten Cop&quot;, &quot;Diary of a Grocery Cart&quot;, &quot;Dionysus: Party Clown&quot;, and &quot;A Brief Conversation with My Hair&quot;.  The forty-plus pieces in this collection find the bizarre in the everyday or some bit of the everyday in the already bizarre.&nbsp; If you ever wondered if Allen Ginsburg could have put his considerable talent to writing pay-per-click ads or how Calvin and Hobbes may have responded to reading Hemingway, you will find the answers here.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>

