<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Magical Realism podcast novels from Podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Pieces]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/pieces/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Pieces - A free podcast novel compiled by Nobilis]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/pieces/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Pieces - A free audiobook compiled by Nobilis</h1><p>Joan&&apos;s world has literally fallen apart.&nbsp; She lives in one tiny piece of the shattered universe, bounded on all sides by shimmering veils.&nbsp; When the creator god, calling himself &quot;Cassius&quot;, stumbles into the cathedral where she lives, she is drawn into an adventure of cosmic proportions.&nbsp; The story is told through the cracked lens of seven experienced podcast authors.&nbsp; Nobilis, Christiana Ellis, Chris Lester, Graydancer, Paul S.&nbsp; Jenkins, Philippa Ballantine, Brandon Crose and John Tanzer take turns, chapter by chapter writing and reading episodes of the story.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Purgatory]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/purgatory/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Purgatory - A free audiobook by Tim Dodge]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/purgatory/" description="<![CDATA[Charles Cunningham, a wealthy real estate developer, dies unexpectedly and finds himself in Purgatory, the place between heaven and hell.&nbsp; Though depressed about his early death, he befriends two other souls doing time there - the writer: &quot;Edgar Allan Poe&quot; and a music-loving deadbeat: &quot;Billy&quot;.&nbsp; Upon receiving a letter from God telling him he must learn some unnamed lessons before he can go to heaven, he convinces Poe to join him in the portal back to earth.&nbsp; They hope to make up for their past mistakes, but they arrive on earth in the year 2049, 42 years after Charles&apos; death.&nbsp; Traveling from mid-21st century New York City to Las Vegas, Charles seeks out the daughter he neglected in life, though she is now in her eighties.&nbsp; However, an unfriendly soul from Purgatory follows them to earth.&nbsp; This soul, an employee with whom Charles had an affair and summarily fired, is determined to keep him from winning passage to heaven.&nbsp; She teams up with Charles&apos; grandson, a debt-ridden gambling addict who has a talent for messing things up.&nbsp; Together, they hatch a deadly scheme to foil Charles&apos; plan to get to heaven and net the grandson badly-needed money.&nbsp; Charles learns of their plans and enlists his friends to help stop them.&nbsp; Will they succeed?&nbsp; The only way to find out is to subscribe.]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by .  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
