<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Mystery podcast novels from Podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Casebook of D.I. Snaith]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-casebook-of-di-snaith/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Casebook of D.I. Snaith - A free audiobook by Dan Evans]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-casebook-of-di-snaith/" description="<![CDATA[The first compilation of the adventures of England's most peerless pig, Detective Inspector Snaith. Cracking crime in a Britain just a few years in the future Snaith works alongside his colleagues the body-dismorphic-disordered D.I. Wilton, the surgically pixillated D.I. Harris and their boss-stroke-guvnor, the Gaffer. In spite of a crippling addiction to cocktails, and the most machiavellian of ex wives Snaith always gets results. Whatever it takes and by any means necessary. He may be a bad man... but he's a damn good copper.Hard boiled, humorous, and just a little surreal.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Eye Of The Storm]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-eye-of-the-storm/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Eye Of The Storm - A free audiobook by Jeffrey Lynn Stoddard ]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-eye-of-the-storm/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Eye Of The Storm</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Jeffrey Lynn Stoddard </h3><p>Dante Dre, a 38 year old single gay man, awakens one morning to a terrifying discovery that implicates him in a horrendous crime. But that's only the beginning. As the day progresses he soon discovers outside forces complicating matters even more and this leads to a night of sheer terror. The clock is ticking. Can he manage to stay alive long enough to find out what really happened and clear his name?</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The May Day Murders]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/may-day-murders/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The May Day Murders - A free audiobook by Scott Wittenburg]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/may-day-murders/" description="<![CDATA[The autumnal tranquility of Smithtown, Ohio is shattered when Dr. David Bradley arrives home to find that his wife has been raped and murdered by an intruder who has left no clues behind except the words "May Day" painted in lipstick on his victim's body. When the police later learn that another Smithtown resident has been raped and strangled in her New York City apartment, it becomes frighteningly clear that a cunning serial killer targeting Smithtown women is on the prowl.Newspaper reporter Sam Middleton is determined to help Detective Roger Hagstrom track down the assailant of his ex-wife's best friend. Sam can only hope that his estranged wife and teenage daughter are out of harm's way living hours away in the Columbus suburb of Woodcrest.  One terrifying question continues to gnaw at Sam as the mystery unfolds: Who will the killer's next victim be?]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Echoes]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/echoes/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Echoes - A free audiobook by Nathan P Butler]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/echoes/" description="<![CDATA[It begins with a murder in an Atlanta hotel room. There is no DNA. There are no fingerprints. There are only the victim&apos;s ties to two powerful men: one a senator, the other a high-ranking aide to the President of the United States.Amid an unfamiliar landscape of D.C. politics, Atlanta Homicide Detective Darren Fox must seek out a killer who leaves no trace, discover secrets long buried, and come face to face with one of America&apos;s darkest secrets and most dangerous truths...]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Virtual Vice]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/virtual-vice/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Virtual Vice - a free podcast novel by Jason M.  Kays]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/virtual-vice/" description="<![CDATA[Follow disillusioned entertainment attorney Ian McKenzie as his professional life takes a decided turn for the questionable when he is hired by the charismatic and dangerous Scott White to represent Scott's interests in his cutting edge Internet startup, Metropoleis Multimedia.  Unfortunately for Ian, Scott has more in common with Scarface's Tony Montana than Apple's Steve Jobs, and things go from questionable to deadly in no time flat.  As Scott's confidant and consigliore, Ian soon finds himself caught between the Feds, La Cosa Nostra, and the Cali Cartel in a fatal game of corporate winner-take-all.  Kays masterfully weaves the nuts and bolts of legal maneuverings and corporate worst-practices into an engaging and unpredictable thrill ride of a crime novel.  Filled with wry humor and twists and turns galore, Virtual Vice keeps you guessing and wanting more while entertaining every step of the way.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Corporate Warfare]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/corporate-warfare/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Corporate Warfare - a free podcast novel by Kris Davis]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/corporate-warfare/" description="<![CDATA[Romance underlines Corporate Warfare - a fast paced novel that deals with corporations bidding on a US proposal.  A scheming foreign conglomerate has other intentions.  With their international genetic patents secured, Project Abacus&apos; success now hinges on the exploitation of the proposal to realize a unique human identification system.  A genetic social security number.  And corporate espionage entangles the love triangles.  But with Anthony's hands tied will fate prevail?]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[See Tom Run]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/see-tom-run/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/see-tom-run/" text="<![CDATA[See Tom Run - A free audiobook by Scott Wittenburg]]>" description="<![CDATA[In this podiobook: Tom Grayson returns home from a quick errand to discover that his family and guests have all mysteriously disappeared. Prior to this chilling discovery, he has been tormented with guilt by a secret that only he and a former lover share: the two have witnessed a brutal crime that Tom has refused to report. He knows that alerting the authorities would jeopardize all that he holds dear in life: his family and career. In a desperate search to find his missing family, Tom embarks on a journey that can only be described as nightmarish and surreal. When it becomes increasingly clear that Tom may lose something even more precious than his comfortable existence, his priorities in life shift dramatically as he becomes an unwitting detective with a mission. But will it be too late for him to set the record straight?]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Serve It Cold]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/serve-it-cold/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Serve It Cold - a free audiobook by Ronnie Blackwell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/serve-it-cold/" description="<![CDATA[Detective Jonny C.  Speed's life can't get much better.  He's booked into the  French Quarter's most luxurious guesthouse, and his day job as convenience store manager is 104 miles behind him in Catherine, Mississippi.  He's already taken care of one pro-bono missing persons job since he's been in New Orleans, and his paying client's cheating wife is a beautiful and very accommodating exhibitionist.  Are things too good to be true? Of course they are.  Jonny starts to worry when his client turns up dead, but when the suspects start dropping, Jonny and his crack team of beauty queens, recovering addicts, professional athletes, computer hackers, and pampered dogs find themselves caught in a twisted scheme of revenge that threatens to turn the town of Catherine inside out.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[hackoff.com]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/hackoff/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[hackoff.com - A free audiobook by Tom Elvsin]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/hackoff/" description="<![CDATA[Larry Lazard, CEO of hackoff.com, takes his company public and watches its stock price soar and collapse.  Following a hostile takeover attempt, Lazard is found dead in his office of an apparently self-inflicted gunshot wound.  Author Tom Evslin, a serial CEO, also took a company public in the Internet bubble and fought off hostile takeover attempts in the subsequent rubble.  Unlike Larry, Evslin lived to tell what may be the definitive story of those strange times.  The mystery moves backwards and forwards around the time of Larry&apos;s death.  If you&apos;ve ever wanted to be a fly on the wall of the boardrooms, private jets, and ornate meeting rooms of brokerage firms, hackoff.com gives you your chance.  You&apos;ll be better prepared for the next bubble if you read this book but that&apos;s not why you&apos;ll eagerly download each online episode.  You&apos;ll do that because the cleverly woven mystery will have you dying to know whodunit.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The May Day Murders]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/may-day-murders/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The May Day Murders - A free audiobook by Scott Wittenburg]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/may-day-murders/" description="<![CDATA[The autumnal tranquility of Smithtown, Ohio is shattered when Dr.  David Bradley arrives home to find that his wife has been raped and murdered by an intruder who has left no clues behind except the words &quot;May Day&quot; painted in lipstick on his victim's body.  When the police later learn that another Smithtown resident has been raped and strangled in her New York City apartment, it becomes frighteningly clear that a cunning serial killer targeting Smithtown women is on the prowl.Newspaper reporter Sam Middleton is determined to help Detective Roger Hagstrom track down the assailant of his ex-wife's best friend.  Sam can only hope that his estranged wife and teenage daughter are out of harm's way living hours away in the Columbus suburb of Woodcrest.  One terrifying question continues to gnaw at Sam as the mystery unfolds: Who will the killer's next victim be?]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Onion Files]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-onion-files/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Onion Files - A free audiobook by Val Pattee]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-onion-files/" description="<![CDATA[Former NATO intelligence chief writes cyberterrorism spy thriller -- Major General Val Pattee's novel lauded as compelling and a &quot;tutorial for homeland security personnel&quot;.  Suppose al-Qaeda had a second, potentially more devastating attack planned in 2001.  How would it be thwarted? &quot;The Onion Files&quot; is a spy thriller differing from all previous novels in one very important aspect: author Val Pattee was one of the Western world's top spy masters.  Serving as chief of intelligence for NATO in Europe during periods of Cold War-era terrorism, he worked with the heads of intelligence for sixteen member nations, and conferred with his Soviet and Red Chinese counterparts.Although &quot;The Onion Files&quot; is fiction, Pattee infuses the action with a realism of people and places only an insider could deliver.  The title refers to an ingenious and diabolical plot by al-Qaeda to devastate vast areas of the United States soon after the 9/11 attacks.  Pattee introduces readers to protagonists Jim and Mark Buchan, who work with the US Central Intelligence Agency and Russian counter-terrorism units in a fast-paced hunt across three continents to halt a computer virus and its brilliant creator.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Theft of the Master]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/theft-of-the-master/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Theft of the Master - A free audiobook by Edwin Alexander]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/theft-of-the-master/" description="<![CDATA[Theft of the Master has been described as the Boys from Brazil meets The Da Vinci Code -KirkusPrivate Investigator Al Hershey takes the reader across the globe in his search for a young woman's killer.  Hired by the girl's parents to look into her &quot;accidental&quot; death Al finds he is in the middle of a more than a murder investigation.Modern day Nazis and a stolen renaissance sculpture all play a part in this intricate character driven tale of promises and deceit.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Faithful Warrior]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/faithful-warrior/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Faithful Warrior - A free audiobook by Basil Sands]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/faithful-warrior/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Faithful Warrior</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Basil Sands</h3><p>Pastor Michael Farris was a well loved man.&nbsp; Loving husband and father, Shepherd of his church, Courageous minister to the inner city gangs of Columbus Ohio.&nbsp; He helped people change their lives for the better.&nbsp; But when his peaceful life is suddenly shattered by a senseless drive by shooting, a side of Pastor Farris that almost no one knew comes to the surface...a violent shadow of a life that he had been able to keep secret all these years.&nbsp; As he seeks to right the crimes committed against him he is unexpectedly confronted by a ghost from his past, and Mike Farris suddenly finds himself in a race against the clock to stop an insane terrorist from killing thousands, maybe even millions in one fell swoop.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
