<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Romantic podnovels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Romance Novels Podcast]]>" xmlUrl="http://romancepodcast.com/podcasts/rss/podcast.xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Romance Novels Podcast @ <a href='http://romancepodcast.com/'>Romance Podcast.Com</a>]]>" htmlUrl="http://romancepodcast.com/" description="<![CDATA[Every two weeks, we upload a new chapter of an original romance story in mp3 format.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Sweet Dreams]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/sweet-dreams/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Sweet Dreams]]>" htmlUrl="http://sweetdreamsnovel.com/" description="<![CDATA[At twenty-one, Rob Malloy is a successful San Francisco entertainment manager and has achieved more than most men twice his age. Wealthy and famous for closing any deal, he may seem to have everything a man could want. However, he longs to meet a woman he can share his life with. Victoria Knox is a poor eighteen year old student who dreams of nothing but becoming a singer. Dating is the last thing on her mind when she accidentally bumps into Rob in an airport gift shop on Christmas day. Instant attraction draws them to one another, despite their different lifestyles. Looking as if he stepped out of a GQ ad, Rob exudes high class and money. Victoria is convinced he is too good for her, but Rob is immediately attracted to how she freely shares her innocently opinionated views. He likes her down to earth personality that is such a breath of fresh air compared to the gold digging socialites he is normally plagued with.In this love story, Rob introduces Victoria to a high society world where she meets the rich and famous. For the first time she dares to believe her dream of becoming a singing star is possible through Rob&apos;s industry connections. However, Rob is different from anyone she has ever met and she fears she won&apos;t fit into his world. Her mother adds fuel to Victoria&apos;s misgivings by questioning Rob&apos;s intentions. Though sincere, Rob may have trouble convincing his country club parents that Victoria is a proper match. Join Rob and Victoria as they battle social class lines, parental disapproval and ghosts from their pasts to prove that their love is meant to last.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Crazy Gone Love]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/crazy-gone-love/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Crazy Gone Love - a free audiobook by Cate Brody]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/crazy-gone-love/" description="<![CDATA[Ceil Clark is fed up with dating the twenty-something hipsters and slackers that litter the streets of Los Angeles nightlife like empty, discarded cans of Red Bull. Against the wise advice of her best friend, Lupe, she makes a pre-meditated decision to seduce, tag and bag her newest boss---Wayne Hayter; the cool and always collected thirty-something, corporate-loving, sports-car-driving, designer duds wearing, General Manager of the Porsche dealership where Ceil merely tolerates her 9 to 5 gig.But when a deliciously cute, mysterious and vaguely wild-eyed musician by the name of Mason Philips begins to crop up almost daily in and around the parking lot adjacent to her job just to chat---Ceil is intrigued---though he is just 'another loser in a garage band'. Suddenly, the stoic and unruffled Wayne Hayter has some serious competition to contend with almost before his flirtation with Ceil manages to get off the ground. But Mason Phillips---with his cheerful positive outlook, pit bull-like tenacity and an unwillingness to hear the word 'no'--- has a couple of tricks up his sleeve to keep the ball in his court. By the end, Ceil's only wish is to keep her hair from turning white before she has a chance to choose between her two dream suitors.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Star Struck]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/star-struck/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Star Struck - A free audiobook by Emmy Z. Madrigal]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/star-struck/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Star Struck</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Emmy Z. Madrigal</h3><p>This is the second book in the Sweet Dreams series.&nbsp; Three days is not very long, but to Victoria, who&apos;s been away from her new love Rob Malloy, it seems like forever.&nbsp; Returning from Colorado, Victoria reconnects with her friends, finding one particular friend isn&apos;t too happy about her having a high society boyfriend.&nbsp; Imagine waking from a nap to find your favorite boy band star sitting in the chair across from you.&nbsp; That&apos;s what happens to Cynthia Porter.&nbsp; She can hardly believe she isn&apos;t dreaming when Derek Montgomery shows up at Rob&apos;s apartment.&nbsp; The initial shock gives way to real mutual admiration as they spend time together.&nbsp; Unfortunately, it seems Derek&apos;s old girlfriend haunts him too much to let go.&nbsp; Will Cynthia ever find a guy who is completely into her?&nbsp; Or will she constantly be the friend and counselor to these screwed up males?&nbsp; Music provided by: Neil MacPherson, Brad Wait and Pleasure Trip.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
