<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Present Day Sci-Fi Podnovels from Podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Singularity]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/singularity/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Singularity - a free podcast novel by Bill DeSmedt]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/singularity/" description="<![CDATA[<p><b>What if</b> the cataclysmic Tunguska explosion of 1908 was caused, not by a meteor or a comet, but by a microscopic black hole?</p><p><b>What if</b>  that fantastic object - smaller than an atom, older than the stars, heavier than a mountain - is still down there, orbiting deep inside the earth, slowly consuming the planet?</p><p><b>What if</b>  only a rookie government agent and an uncannily-insightful consultant stand between a renegade Russian billionaire and his plans to use the black hole to change history - or end it?</p><p><b>What if</b>  it's all true?</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Traitor]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/traitor/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Traitor Book One of The Turner Chonicles - a free podcast novel by Mark Eller]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/traitor/" description="<![CDATA[Last Chance - a small town set on the edge of the far frontier.&nbsp; It is a place of gentle manners and common civility.&nbsp; After all, it should be since more than three quarters of its residents are women.&nbsp; However times change when a Talent Master runs rampant, savages threaten war, and an illegal militia from an alternate universe plans invasion and empire.&nbsp; A hero is needed.&nbsp; A Savior.&nbsp; Meet Aaron Turner, the small unassuming man who runs the Last Chance General Store.&nbsp; He is this town&&apos;s&mdash;this world&&apos;s&mdash;only hope.&nbsp; Unfortunately for the town, Aaron also happens to be a soldier and Militia spy whose job is to prepare the ground for the Militia&&apos;s invasion.&nbsp; To help him with this task, he has a cellar filled with advanced weaponry and the unique ability to teleport between the two worlds.&nbsp; However after a year of living within Last Chance, Aaron is no longer sure in which direction his loyalties lie.]]>"/>
	</body>
</opml>

