<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Mystery podcast novels from Podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Borrowed Time]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/borrowed-time/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Borrowed Time - A free audiobook by Keith Hughes]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/borrowed-time/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Borrowed Time</h1><p>Ness Relevant is living on borrowed time.&nbsp; Molecular implosion, cellular degeneration, and dangerous men are but a few of the perils faced by the friendly and unassuming forensic photographer.His quiet bachelorhood is interrupted when he receives an innocent looking device in the mail from a friend and former college professor.&nbsp; Ness unexpectedly finds himself embroiled in events driven by his friend&apos;s success.&nbsp; This device is the focal point of a struggle that could overturn the whole world should Ness or his friend&apos;s invention fall prey to greedy men.&nbsp; Before his time runs out Ness must travel back to an uncomfortable past to prevent an unthinkable future.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Grey]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/grey/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Grey - A free audiobook by Jon Armstrong]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/grey/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Grey</h1><p>High fashion, corporate malfeasance, celebrity culture, and an obsessed media collide with exuberant violence and volatile intensity in Grey, the explosive debut novel by Jon Armstrong.</p><p>For Michael Rivers, life is perfect.&nbsp; Michael has everything; tall, handsome, and famous, he is worshipped by billions of fans around the globe.&nbsp; He is wealthy beyond measure, the heir apparent to RiverGroup, one of the handful of high-tech corporations that controls the world.&nbsp; He is fashionable, setting trends with his wardrobe of immaculate designer suits, each a unique and celebrated work of art.&nbsp; And Michael is in love, perfect love, sharing a private language based entirely on quotes from the latest fashion magazine advertisements, with Nora, his beautiful, witty, and equally perfect fiance, the only woman with whom he can see surgically-altered monochromatic eye to eye.</p><p>When an assassin&apos;s bullets pierce Michael&apos;s body before the unblinking eyes of cameras, reporters, and viewers at a press junket, everything changes, forcing Michael to question everything about his previously perfect world.&nbsp; Illusions shattered and forcibly separated from Nora, Michael seeks to uncover the reasons behind the attempted assassination, embarking on a quest that leads him to question his relationships with his loud, profane, and narcissistically Ultra father; his estranged mother; and the perilous, contaminated, neo-feudalistic world that lies beyond the safe and protected bubble of corporate family life.</p><p>Michael must delve deep into his past, finding that all paths he uncovers seem to lead to the now-closed PartyHaus, and to a time when he was the golden boy, dancing furiously to the beat of notorious all-night Rage parties thrown by his father.</p>]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>

