<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Sci-Fi podcast novels from Podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" type="link" text="<![CDATA[]]>" url="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Time Crime]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/time-crime/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Time Crime from &#039;Astounding Tales, published Feb-March 1955&#039; - a free podcast novel by H. Beam Piper; narrated by Nathan Lowell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/time-crime/" description="<![CDATA[<center>From Astounding Tales Published February and March 1955</center><p>The Paratime Police had a real headache this time! Tracing one man in a population of millions is easy—compared to finding one gang hiding out on one of billions of probability lines!</p><p>This story from 1955 has rocket ships, time travel, slaves, post-hypnotic suggestions, drugged citizens, and a complete disregard for human rights. And those are the good guys. As a look back in time at &quot;classic&quot; science fiction, it's an interesting snapshot of a time when tobacco was common, sexism was unconscious, and female characters were a long way from Lara Croft.</p><center>Narrated by Nathan Lowell.</center>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Singularity]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/singularity/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Singularity - a free podcast novel by Bill DeSmedt]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/singularity/" description="<![CDATA[<p><b>What if</b> the cataclysmic Tunguska explosion of 1908 was caused, not by a meteor or a comet, but by a microscopic black hole?</p><p><b>What if</b>  that fantastic object - smaller than an atom, older than the stars, heavier than a mountain - is still down there, orbiting deep inside the earth, slowly consuming the planet?</p><p><b>What if</b>  only a rookie government agent and an uncannily-insightful consultant stand between a renegade Russian billionaire and his plans to use the black hole to change history - or end it?</p><p><b>What if</b>  it's all true?</p>]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
