<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Super Hero podcast novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Anon Time]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/anon-time/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Anon Time - A free audiobook by Craig Robertson]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/anon-time/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Anon Time</h1><h3>by Craig Robertson</h3><p>What if you weren&apos;t who you thought you were, what others saw you to be?&nbsp; What if the structure of time depended on you to keep it steady.&nbsp; What if unseen forces, both good and evil, surrounded you, effecting your life in way&apos;s you could not begin to imagine?&nbsp; Well, if that were the case, you&apos;d be Mark De Martel, unobtrusive advertising agent in Los Angeles.&nbsp; Or would you?&nbsp; Possibly you were a Mark, but possibly you would be a powerful warrior, using skills such as the manipulation of gravity itself to save existence.&nbsp; The answer can be found by listening to Anon Time.&nbsp; It is a science fiction formatted novel with philosophical and spiritual underpinnings guaranteed to whisk you on an adventure of wondrous scope and amazing clarity.&nbsp; Treat yourself to this fantastic story, trust us, you deserve it.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Son of Man]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-son-of-man/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Son of Man - A free audiobook by CW Johnson]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-son-of-man/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Son of Man</h1><h3>A free audiobook by CW Johnson</h3><p>Imagine they set out to clone the Son of God.Imagine they succeed...The Holy Blood Altar, an elaborate shrine whose centerpiece is said to contain three drops of Jesus Christ&apos;s blood, has for centuries adorned the west choir within the walls of a small, unassuming Catholic cathedral in Rothenberg, Germany.&nbsp; From the time of the Middle Ages the cathedral was little more than a tiny rest stop along the pilgrimage to Santiago de Compostela until an amazing confirmation was made there.&nbsp; The capsule within the shrine did indeed contain human blood.When the blood was tested and found to match a sample of tissue taken from the Shroud of Turin, the Vatican, fearing desecration of the altar, immediately put an end to all testing and ordered the story suppressed.&nbsp; A powerful group of Catholic clergymen, believing their intervention would bring about the second coming of Christ, defy the Church.&nbsp; Starting small at first and building in numbers, they, together with prominent financial and political figures, resurrect an ancient, covert alliance known as &apos;In hoc signo vinces.&apos; (In this, be victorious.) Although forbidden by both papal and international law, the group has but one goal: with the budding new science of bio-reanimation, it plans to clone Jesus Christ, regardless the cost.&nbsp; Maria Rose, Jewish student and legendary UCLA campus beauty, is chosen to be the surrogate mother.&nbsp; Staggeringly beautiful, she is also strong willed and conniving, pulling fellow student Todd Riley into the fray in order to fulfill a &apos;Vinces&apos; stipulation: The child must have both a surrogate mother and father.From the moment the project begins, strange things start to happen:Nobel laureate Doctor James Donahue, who vehemently rejected any involvement in the project, has a supernatural visitation in his hotel room.A homeless, delusional schizophrenic inexplicably finds clarity, proclaims himself the champion of the only begotten son of the father, and becomes Brother Michael, a force to be reckoned with.A man in the final stages of rabies sits up in his hospital bed and delivers an ominous message, which is followed by a monstrous, worldwide earthquake.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
