<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Sci-Fi Fantasy Podnovels from Podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[<h1>The Chameleon Chronicles</h1>]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-chameleon-chronicles/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[<h2>The Chameleon Chronicles: Prisoner of Tim</h2><h3>a free audiobook by Andrew S. Leiter</h3>]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-chameleon-chronicles/" description="<![CDATA[<h2>The Chameleon Chronicles</h2><h3>a free audiobook by Andrew S. Leiter</h3><p>Andrew Webbur's journey of Fate begins when he is confronted by his long time nemesis, Jason Vanzant. Jason accuses Andrew of stealing his girlfriend and confronts him with violent repercussions.</p><p>Mr. Spieker, the principal of Calumet Bay High, also seems to be on the warpath with Andrew in his sights. Neither Mr. Spieker nor Jason Vanzant compare to the butterflies in Andrew's stomach, as he wrestles with his feelings for Bethany Mogg.</p><p>As if Andrew didn't have enough problems, he begins receiving mysterious; &quot;I know who you are&quot; messages. The mysterious stalker seems to know about Andrew's secret abilities. To save the future, Andrew and his friends must discover, &quot;Who is Stalking Andrew?&quot;</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[<h1>The Chameleon Chronicles: Colors of Fate</h1>]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-chameleon-chronicles-prisoner-of-time/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[<h2>The Chameleon Chronicles: Prisoner of Tim</h2><h3>a free audiobook by Andrew S. Leiter</h3>]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-chameleon-chronicles-prisoner-of-time/" description="<![CDATA[<h2>The Chameleon Chronicles: Prisoner of Tim</h2><h3>a free audiobook by Andrew S. Leiter</h3><p>Andrew Webbur and his friends must serve their Saturday detention the day after the big homecoming dance. Intent on finding Brian’s parents, Andrew and Brian must sneak out of school without Mr. Spieker discovering their absence. The Chameleon discovers more than he bargained for when he finds a hidden island full of powerful Izmite terrorists.</p><p>Jodi Webbur’s powers began failing, when reality begins crumbling around her and she can’t decipher if she is living in the past, present, or future.</p><p>Jim Jones Brawn unleashes the second phase of his plan to destroy Andrew by releasing his newest weapon against the Chameleon. Striking from the shadows, this new menace seems intent on destroying Andrew and his friends. Who is this new threat that frightens even Landru Brawn?</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Amerindian 2192]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/amerindian-2192/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Amerindian 2192 - a free audiobook by J. Scott Garibay]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/amerindian-2192/" description="<![CDATA[AmerIndian 2192 is a science-fiction novel that explores the intriguing possibilities of Native Americans in mankind's star flung future. AmerIndian 2192 presents the story of two brothers, Wovoka and Keokuk, restoring the Native American people to a Homeland where their vibrant culture can thrive. Lodge ships, Cybershaman rituals and Tsimshian high technology are all elements in this action-oriented tale of interstellar politics and personal struggles.]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free audiobook by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
