<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Short Story Collections &amp; Anthologies</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Town Without a Soul and Other Stories]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/town-without-a-soul/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Town Without a Soul and Other Stories - A free audiobook by Andrew Culver and Josh Charney]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/town-without-a-soul/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Town Without a Soul and Other Stories</h1><h3>by Andrew Culver and Josh Charney</h3><p>Andrew Culver and Josh Charney have combined their talents to bring you a listening experience like no other - music and narration perfectly combined to create a complete immersion in a fictional world. In these dark tales, a young girl realizes her mother has changed into something terrible; a man arrives in an ominous town and receives an offer too good to turn down; another man on a space station accepts a nasty job because the money is too good to resist; and a third man seeks revenge - or does revenge seek him? Get ready to enter a world in which man is inches away from his own downfall. Get ready for Existent Domain.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Aliens and Satanic Creatures Wanted: Humans Need Not Apply]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/aliens-and-satanic-creatures-wanted-humans-need-no/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Aliens and Satanic Creatures Wanted: Humans Need Not Apply - A free audiobook by Tony Ruggiero]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/aliens-and-satanic-creatures-wanted-humans-need-no/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Aliens and Satanic Creatures Wanted: Humans Need Not Apply</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Tony Ruggiero</h3><p>Do you think its easy being an alien, a satanic creature or anything else not considered part of the Homo sapiens only club?&nbsp; They have tough days just like humans do and their frustration is growing.&nbsp; Don&apos;t believe it?&nbsp; Well, what about Lucifer, the prince of darkness, who runs a car dealership--what about his feelings when he is faced with that impossible sale and he can&apos;t get that signature on form 666, the standard soul contract?&nbsp; Or maybe you wondered about how an extremely vain alien copes with having a bad hair day as he tries to alter the future of Earth?&nbsp; Will his cosmetic problems be our problems in other ways?&nbsp; Perhaps you heard about the opposite vampire who loves to give blood, hates the darkness and has a fetish for garlic - how does he get through a bad relationship?&nbsp; How about a DNA altered cat that has been given the personality of one of the world&apos;s most fearsome criminals?&nbsp; Will its human owners understand or will it be a less then purr-fect arrangement?&nbsp; What&apos;s the common thread do all this discontent, you ask?&nbsp; What is it about most stories that stay the same?&nbsp; It&apos;s the human!&nbsp; These aliens and demonic creatures are sick and tired of being the second fiddle in the story.&nbsp; They want what everybody wants: to be the center of attention of the stories instead of the pesky humans for a change...and now they finally get their wish.&nbsp; In Aliens and Satanic Creatures Wanted: Humans Need Not Apply, they finally get top billing and they exploit it as far as they can. </p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Serving Worlds]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/serving-worlds/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Serving Worlds - a free audiobook by John Mierau]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/serving-worlds/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Serving Worlds - a free audiobook by John Mierau</h1><p><p>A cowboy on the run to keep his soul.&nbsp; A vampire running a Nigerian investor scam.&nbsp; A wolf racing to the mountaintop, before a dragon can catch and kill him.&nbsp; A human protecting one of the aliens he fought in war, from an old army buddy.&nbsp; Meet these and other characters in Serving Worlds, the genre-blending podcast fiction collection from John Mierau.&nbsp; Weekly episodes are 20 minutes or less but Beware: there be cliffhangers here!</p></p>]]>"/>
	</body>
</opml>
