<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Short Story Collections &amp; Anthologies</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Voices of New Media Fiction]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/voices-new-media-fiction/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Voices of New Media Fiction - A free audiobook edited by Mur Lafferty]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/voices-new-media-fiction/" description="<![CDATA[New Media Fiction brings together the pioneer short fiction podcasters.&nbsp; Experimenting from putting short-short fiction to novellas over their podcasts, these writers were the first to test the new medium for storytelling.&nbsp; Some wrote specifically for podcasts, some read previously published fiction, and some read entirely new stories.&nbsp; Some listeners asked if they could get just the stories in audio form, and that request brought about this podiobook.&nbsp; Cory Doctorow tells us a story about a post-apocalyptic government run by sysadmins and James Patrick Kelly narrates a story of a strange reconciliation.&nbsp; We've collected 18 stories for you, the first short fiction to go out over podcast, and look forward to bringing you more.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Podioracket Presents - Visionaries]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/podioracket-presents-visionaries/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Podioracket Presents: Visionaries - A free short stories anthology from Podiobooks.com authors]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/podioracket-presents-visionaries/" description="<![CDATA[Podioracket Presents-Visionaries is a collection of short stories by Podiobooks.com authors collected by H.E. Roulo and Brian Holtz.&nbsp; The stories are a mix of genre from some of Podiobooks.com&apos;s best authors.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Aliens and Satanic Creatures Wanted: Humans Need Not Apply]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/aliens-and-satanic-creatures-wanted-humans-need-no/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Aliens and Satanic Creatures Wanted: Humans Need Not Apply - A free audiobook by Tony Ruggiero]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/aliens-and-satanic-creatures-wanted-humans-need-no/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Aliens and Satanic Creatures Wanted: Humans Need Not Apply</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Tony Ruggiero</h3><p>Do you think its easy being an alien, a satanic creature or anything else not considered part of the Homo sapiens only club?&nbsp; They have tough days just like humans do and their frustration is growing.&nbsp; Don&apos;t believe it?&nbsp; Well, what about Lucifer, the prince of darkness, who runs a car dealership--what about his feelings when he is faced with that impossible sale and he can&apos;t get that signature on form 666, the standard soul contract?&nbsp; Or maybe you wondered about how an extremely vain alien copes with having a bad hair day as he tries to alter the future of Earth?&nbsp; Will his cosmetic problems be our problems in other ways?&nbsp; Perhaps you heard about the opposite vampire who loves to give blood, hates the darkness and has a fetish for garlic - how does he get through a bad relationship?&nbsp; How about a DNA altered cat that has been given the personality of one of the world&apos;s most fearsome criminals?&nbsp; Will its human owners understand or will it be a less then purr-fect arrangement?&nbsp; What&apos;s the common thread do all this discontent, you ask?&nbsp; What is it about most stories that stay the same?&nbsp; It&apos;s the human!&nbsp; These aliens and demonic creatures are sick and tired of being the second fiddle in the story.&nbsp; They want what everybody wants: to be the center of attention of the stories instead of the pesky humans for a change...and now they finally get their wish.&nbsp; In Aliens and Satanic Creatures Wanted: Humans Need Not Apply, they finally get top billing and they exploit it as far as they can. </p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Serving Worlds]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/serving-worlds/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Serving Worlds - a free audiobook by John Mierau]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/serving-worlds/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Serving Worlds - a free audiobook by John Mierau</h1><p><p>A cowboy on the run to keep his soul.&nbsp; A vampire running a Nigerian investor scam.&nbsp; A wolf racing to the mountaintop, before a dragon can catch and kill him.&nbsp; A human protecting one of the aliens he fought in war, from an old army buddy.&nbsp; Meet these and other characters in Serving Worlds, the genre-blending podcast fiction collection from John Mierau.&nbsp; Weekly episodes are 20 minutes or less but Beware: there be cliffhangers here!</p></p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Theme and Variations]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/theme-and-variations/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Theme and Variations - A free audiobook by Michelle M. Welch, editor]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/theme-and-variations/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Theme and Variations - A free audiobook</h1><p>A podcast anthology of speculative fiction with music as a theme.&nbsp; Science fiction, fantasy, and slipstream tales include stories of a future world where music has been lost, office workers whose embedded soundtracks direct their lives, the Martian superstar who doesn&apos;t want to play anymore, singers who can compel men to kill with the sound of their voices, and more.&nbsp; The eight episodes present short stories by Keyan Bowes, Ernest Hogan, Elaine Isaak, Lejon A. Johnson, Jack Mangan, Rick Novy, Lon Prater, Caroline Rhodes, and Michelle M. Welch, and some of the episodes feature performances or original music by the authors.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Sonic Fiction]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/sonic-fiction/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Sonic Fiction - A free audiobook by Jeff Kafer (Editor)]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/sonic-fiction/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Sonic Fiction - A free audiobook</h1><p>Sonic Fiction features an eclectic mix of authors from a range of ages and backgrounds.&nbsp; This collection of short stories is a true potpourri of genres.&nbsp; From fantasy to noir, to modern-day struggles with relationships, this book spans the gamut of human emotions and experiences, from the ancient past to the far-off future.&nbsp; Featuring works of Science fiction, gritty war tales, murder and intrigue, comedy and farce, this is a book for any fan of short fiction.&nbsp; Let us tell you a story!&nbsp; Compiled and narrated by Jeffrey KaferSonic Fiction Book cover art by Krista of r*stiltskin design </p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Theme and Variations]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/theme-and-variations/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Theme and Variations - A free audiobook by Michelle M. Welch, editor]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/theme-and-variations/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Theme and Variations - A free audiobook</h1><p>A podcast anthology of speculative fiction with music as a theme.&nbsp; Science fiction, fantasy, and slipstream tales include stories of a future world where music has been lost, office workers whose embedded soundtracks direct their lives, the Martian superstar who doesn&apos;t want to play anymore, singers who can compel men to kill with the sound of their voices, and more.&nbsp; The eight episodes present short stories by Keyan Bowes, Ernest Hogan, Elaine Isaak, Lejon A. Johnson, Jack Mangan, Rick Novy, Lon Prater, Caroline Rhodes, and Michelle M. Welch, and some of the episodes feature performances or original music by the authors.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
