<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Short Story Collections &amp; Anthologies</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Every Photo Tells... Book 1]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/every-photo-tells-book-1/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Every Photo Tells... Book 01 - A free audiobook by Katharina Maimer and Mick Bordet]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/every-photo-tells-book-1/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Every Photo Tells... Book 1</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Katharina Maimer and Mick Bordet</h3><p>Kilted pirate Greenbeard&apos;s last voyage turns up some unexpected surprises...Who is behind the murder at the Eagle Cave?Love crops up when it is least expected...An ancient terror awakens to threaten mankind&apos;s existence...&apos;Every Photo Tells...&apos; is a short story anthology that sets out to show that every picture can tell more than just one story, by presenting a range of tales inspired by seven photographs.&nbsp; Read by hosts Mick Bordet and Katharina Maimer, and featuring the writing talents of several guest authors, the stories cover a wide range of themes and genres.&nbsp; Whether your taste is for horror or whodunnit, modern thriller or period swashbuckler, fantasy or sci-fi, there is sure to be something for you in this collection.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Winter of Different Directions]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/winter-of-different-directions/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Winter of Different Directions - A free audiobook by Steven J. McDermott]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/winter-of-different-directions/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Winter of Different Directions - A free </h1><p>The characters in Steven J.&nbsp; McDermott&apos;s short story collection Winter of Different Directions struggle to keep life&apos;s body blows and uppercuts from becoming knockout punches, whether they bring them on themselves, or receive them from friends, lovers, co-workers, or family.&nbsp; You might root for them.&nbsp; You might root against them.&nbsp; But just like the relatives you hope won&apos;t show for Thanksgiving, these are characters you can&apos;t forget.&nbsp; With his stunning range and passionate delivery, it is McDermott who delivers the knockout punch in this debut collection of twenty short stories.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Theme and Variations]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/theme-and-variations/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Theme and Variations - A free audiobook by Michelle M. Welch, editor]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/theme-and-variations/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Theme and Variations - A free audiobook</h1><p>A podcast anthology of speculative fiction with music as a theme.&nbsp; Science fiction, fantasy, and slipstream tales include stories of a future world where music has been lost, office workers whose embedded soundtracks direct their lives, the Martian superstar who doesn&apos;t want to play anymore, singers who can compel men to kill with the sound of their voices, and more.&nbsp; The eight episodes present short stories by Keyan Bowes, Ernest Hogan, Elaine Isaak, Lejon A. Johnson, Jack Mangan, Rick Novy, Lon Prater, Caroline Rhodes, and Michelle M. Welch, and some of the episodes feature performances or original music by the authors.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Voices of New Media Fiction]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/voices-new-media-fiction/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Voices of New Media Fiction - A free audiobook edited by Mur Lafferty]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/voices-new-media-fiction/" description="<![CDATA[New Media Fiction brings together the pioneer short fiction podcasters.&nbsp; Experimenting from putting short-short fiction to novellas over their podcasts, these writers were the first to test the new medium for storytelling.&nbsp; Some wrote specifically for podcasts, some read previously published fiction, and some read entirely new stories.&nbsp; Some listeners asked if they could get just the stories in audio form, and that request brought about this podiobook.&nbsp; Cory Doctorow tells us a story about a post-apocalyptic government run by sysadmins and James Patrick Kelly narrates a story of a strange reconciliation.&nbsp; We've collected 18 stories for you, the first short fiction to go out over podcast, and look forward to bringing you more.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Podioracket Presents - Visionaries]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/podioracket-presents-visionaries/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Podioracket Presents: Visionaries - A free short stories anthology from Podiobooks.com authors]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/podioracket-presents-visionaries/" description="<![CDATA[Podioracket Presents-Visionaries is a collection of short stories by Podiobooks.com authors collected by H.E. Roulo and Brian Holtz.&nbsp; The stories are a mix of genre from some of Podiobooks.com&apos;s best authors.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Streetwise Cycle]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-streetwise-cycle/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Streetwise Cycle - A free audiobook by Bronwyn Mauldin]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-streetwise-cycle/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Streetwise Cycle</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Bronwyn Mauldin</h3><p>The Streetwise Cycle is a series of nine interconnected stories about people living unexpectedly interconnected lives on the streets of Los Angeles. It&apos;s a view of the city, as seen by the people who sleep on its streets.There are nine stories in all, each of them exactly 999 words long. The podcast is available in three episodes, each containing three stories. To read the stories or see a map of where they take place, visit <a href='http://streetwisecycle.com/'>StreetwiseCycle.com</a>.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Sonic Fiction]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/sonic-fiction/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Sonic Fiction - A free audiobook by Jeff Kafer (Editor)]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/sonic-fiction/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Sonic Fiction - A free audiobook</h1><p>Sonic Fiction features an eclectic mix of authors from a range of ages and backgrounds.&nbsp; This collection of short stories is a true potpourri of genres.&nbsp; From fantasy to noir, to modern-day struggles with relationships, this book spans the gamut of human emotions and experiences, from the ancient past to the far-off future.&nbsp; Featuring works of Science fiction, gritty war tales, murder and intrigue, comedy and farce, this is a book for any fan of short fiction.&nbsp; Let us tell you a story!&nbsp; Compiled and narrated by Jeffrey KaferSonic Fiction Book cover art by Krista of r*stiltskin design </p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
