<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Short Story Collections &amp; Anthologies</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[&apos;s audio dramas]]>" url="" type="link" text="<![CDATA[Podcast audio dramas from ]]>" description="<![CDATA[Podcast audio dramas from ]]>" />-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Fresh Kills]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/fresh-kills/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Fresh Kills - A free audiobook by Basil Sands and The Authors of The Killzone Blog]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/fresh-kills/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Fresh Kills - A free audiobook</h1><p>Fresh Kills is a podcast collection of original short stories by the authors of the popular literary blog The Kill Zone.&nbsp; Reminiscent of the Twilight Zone, these killer tales vary from the paranormal to the chilling to the just plain scary.&nbsp; Each delivers a finely crafted tale that will keep you clicking through the pages.&nbsp; Contributors to the podcast version include these award winning and best selling authors: John Gilstrap, Michelle Gagnon, James Scott Bell, Kathryn Lilley, John Ramsey Miller, Clare Langley-Hawthorne, Joe Moore and Basil Sands.&nbsp; Originally posted as an ebook at Amazon and Smashwords, the podcast version includes 3 extra stories, not available in print including one by award winning podcast author and narrator Basil Sands.&nbsp; So pop on the ear phones and buckle your seatbelt for a trip to the edge of sanity....it&apos;s going to be a wild ride.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Serving Worlds]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/serving-worlds/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Serving Worlds - a free audiobook by John Mierau]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/serving-worlds/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Serving Worlds - a free audiobook by John Mierau</h1><p><p>A cowboy on the run to keep his soul.&nbsp; A vampire running a Nigerian investor scam.&nbsp; A wolf racing to the mountaintop, before a dragon can catch and kill him.&nbsp; A human protecting one of the aliens he fought in war, from an old army buddy.&nbsp; Meet these and other characters in Serving Worlds, the genre-blending podcast fiction collection from John Mierau.&nbsp; Weekly episodes are 20 minutes or less but Beware: there be cliffhangers here!</p></p>]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Voices of New Media Fiction]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/voices-new-media-fiction/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Voices of New Media Fiction - A free audiobook edited by Mur Lafferty]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/voices-new-media-fiction/" description="<![CDATA[New Media Fiction brings together the pioneer short fiction podcasters.&nbsp; Experimenting from putting short-short fiction to novellas over their podcasts, these writers were the first to test the new medium for storytelling.&nbsp; Some wrote specifically for podcasts, some read previously published fiction, and some read entirely new stories.&nbsp; Some listeners asked if they could get just the stories in audio form, and that request brought about this podiobook.&nbsp; Cory Doctorow tells us a story about a post-apocalyptic government run by sysadmins and James Patrick Kelly narrates a story of a strange reconciliation.&nbsp; We've collected 18 stories for you, the first short fiction to go out over podcast, and look forward to bringing you more.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Podioracket Presents - Visionaries]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/podioracket-presents-visionaries/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Podioracket Presents: Visionaries - A free short stories anthology from Podiobooks.com authors]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/podioracket-presents-visionaries/" description="<![CDATA[Podioracket Presents-Visionaries is a collection of short stories by Podiobooks.com authors collected by H.E. Roulo and Brian Holtz.&nbsp; The stories are a mix of genre from some of Podiobooks.com&apos;s best authors.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Theme and Variations]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/theme-and-variations/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Theme and Variations - A free audiobook by Michelle M. Welch, editor]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/theme-and-variations/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Theme and Variations - A free audiobook</h1><p>A podcast anthology of speculative fiction with music as a theme.&nbsp; Science fiction, fantasy, and slipstream tales include stories of a future world where music has been lost, office workers whose embedded soundtracks direct their lives, the Martian superstar who doesn&apos;t want to play anymore, singers who can compel men to kill with the sound of their voices, and more.&nbsp; The eight episodes present short stories by Keyan Bowes, Ernest Hogan, Elaine Isaak, Lejon A. Johnson, Jack Mangan, Rick Novy, Lon Prater, Caroline Rhodes, and Michelle M. Welch, and some of the episodes feature performances or original music by the authors.</p>]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Sonic Fiction]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/sonic-fiction/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Sonic Fiction - A free audiobook by Jeff Kafer (Editor)]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/sonic-fiction/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Sonic Fiction - A free audiobook</h1><p>Sonic Fiction features an eclectic mix of authors from a range of ages and backgrounds.&nbsp; This collection of short stories is a true potpourri of genres.&nbsp; From fantasy to noir, to modern-day struggles with relationships, this book spans the gamut of human emotions and experiences, from the ancient past to the far-off future.&nbsp; Featuring works of Science fiction, gritty war tales, murder and intrigue, comedy and farce, this is a book for any fan of short fiction.&nbsp; Let us tell you a story!&nbsp; Compiled and narrated by Jeffrey KaferSonic Fiction Book cover art by Krista of r*stiltskin design </p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Theme and Variations]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/theme-and-variations/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Theme and Variations - A free audiobook by Michelle M. Welch, editor]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/theme-and-variations/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Theme and Variations - A free audiobook</h1><p>A podcast anthology of speculative fiction with music as a theme.&nbsp; Science fiction, fantasy, and slipstream tales include stories of a future world where music has been lost, office workers whose embedded soundtracks direct their lives, the Martian superstar who doesn&apos;t want to play anymore, singers who can compel men to kill with the sound of their voices, and more.&nbsp; The eight episodes present short stories by Keyan Bowes, Ernest Hogan, Elaine Isaak, Lejon A. Johnson, Jack Mangan, Rick Novy, Lon Prater, Caroline Rhodes, and Michelle M. Welch, and some of the episodes feature performances or original music by the authors.</p>]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast audio drama from ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by .  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
	</body>
</opml>
