<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Supernatural &amp; Magickal podcast novels from Podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Dark Matter]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/dark-matter/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Dark Matter - a free podcast novel by Michele Roger]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/dark-matter/" description="<![CDATA[<p>In a freak accident that leads to her untimely death Louella, a plain Jane from the suburbs finds herself transformed into one of the walking undead. Michael, the Archangel, offers her a chance to win her life and family back.</p><p>Louella learns that even in the afterlife nothing is free. She must pit her meager supernatural abilities against the mounting forces of darkness. Confronting problematic demons and monsters from Otherworld and beyond who agressively continue to tip the scales in the war of good and and evil in the favor of the Dark One. With the help of Steven, the altruistic vampire and De Vok, a dead librarian from the ancient Alexandria, Luella walks the world between the living and the dead. In her quest to regain her life she learns that even the forces for good have their own agendas and cannot always be trusted.</p><p>This book is a macabre stew of horror, fantasy, science fiction and humor.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Serving Worlds]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/serving-worlds/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Serving Worlds - a free podcast novel by John Mierau]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/serving-worlds/" description="<![CDATA[<p>A cowboy on the run to keep his soul. A vampire running a Nigerian investor scam.  A wolf racing to the mountaintop, before a dragon can catch and kill him. A human protecting one of the aliens he fought in war, from an old army buddy. Meet these and other characters in Serving Worlds, the genre-blending podcast fiction collection from John Mierau.  Weekly episodes are 20 minutes or less but Beware: there be cliffhangers here!</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The House of Grey]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-house-of-grey/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The House of Grey - A free podcast novel by Collin Earl]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-house-of-grey/" description="<![CDATA[14-year-old Monson Grey faces the same challenges that any freshman high school kid would.&nbsp; Difficult classes, weird teachers, food fights...girls.&nbsp; Except Monson Grey is not Monson Grey.&nbsp; At least, when he looks at himself in the mirror, the scarred face staring back is not someone he recognizes.&nbsp; Now he finds himself attending an extraordinary school, the recipient of an incredible scholarship, among ridiculously rich classmates, and with no memory of how he got there or what to expect.&nbsp; As bizarre events start to unfold around him, Monson wonders what secrets lay locked in his hidden past.&nbsp; Add all this to a mysterious silver stone, an Indiana-Jones-copycat professor, Merlin the wizard, and even Atlantis, and you&#039;ll find yourself in a fantastic tale in which magic does exist and everything is never as it seems.]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>

