<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Thriller podcast novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Immortal Game]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-immortal-game/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Immortal Game - A free audiobook by Mark Coggins]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-immortal-game/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Immortal Game</h1><h3>by Mark Coggins</h3><p>When the world's most innovative computer chess software is stolen, wisecracking, jazz bass-playing PI August Riordan is hired to find it.Sifting through a San Francisco peopled with bruising, ex-NFL henchmen, transvestite techno geeks, and alluring, drug-addicted dominatrices, Riordan has got his work cut out for him.But with a smart-ass attitude like Riordan's, nothing is easy ...A darkly comic sojourn through a town unrecognizable from the Tony Bennett song and the Rice-a-Roni ads, THE IMMORTAL GAME is a San Francisco Chronicle book of the year and a Shamus, Barry, and Independent Publisher (IPPY) award nominee.&quot;Smart, stylish, sexy and amusingly insouciant. It's a true find, a well-written and sophisticated addition to the heralded San Francisco private-detective story...a panoramic tour de force.&quot;-San Francisco Chronicle&quot;Gritty...seamy...very, very funny. [Coggins] has given the form fresh life.&quot;-National Public Radio&quot;Here's a first novel that pays homage to Hammett, Chandler, and every wisecracking PI in the genre, and then some. It also introduces one of the most delightful characters to come along in some time: August Riordan, a jazz bass-playing PI who is cynical, irreverent, and a laugh a minute.&quot;-Otto Penzler for Amazon.com&quot;Coggins hauls us on a dark, hip journey into the grittier parts of San Francisco, with only an occasional appearance of the city we know from Rice-a-Roni ads...a superb new take on a classic mystery form.&quot;-Detroit Free Press&quot;August Riordan takes the reader on a wisecracking, action-packed ramble through San Francisco's kinky sex milieux, including S/M and bondage emporia.&quot;-Jazz Fiction: A History and Comprehensive Reader's Guide&quot;Coggins clearly recalls the old masters in his debut novel. Think of it as THE MALTESE FALCON played out at the end of the century. Short on the genre cliches that have become all too common today, Coggins' novel has all the power and wit that make a detective story into a great read.&quot;-The Bookman's Week</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Heart Of Diamonds]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/heart-of-diamonds/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Heart Of Diamonds - a podcast novel by Dave Donelson.  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/heart-of-diamonds/" description="<![CDATA[Corruption at the highest levels of government, greed in the church, and brutality among warring factions make the Congo a very dangerous place for television journalist Valerie Grey.  Amid the bloody violence of that country's endless civil war, Grey uncovers a deadly diamond-smuggling scheme that reaches from the heart of the Congo to the White House by way of a famous American televangelist.  Aided by an altruistic doctor, Grey is pursued by the soldiers of the country's dictator, the mercenaries of the mine's owner, and the rebels seeking control of the country.  HEART OF DIAMONDS is a fast-paced tale of ambition, avarice, betrayal, and love.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Serve It Cold]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/serve-it-cold/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Serve It Cold - a free podcast novel by Ronnie Blackwell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/serve-it-cold/" description="<![CDATA[Detective Jonny C.&nbsp; Speed&apos;s life can&apos;t get much better.&nbsp; He&apos;s booked into the  French Quarter&apos;s most luxurious guesthouse, and his day job as convenience store manager is 104 miles behind him in Catherine, Mississippi.&nbsp; He&apos;s already taken care of one pro-bono missing persons job since he&apos;s been in New Orleans, and his paying client&apos;s cheating wife is a beautiful and very accommodating exhibitionist.&nbsp; Are things too good to be true?&nbsp; Of course they are.&nbsp; Jonny starts to worry when his client turns up dead, but when the suspects start dropping, Jonny and his crack team of beauty queens, recovering addicts, professional athletes, computer hackers, and pampered dogs find themselves caught in a twisted scheme of revenge that threatens to turn the town of Catherine inside out.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Acts of Desperation]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/acts-of-desperation/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Acts of Desperation - A free audiobook by Tim Dodge]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/acts-of-desperation/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Acts of Desperation</h1><h3>by Tim Dodge</h3><p>Ray Davis is newly divorced, going nowhere at a dead-end job in a warehouse, and has almost worked off the debts his ex-wife rang up.&nbsp; Then his underinsured brother&apos;s need for a liver transplant forces Ray to come up with a lot of money, fast.&nbsp; When he attempts to recover the profit he made with an old business partner, Ray discovers that the partner is dead and his investment has fallen into the hands of a drug dealer.&nbsp; The dealer has used the cash to buy a large supply of cocaine; he and his gun are not inclined to return the proceeds.&nbsp; Ray enlists a crude private eye to help him get it back, and he falls in love with Jenna, a beautiful waitress.&nbsp; His struggle to recover the money soon takes him deep into a swamp of crime, drugs, murder and revenge.&nbsp; Caught in a war between rival dealers, he comes to realize that the stakes have risen beyond the woman he loves or the money he needs to save his brother.&nbsp; He&apos;s fighting for his life.&nbsp; ACTS OF DESPERATION is the new thriller from Tim Dodge.&nbsp; It combines crime, action, adventure, romance and humor into a roller coaster ride of a story.</p>]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
