<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Vampire podcast novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Night&#39;s Knights published on Podiobooks.com]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/nights-knights/feed/" text="<![CDATA[Night&#39;s Knights - a free podcast novel by Emerian Rich]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/nights-knights/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Three vampires challenge each other to create the perfect offspring.&nbsp; Beings from another realm attempt to orchestrate things to serve their purpose.&nbsp; Luckily a tough street chick named Jespa is there to kick some immortal butt.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Prophecy Awakens - A free podcast novel by Brenda Wamsley]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/prophecy-awakens/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Prophecy Awakens - A free audiobook by Brenda Wamsley]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/prophecy-awakens/" description="<![CDATA[Jane, a preacher's daughter, is getting forced into marrying a man twice her age and whom she does not love.&nbsp; Her prayers for a way out of her life are answered one fateful night starting a whole new existence and all new dangers.&nbsp; Soon she realizes that she can be more than just a dutiful daughter as she tries to survive a world where demons are real and they want to destroy her because she has a scar on her neck that matches a prophecy.&nbsp; Join Jane on her travels as the Prophecy Awakens.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Forever Fifteen]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/forever-fifteen/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Forever Fifteen - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/forever-fifteen/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Lucy Albert is not your ordinary maladjusted suburban adolescent.&nbsp; Born into the era of the Black Plague in medieval Italy, Lucy is chosen as a mate by the sinister vampire Sebastianus against her will.&nbsp; Struggling to survive in a modern world she cannot identify with, Lucy isn't looking for attention.</p><p>Welcome to Forever Fifteen, where a lonely girl seeks refuge in a world awash in everyday brutality, a world where only blood and death can sate her hunger.&nbsp; Journey into Lucy's past as you experience the terror of the Black Death and the harsh reality of womanhood in the Middle Ages.&nbsp; Enter Forever Fifteen, the fast-paced thrill ride that is redefining vampire horror.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Lilith's Love]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/liliths-love/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Lilith's Love - A free audiobook by Dan Shaurette]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/liliths-love/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Lilith's Love</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Dan Shaurette</h3><p>Donovan, lonely and getting over the recent death of his parents, asks his long-time friend Christian to move in with him when he relocates back home again to Phoenix from Los Angeles.&nbsp; After the Vampire Hunters find Lilith in New Orleans, she and her Wiccan friend Anna decide to go where they think no one would expect to find vampires - The Valley of the Sun, Phoenix, AZ.&nbsp; Christian, who is also a Wiccan, meets Anna at a Samhain event (Halloween). The chemistry between them is immediate, and when they introduce their roommates to each other, Don realizes Lilith is not only the woman of his dreams - but that she is the woman in his dreams at night.&nbsp; Two romances are sparked, and now that both couples have found each other, they must fight the vengeful plans of Lilith&apos;s Master.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Conjuring Raine]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/conjuring-raine/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Conjuring Raine - A free audiobook by Maya Lassiter]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/conjuring-raine/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Conjuring Raine</h1><h3>A free audiobook by Maya Lassiter</h3><p>From San Fransisco&apos;s Tenderloin to the Dismal Swamp of North Carolina, human trafficking, vampires, and conjure magic combine in this sexy, funny, spooky story about Raine Black, a struggling comic strip artist with a gift--her comics come true.&nbsp; Enter Joshua: Raine&apos;s secret childhood friend, an abolitionist, and a vampire.&nbsp; Possessed by a revenge demon his vampire religion can&apos;t contain, Joshua just wants to get Raine safe from the demon, and from the other vampires, so he can kill himself in peace before the demon takes him over.&nbsp; But Raine thinks she can draw Joshua a comic with a happy ending, if she just has a little more time.&nbsp; And the demon has an offer.&nbsp; It wants to strike a bargain...with Raine.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Blood Witness published on Podiobooks.com]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/blood-witness/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Blood Witness - a free podcast novel by Dave Hitt]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/blood-witness/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Catherine is a 1500 year old vampire. (She’s really 1800 but she lies about her age.) Chris is a high school senior.&nbsp; She is a blood sucking creature of the night.&nbsp; He is a Jehovah’s Witness.&nbsp; Together they discover something that threatens the existence of every vampire, and the only solution is to break the One Law that binds them all.</p>]]>"/>
	</body>
</opml>

