<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Vampire podcast novels from Podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Blood Witness]]>" xmlUrl="http://podiobooks.com/title/blood-witness/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Blood Witness - a free podcast novel by Dave Hitt]]>" htmlUrl="http://podiobooks.com/title/blood-witness/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Catherine is a 1500 year old vampire. (She’s really 1800 but she lies about her age.) Chris is a high school senior. She is a blood sucking creature of the night. He is a Jehovah’s Witness. Together they discover something that threatens the existence of every vampire, and the only solution is to break the One Law that binds them all.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Forever Fifteen]]>" xmlUrl="http://podiobooks.com/title/forever-fifteen/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Forever Fifteen - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="http://podiobooks.com/title/forever-fifteen/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Lucy Albert is not your ordinary maladjusted suburban adolescent. Born into the era of the Black Plague in medieval Italy, Lucy is chosen as a mate by the sinister vampire Sebastianus against her will. Struggling to survive in a modern world she cannot identify with, Lucy isn't looking for attention.</p><p>Welcome to Forever Fifteen, where a lonely girl seeks refuge in a world awash in everyday brutality, a world where only blood and death can sate her hunger. Journey into Lucy's past as you experience the terror of the Black Death and the harsh reality of womanhood in the Middle Ages. Enter Forever Fifteen, the fast-paced thrill ride that is redefining vampire horror.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Night&#39;s Knights]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/nights-knights/feed/" text="<![CDATA[Night&#39;s Knights - a free podcast novel by Emerian Rich]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/nights-knights/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Three vampires challenge each other to create the perfect offspring. Beings from another realm attempt to orchestrate things to serve their purpose. Luckily a tough street chick named Jespa is there to kick some immortal butt.</p>]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>

