<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>&apos;s podcast novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds.feedburner.com/secretworldchronicle?format=xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.secretworldchronicle.com/" description="<![CDATA[Book Three: World Well Lost has arrived! Famed fantasy and sci-fi author Mercedes Lackey and newcomer Steve Libbey have joined forces to create a superhero-themed braided novel podcast series called The Secret World Chronicle. The series depicts an ensemble cast of metahuman characters coping with worldwide attacks by a mysterious, technologically advanced Nazi secret society, and the ensuing chaos.  The Secret World is a meeting ground for pulpy adventure and thoughtful science fiction speculation, where ordinary people are elevated above their fellow humans and must grapple with the consequences of their newfound abilities. ]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by .  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book One: World Well Lost]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-secret-world-chronicle-book-three-world-well-lost/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book One: World Well Lost - a podcast novel by Mercedes Lackey and Steve Libbey]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-secret-world-chronicle-book-three-world-well-lost/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Continuing the action and intrigue of the first two books, World Well Lost joins the ensemble cast of metahuman characters as they struggle against the growing powers of the Thule Society as well as Echo's own waning popularity. Famed fantasy and sci-fi author Mercedes Lackey and newcomers Steve Libbey, Dennis Lee, and Cody Martin bring this superhero-themed braided novel podcast series to life with characters such as the Seraphym, Red Saviour, John Murdock, and Red Djinni.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book One: Invasion]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/secret-world-chronicle-book-one/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book One: Invasion - A free podcast novel by Mercedes Lackey and Steve Libbey]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/secret-world-chronicle-book-one/" description="<![CDATA[Emerging mysteriously during World War II, metahumans became icons of the best - and worst - humanity had to offer.&nbsp; Yet sixty years later, the world still suffers from war, greed and madness.&nbsp; Worse, man&apos;s nadir of systematic cruelty returns with bizarre new weapons.&nbsp; The metahumans of Earth must find a way to defeat this powerful foe and discover what lurks behind the scenes - a secret world hidden from our own.&nbsp; Mercedes Lackey, one of fantasy&apos;s most beloved voices, and new talent Steve Libbey bring you a podcast series that catapults the classic superhero into the 21st century.Book One: Invasion starts the series off with a bang - a set of coordinated attacks by Nazi warriors in futuristic battle armor.&nbsp; We meet our cast of heroes in the midst of chaos: Belladonna Blue, a young azure-skinned healer; Victoria Victrix Nagy, a geomancer fighting panic attacks; Handsome Devil, whose luck is metahumanly good; Red Saviour, strident leader of an anachronistic Soviet team; Red Djinni, the shapeshifting criminal; and John Murdock, a fugitive super-soldier.&nbsp; Watching over them all is the Seraphym, descended from the Infinite to protect humanity.As the heroes fend off the blitzkrieg attack, they are left wondering what secrets have erupted from this hidden world, and whether, once unleashed, they can be contained.&nbsp; For there are clues that all is not what it seems...]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book Two: The Hunt]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/secret-world-chronicle-book-two/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book Two: The Hunt - A free podcast novel by Mercedes Lackey and Steve Libbey]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/secret-world-chronicle-book-two/" description="<![CDATA[The Hunt portrays the frenzied aftermath of the devastating Thule Society attacks.&nbsp; Famed fantasy and sci-fi author Mercedes Lackey and newcomer Steve Libbey have joined forces to create a superhero-themed braided novel podcast series called The Secret World Chronicle.&nbsp; The series depicts an ensemble cast of metahuman characters coping with worldwide attacks by a mysterious, technologically advanced Nazi secret society, and the ensuing chaos.&nbsp; The Secret World is a meeting ground for pulpy adventure and thoughtful science fiction speculation, where ordinary people are elevated above their fellow humans and must grapple with the consequences of their newfound abilities.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book Three: World Well Lost - A free podcast novel by Mercedes Lackey]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-secret-world-chronicle-book-three-world-well-lost/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book Three: World Well Lost - A free audiobook by Mercedes Lackey]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-secret-world-chronicle-book-three-world-well-lost/" description="<![CDATA[Continuing the action and intrigue of the first two books, World Well Lost joins the ensemble cast of metahuman characters as they struggle against the growing powers of the Thule Society as well as Echo's own waning popularity. Famed fantasy and sci-fi author Mercedes Lackey and newcomers Dennis Lee and Cody Martin bring this superhero-themed braided novel podcast series to life with characters such as the Seraphym, Victoria Victrix, John Murdock, and Red Djinni, with stories read by Veronica Giguere.]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by .  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
