<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Fantasy podcast novels from Podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Empress Sword - A free audiobook by Paulette Jaxton]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-empress-sword/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Empress Sword - A free audiobook by Paulette Jaxton]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-empress-sword/" description="<![CDATA[A prince, a dragon &amp; a magic sword - all the elements of a classic adventure story.Unfortunately for Prince Aster the dragon in question may not be the evil beast he thinks it is, and the magic sword might not even let the adventurous young prince touch it. When Aster discovers the price he must pay to save his kingdom, he&apos;ll have to make a choice no self-respecting adventure book hero would even consider.For most of his life, Aster has known he would one day face the fearsome dragon known as Mandrake. For the past ten years this beast has burned crops, destroyed villages, killed countless worthy knights and generally made life in the Kingdom of Caledon a royal pain. Now the young prince has learned of a magic sword powerful enough to defeat the dragon.The history books say it can be found in the ruins of a once great empire hidden somewhere beyond the Misty Mountain. If Aster can find the lost Empire, if he can brave the perilous journey through the mountains alone, if he can convince the ghost of the long dead Empress that he is worthy, then the only thing standing between him and the Empress Sword might just be a skirt.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Prophecy Of Swords]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/prophecy-of-swords/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Prophecy Of Swords - a free podcast novel by M.H. Bonham]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/prophecy-of-swords/" description="<![CDATA[In this podiobook: To End A WarTo End A WarNearly a thousand years ago a great warrior named Lachlan sought to unify his people, using the power of the Three Swords of Destiny.  Before his victory, Lachlan was killed by his trusted friend, Allarun.  Now, Allarun is still in power but haunted by dreams of Lachlan's death curse: that Lachlan would return to avenge his death.  Allarun's decision is to destroy the very people Lachlan tried to unite. Only two men have the power to stop the slaughter.  Romarin, the last of a line of kings, and a half-blood mercenary named Shadowhelm.  One may be destined to be Lachlan, but can they unlock the secret to Lachlan's power before Allarun kills them?  &quot;Prophecy Of Swords is a remarkably rich fantasy that takes you into new realms of wonder and imagination.  The battles and magic portrayed here full of excitement and intrigue.  It's hard to find a good fantasy that isn't a rehash of all that has been done before, but Margaret H. Bonham has managed to break the mold and give readers something totally unique and different.  A guaranteed winner.&quot;  -- Laura J. Underwood, author of Ard Magister, Chronicles Of The Last War, and forthcoming Dragon's Tongue and Wandering Lark &quot;In Prophecy Of Swords, Bonham has written an enjoyable and intriguing novel, filled with believable characters and a rich, satisfying plot.  I look forward to the next book in the series with great anticipation.&quot;  --  Karen E. Taylor, author of The Vampire Legacy series.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATAThe Bloodbaths[]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/bloodbaths/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Bloodbaths - a free podcast novel by Steve Libbey]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/bloodbaths/" description="<![CDATA[The Bloodbaths is the first book of Steve Libbey&apos;s new Aqua Pura Trilogy, a sword and sandal fantasy featuring a plumber on an epic quest to win back his beloved. Mercedes Lackey says: &quot;Steve Libbey gives the &apos;sword-and-sandal&apos; epic a kick in the tunic and  propels it into the gestalt of the 21st century, with an everyman hero whose brains triumph over brawn.&quot;Crixus Oraan is a water artesan, an engineer who builds aqueducts and piping for bathhouses and mansions in the empire of Rond (which bears a resemblance to our own Roman Empire). His guild has entrusted him with a large sum of gold to establish a branch in the up-and-coming coastal town of Restia. In a misguided effort to win enough gold to buy a lavish house for his new fiancé Kharrina, he loses the guild&apos;s gold in a card game.A shady sea captain present at the game-and possibly responsible for fleecing him-offers to sneak him off to the wild and mysterious continent of Minq. Afraid to lose his status in society for his crime, he agrees, hoping to gain back the gold he lost and compensate the guild back in Rond.In this first volume in the bold new Aqua Pura Trilogy, Crixus finds employment with the Lamiae of Nistru, a cruel society where those at the top bathe in the lifeblood of those on the bottom. Will his conscience allow him to finish the job?By turns dark, comedic, erotic and thrilling, The Bloodbaths is a book that transcends genre to stand on its own.This podcast is read by SWC&apos;s own Veronica Giguere.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The White Shadow Saga: The Stolen Moon of Londor]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-white-shadow-saga-the-stolen-moon-of-londor/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The White Shadow Saga: The Stolen Moon of Londor - a free podcast novel by A.P. Stephens]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-white-shadow-saga-the-stolen-moon-of-londor/" description="<![CDATA[<p>The era of peace among the elves, men, and dwarves comes to an end when one of Londor's twin moons disappears from the heavens…..Without the moon's balancing effect, evil forces grow bold, and warfare, sickness, and chaos threaten life itself.</p><p>Hearing the prayers of desperation that ride on the violent winds, the ancient wizard Randor Miithra, servant to the elf-gods, takes it upon himself to mend the world he has sworn to protect. The task will not be an easy one, though, for the wizard, too, has begun to feel the effects of the world's imbalance. As Randor struggles to maintain some semblance of his powers, he meets a secretive band of colorful characters from all walks of life, drawn together by a common goal: to find the stolen moon, whatever the cost. It does not take Randor and his motley company long to see that someone or something does not want the moon returned to the heavens.</p><p>The road is perilous….the stakes have never been greater….will they find victory…or will they only find their deaths?</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Wrath of the White Tigress]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/wrath-of-the-white-tigress/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Wrath of the White Tigress - a free podcast novel by David Alastair Hayden]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/wrath-of-the-white-tigress/" description="<![CDATA[<p>The Palymfar Order, which once protected the land of Hareez, now holds it in an iron grip of terror under the malevolent sorcerer Grandmaster Salahn and his mind-controlled assassin, Jaska the Slayer. As Salahn prepares to absorb the immortal White Tigress and become a god himself, Jaska and the palymfar annihilate all who stand in the way.</p><p>On the run since Salahn destroyed her temple and murdered her family, only Zyrella, last high priestess of the White Tigress, has the power to free her goddess. But the White Tigress has other plans and instead releases Jaska. For Salahn has demented ambitions reaching far beyond immortality and only together do Jaska and Zyrella hold a hope of stopping him before it’s too late.</p><p>Warning: This story contains graphic depictions of sex and violence, swords and sorcery.</p>]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Raven's Gift]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/ravens-gift/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Raven's Gift - a free podcast novel by Tobias D. Robison]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/ravens-gift/" description="<![CDATA[<p>When Raven comes to Redthwen to meet her mentor Orvannon, she encounters a vicious traveler, a hag with an extraordinary Voice of Command, and that hag's charge, a mysterious little girl. By the time Orvannon arrives, Raven will have learned too much about these strangers, and she will have discovered a dragon with the ability to put people into a swoon.</p><p>Orvannon's instructions start Raven off on an epic adventure. She will master the greatest bit of nose-magic in all of her native Ausland. She will face the dragon in combat. And she will have to deal with the hag while totally under control of that woman's power. These adventures lead to more, as Raven discovers how the great city of Shelton is under attack. She must use all her persuasion to bring a powerful wizard to the city's aid, and she will find that facing up to the attacking army is not enough.</p><p>Raven explores the magical caves created by three great wizards, eventually discovering the greatest evil of her time. Victory in the &quot;big boss battle&quot; is not enough. When the evil magic is destroyed, Raven and her friend must avoid starvation, and face the lightning bolts of yet another mage, to have a chance of staying alive in peace.</p><p>Raven's Gift is set in a magical, pastoral medieval world. Raven has a strange ability that is as much a curse as a gift. Trouble follows her every step, and danger approaches at every turn. She begins her journey with only her wits and her nose, but though her past haunts her, she finds companions who help her make amends for a terrible mistake.</p><p>Raven's Gift is a dramatic fantasy with an unusual heroine and intriguing magic. With Raven's deep bond to nature and her pragmatic attitude toward the obstacles in her path, she manages to find her place as destiny's unsung hero in her dangerous world.</p><p>One reader has said that Raven's Gift is like South Park mets James Bond meets Dungeons and Dragons. Although there's combat and even a military campaign in this novel, much of the action occurs in lively conversations. Even today, at the beginning of the 21st century, it is impossible to imagine making Raven's Gift into a movie -- for an unusual reason -- but if such a movie could be made, some parts of it might earn an R rating for being a bit earthy.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Legon Awakening]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/legon-awakening/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Legon Awakening - A free podcast novel by yn jen]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/legon-awakening/" description="<![CDATA[Set in a world that is not our own, Legon Awakening takes you through an epic journey into a land full of imagination and innovation.Join Legon and his sister, Sasha, search to understand their true heritage, confused at the possibility that of being part human and part elf.&nbsp; Surrounded by elves, the newly introduced Iumenta race, Dragons and Humans; Legon and Sasha&#039;s lives are filled with adventure and fantasy on their search for answers as they begin an epic journey of discovery; not to mention the incredible battle scenes which will be surely to capture your imagination!]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The WorldWrights]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-worldwrights/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The WorldWrights - a free podcast novel by Max Grant]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-worldwrights/" description="<![CDATA[<p>Kalukan awakens from millenia of cold sleep to find his companions dead. He has been charged by the long-dead Worldwrights to protect their creation from its out-of-control Overseer.</p><p>As Kalukan prepares for his final quest against the Overseer, now named the Ghala, he begins to learn that the World's purpose is not that which he was taught. With a frayed sense of faith in his purpose, Kalukan sets out to reach the inexplicable construction known as the Skylock, where history tells him a city will be built to stand against the Ghala, a final bastion of civilization. Kalukan hopes but cannot believe that he is the hero they imagine he is.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Legacy of Jade: A Traveler's Faith - A free audiobook by Paul B. Moore]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-legacy-of-jade-a-travelers-faith/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Legacy of Jade: A Traveler's Faith - A free audiobook by Paul B. Moore]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-legacy-of-jade-a-travelers-faith/" description="<![CDATA[The first novel of Alluvion, the Hidden Realm series.Velinor, a seeker, believer, and member of the Travelers, journeys with young Jade to seek the Orb of Chandrylon and the Crimson Cross - weapons with which to fight the the most powerful sorcerer ever known in Alluvion. With the assistance of his companions Aramil, Dantanious, the dwarf Oren, and Gathylon (a golden dragon of the House of Wentmane), Velinor and Jade traverse the forests, mountains and plains of Alluvion on their quest, battling  rival tribes, goblins, dragons, and the machinations of Aramil's evil uncle, Tirden, King of the Celides, on the way.]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[Outcast]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/outcast/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Outcast - a free podcast novel by Chris Hvidston]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/outcast/" description="<![CDATA[<h3>Dalan Kalamar had it all.</h3><p>An life of luxury, a loving family, and intended bride, and a destiny that would one day see him assume the Eldership of his Clan.</p><p>Then, on a dark night in his 12th year of life, four would-be assassins changed all that. Charged by his father with protecting a sacred artifact, Dalan was left for dead by his attackers, and the artifact subsequently stolen.</p><p>One year later, Dalan awakens from a comatose state not only to find his body healed, but also to the fact that his family has disowned him. Humiliated before his peers, the would-be heir to the Tiger’s Paw Clan is cast out to live amongst the lowest of the low in Bengalan society:</p><h3>The exiles.</h3><p>Outcasts from the Clans, the exiles are a society unto themselves, shunned by all and forced to live in secret. They move through the secular, non-Clan world under the cover of assumed identities, taking jobs where strong backs are favored over questionable pasts. Through an elaborate underground network known as The Foundation, many exiles have found some glimmer of hope in a world committed to rooting them out and exterminating them like so much vermin.</p><p>It is into this world that a 13-year old Dalan is thrust. With no money and only a tiny bit of martial arts training, the young tiger begins his journey through the dark underbelly of Bengalan society. His eyes are quickly opened to the true brutality of the Clans, as he bears witness to an act so horrifying that he begins to question all he’d been brought up to believe.</p><p>Hope does exist for the young tiger, however…in the form of a mysterious trainer who extends an offer to him. The offer is to train Dalan in an ancient fighting form…one that will transform him from a desperate, fearful exile into a beast to be feared and respected by all. The young tiger accepts, and before long finds himself on a journey towards a destiny that will challenge all he’s ever known and believed, and make him see the world in a new, cold light.</p><p>He also finds hope in the loving arms of a fellow exile, one from a far off land running from an alleged curse put on her by those who cast her out. As their love for each other grows, Dalan soon finds himself faced with a choice: Devote his life to his newfound love and abandon any hope of regaining his honor…</p><p>Or risk losing everything for one chance at bloody, unforgiving vengeance</p>]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Ninth Avatar]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-ninth-avatar/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Ninth Avatar - a free podcast novel by Todd Newton]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-ninth-avatar/" description="<![CDATA[<center>Nine Pillars, Eight Avatars</center><p>For Starka, an outcast accused of incest, life is about as simple as one could hope. A prophecy of the ascension of the Avatar of Darkness changed that. Starka, protected by the mysterious warrior DaVille, tries desperately to prevent the disturbing prophecy from becoming a reality.</p><p>The world is thrown into chaos as the Carrion Army comes to power, destroying the rival nations of Brong and Rochelle. Wan Du and Mayrah are drawn into the conflict when their homes are destroyed and Cairos, a wizard from the betrayed city of Illiadora, likewise seeks revenge for his fallen comrades.</p><p>As the leader of the Carrion army seeks to cover the world in death and darkness to become a living embodiment of magic, these uncertain allies battle against an inevitable conclusion.</p><center>The Ninth Avatar is coming.</center>]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[KIRINS: The Spell of No&#039;an]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/kirins-the-spell-of-noan/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[KIRINS: The Spell of No&#039;an - a free podcast novel by James D. Priest]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/kirins-the-spell-of-noan/" description="<![CDATA[<p>A race of tiny, magical beings lives on Earth today. They dwell in elaborate tree homes and mysterious underground sanctuaries. Because of an ancient dispute, however, humans are unaware of their hidden civilization.</p><p>They are kirins.</p><p>For thousands of years they lived in peace. But a deadly menace now threatens their existence. A party of daring explorers, led by the wise magician Speckarin, is sent on trained ravens to destroy an evil lurking a continent and an ocean away. Failure of this mission would mean death to the voyagers and the entire kirin race. But their success will depend on aid from a truly unexpected source, human beings.</p><p>Fly with these adventurers and witness today's world as it has never before been seen. You'll find yourself looking to the skies for this mystical race of beings, because maybe, just maybe...</p>]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Dark Fever]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/darkfever/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Darkfever - A free podcast novel by Karin Marie Moning]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/darkfever/" description="<![CDATA[MacKayla Lane&#039;s life is good. She has great friends, a decent job, and a car that breaks down only every other week or so. In other words, she&#039;s your perfectly ordinary twenty-first-century woman. Or so she thinks...until something extraordinary happens.When her sister is murdered, leaving a single clue to her death-a cryptic message on Mac&#039;s cell phone-Mac journeys to Ireland in search of answers. The quest to find her sister&#039;s killer draws her into a shadowy realm where nothing is as it seems, where good and evil wear the same treacherously seductive mask. She is soon faced with an even greater challenge: staying alive long enough to learn how to handle a power she had no idea she possessed-a gift that allows her to see beyond the world of man, into the dangerous realm of the Fae....As Mac delves deeper into the mystery of her sister&#039;s death, her every move is shadowed by the dark, mysterious Jericho, a man with no past and only mockery for a future. As she begins to close in on the truth, the ruthless Vlane-an alpha Fae who makes sex an addiction for human women-closes in on her. And as the boundary between worlds begins to crumble, Mac&#039;s true mission becomes clear: find the elusive Sinsar Dubh before someone else claims the all-powerful Dark Book-because whoever gets to it first holds nothing less than complete control of the very fabric of both worlds in their hands....]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Ancient Rising - Rise of the Ancients Book 1]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/ancient-rising-1/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Ancient Rising - Rise of the Ancients Book 1 - a free podcast novel by JC De La Torre]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/ancient-rising-1/" description="<![CDATA[A widower is set off on an amazing adventure by a man claiming to be a God.&nbsp; Like Indiana Jones meets Clash of the Titans.&nbsp; Follow Dan Ryan through Egypt, Greece, and the Mexican jungle as he unlocks the keys to finding the lost continent of Atlantis and the Gods that are imprisoned there.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Quilt, Book and Bard]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/quilt-book-and-bard/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Quilt, Book and Bard - a free podcast novel by Bryna Chalmer]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/quilt-book-and-bard/" description="<![CDATA[<p>For years the picture of the man with the oxcart has hung on the wall of her Aunt and Uncle's house. It never occurred to Tory that one day she might actually find herself in the picture. She frees Neal, an imp who has been imprisoned in Castle Hildegard for two hundred years. Together, they journey through the world of the Kingdom Trees, racing to break the spell that has bound the world together - in war.</p><p>King Delphic is bent on taking the spell for himself, and becoming monarch of all. Tory and Neal find help among the Bards and the Cloud Jumpers, along with some who are not as trustworthy as they seem. The World Tree is not the universe of Good and Evil; it's leaves are shades of gray.</p><p>Check out a tale where no fairies are hurt, but everything else is up for grabs.</p>]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[A Dance With Demons - A free podcast novel by Jeff Offringa]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/a-dance-with-demons/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[A Dance With Demons - A free audiobook by Jeff Offringa]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/a-dance-with-demons/" description="<![CDATA[Tarn Nohmal doesn't want much out of life. Food on the table, a roof over his head, and privacy. But when his old commander shows up and needs someone to track a band of orcs, what should be a simple mission turns out to become an endeavor to stop disaster from spreading across the entire realm of Averim.Not only is the kingdom threatened from within by a civil war, but the lack of troops on the eastern border seems to be making the orcs bolder. And to top it off, a demon is slaughtering orcs and humans alike. And it's up to Tarn and his companions; Nyla, a half-elven wizard, and Logan, a human priest raised by dwarves, to stop it before it comes to their home town and slaughters everyone there.But will there be a home town to return to? The Earl keeps calling troops west to support him in the civil war. The orcs can't be that big a threat... right?Step into the world of Aromathus, the creation of author Jeff Offringa, and experience swords and sorcery, military maneuvers, and political intrigue in a place where magic abounds, knights charge gloriously into battle, and the orcs may not be as stupid as they appear...]]>" />
	</body>
</opml>
