<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Historical &amp; Alternativ History podcast novels from Podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Paraffin Winter]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/paraffin-winter/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Paraffin Winter - a free podcast novel by Peter Chowney]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/paraffin-winter/" description="<![CDATA[<p>The winter of 1963 was the coldest winter of the century in the UK, at a time when post-war austerity and social class divisions made for a miserable life for many people. These were the days of back boilers, bubble and squeak, paraffin oil stoves, gas works, steam trains, and starting handles. The 1960s technological and social revolution hadn’t happened yet.</p><p>Ronnie and Jenny Delaney live in the south coast town of Poole, close by the gas works. They get by - Jenny works in the local pottery and Ronnie runs a paraffin delivery round, helping to keep his grateful customers warm. But then something unexpected turns up on the paraffin round: an eyeball. It doesn't take Ronnie long to work out that it's got something to do with his past as a small-time crook, back in the East End of London. Someone's messing him about. He can handle it. Or so he thinks.</p><p>But things start to get complicated, and he quickly finds himself way out of his depth. It's going to take someone cleverer than Ronnie to get to the bottom of this one. And that someone is closer than he could ever have imagined ...</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[In the Service of Samurai]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/in-the-service-of-samurai/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[In the Service of Samurai - A free podcast novel by Gloria Oliver]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/in-the-service-of-samurai/" description="<![CDATA[The choice: Serve the undead or become one of them.Toshi never expected the strange visitor who one evening stepped foot insidehis master&apos;s shop.&nbsp; A samurai smelling of the sea, dripping on the ground,algae strung from his armor.&nbsp; For the first time in his life, he discoversthat monsters do roam the earth.&nbsp; And this one has been specifically lookingfor him.Dragged from his home and all he has ever known, Toshi must now use hisacquired skills in foreign maps to help the creatures who have taken him.Yet at every turn there are problems.&nbsp; There are even those seeking toterminate his very life, not wanting his new master to succeed in hisassigned task.&nbsp; And when they do find it, Toshi discovers his new master&apos;senemies have prepared for their eventual arrival, leaving him the only onecapable of recovering what has been lost.&nbsp; Can he do what even the undeadcannot? Or will he fail and be forced to wander the world as one of them?]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Mark of a Druid]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-mark-of-a-druid/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Mark of a Druid - A free podcast novel by Rhonda R. Carpenter]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-mark-of-a-druid/" description="<![CDATA[When twenty-six-year-old Eve McCormick awakes, the images from her nightmare are indelible.&nbsp; The dream feels so real she must force herself to get a grip.&nbsp; This experience is just the beginning for Eve, a Los Angeles clinical hypnotherapist and researcher investigating whether reincarnation is fact or fiction.Unstoppable visions of an ancient lifetime steal days from her.&nbsp; The danger escalates when she wakes up physically injured and marked with a strange symbol.&nbsp; While Eve battles the past to maintain her sanity and safety, her project is jeopardized as another researcher&apos;s attempts to take over.&nbsp; One partner dies and another is accused of inappropriate conduct.&nbsp; Eve and her friend, Dr.&nbsp; Andrea McMurray, don&apos;t believe in coincidence and probe their shared visions for answers.&nbsp; On the other side of the Atlantic, Welshman Ryerson Sanders is haunted by his dreams and believes Eve&apos;s research project can help him.&nbsp; For both of them, an ancient Celtic prophecy and long-sought revenge entangles the past with the present.&nbsp; A druidess and a shape-shifter must join to save the druid way of life, while a queen conspires to kill Erin&apos;s only high king.&nbsp; Will the oaths and agendas of the past reach across the centuries to strengthen or to destroy?]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Toothless]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/toothless/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Toothless - a free podcast novel by J. R. Moore]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/toothless/" description="<![CDATA[France, 1180 AD: an ancient evil is on the march. The Black Yew leads an army of demons through Europe, laying waste with a devastating plague and destroying the relics of Christendom. After losing his wife and daughter, a failed Templar rejoins his comrades in the crusade against the Yew's army. But the dice are cast against the living, and the Black Yew's demons slay him, impressing his reanimated corpse into their ranks. He is gifted. He shows great promise as a servant to the Yew. But life is not yet done with him.]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>

