<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Podiobooks.com&#039;s podcast novel</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline type="link" title="<![CDATA[Podiobooks.com]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds2.feedburner.com/podiobooks?format=xml" text="<![CDATA[Podiobooks.com&#039;s homepage]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/" description="<![CDATA[Podiobooks.com - Free online serialized fiction.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Podio Racket&apos;s Live Show - on BlogTalkRadio]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds2.feedburner.com/RaiseARacket?format=xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Podio Racket -The Big Show- What are you putting in your ears?]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.blogtalkradio.com/PodioRacket" description="<![CDATA[Podio Racket - What are you putting in your ears?  New, reviews, &amp; interviews about what&#039;s going on at Podiobooks.com]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Podio Racket]]>" xmlUrl="http://feeds2.feedburner.com/RaiseARacket?format=xml" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Podio Racket - What are you putting in your ears?]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podioracket.com/" description="<![CDATA[Podio Racket - What are you putting in your ears?  New, reviews, &amp; interviews about what&#039;s going on at Podiobooks.com]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Podiobooker]]>" xmlUrl="http://feedproxy.google.com/podiobooker" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Podiobooker]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/blog/" description="<![CDATA[News &amp; updates from the staff of Podiobooks.com]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Collapse At Hidden Verse Three Three Two]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/collapse-at-hidden-verse-three-three-two/feed/" text="<![CDATA[DarkSide Sally&#039;s Podnovel: Collapse At Hidden Verse Three Three Two]]>" htmlUrl="http://darksidesally.com/" description="<![CDATA[The Multiverse Generator is failing.&nbsp; Dimensions threaten to collapse and entire populations will cease to exist unless it is reset.&nbsp; One being from each of more than five thousand verses has been acquired, and their DNA verified.&nbsp; Only one remains.&nbsp; His name is Timothy Rayburn and he is a resident of Earth.&nbsp; The Consolidation of Organized Systems has sent a ship to retrieve him.&nbsp; Timothy is a teenager failing speech class due to a paralyzing fear of public speaking.&nbsp; He soon learns that his problems are quite small compared to the impending collapse of all existence.&nbsp; He must overcome his fear if he is to survive not only the dangers of space travel and multiversal war, but himself.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Dorothea&#039;s Song]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/dorotheas-song/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Dorothea&#039;s Song]]>" htmlUrl="http://losoil.typepad.com/losoilcom/novels/" description="<![CDATA[&quot;Dorothea&#039;s Song&quot; tells the story of an ordinary boy named Peter who dreams up an extraordinary fantasy realm to flee the hardships of his own life.&nbsp; Inspired by classic high-fantasy themes, his tale has all the makings of a great adventure—a brave elvish warrior named Dorothea, a ruthless coven of witches, a renegade elf lord and a kingdom on the verge of collapse.&nbsp; But as the chaos intensifies in both worlds, instead of retreating from it, Peter is forced to take a daring stand in each.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Heart of the Ronin]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/heart-of-the-ronin/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Heart of the Ronin - A free podcast novel by Travis Heermann]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/heart-of-the-ronin/" description="<![CDATA[Thirteenth-century Japan is a dangerous place, even in a time of peace.&nbsp; Capricious gods, shape-changing animals, and bloodthirsty demons are as real and unpleasant as a gang of vicious bandits.&nbsp; From the wilderness emerges a young, idealistic warrior with his father&#039;s mysterious sword on his hip, a wise, sarcastic dog at his side, and a yearning in his heart to find a worthy master.&nbsp; He dreams only of being samurai.&nbsp; Little does he suspect the agony and glory that await him when his dreams come true.Finding a master should be easy for a warrior as skilled as Ken&#039;ishi, but the generations-long wars for the Imperial throne have ended.&nbsp; The land has settled into an uneasy peace and cast multitudes of proud, powerful warriors to the four winds.&nbsp; The new peace means that these masterless warriors, ronin, often must stoop to crime and banditry to feed themselves.&nbsp; Ken&#039;ishi finds himself plagued by the hatred and mistrust of peasants and samurai alike.When he saves a noble maiden from a pack of bandits, he and his faithful dog become enmeshed in the intrigues of samurai lords, vengeful constables, Mongol spies, and a shadowy underworld crime boss known as Green Tiger.&nbsp; But Ken&#039;ishi has a few secret weapons of his own, granted to him by his mysterious past and his magical upbringing.&nbsp; If only he knew more about his mysterious past, his parents&#039; murder, and the sword that seems to want to talk to him.&nbsp; .&nbsp; .&nbsp; .&nbsp; Heart of the Ronin is an action-packed historical fantasy, set against the backdrop of ancient intrigue and impending war, the first of a sweeping three-part epic filled with deadly duels and climactic battles.&nbsp; Creatures of folklore and myth are as real as the katana in one&#039;s hand.&nbsp; And just as deadly.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Corridor]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-corridor/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Corridor - A free podcast novel by Zan]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-corridor/" description="<![CDATA[The Corridor is a fantasy/horror story about Stuart Morrow, a man who has lost all hope and reason to live.&nbsp; However, a strange coincidence brings him unexpectedly into contact with a multitude of worlds beyond our own.&nbsp; Hunted by a despot who rules over countless alternate realities, Stuart&#039;s only hope is to seek help amongst the assortment of bizarre and grotesque characters who await him in the Corridor.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Children of Rhatlan]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/children-of-rhatlan/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Children of Rhatlan - A free podcast novel by Jonathan Fesmire]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/children-of-rhatlan" description="<![CDATA[Garum and Vayin are &quot;duals&quot;, twins trapped in each other&#039;s minds and bodies, sharing one life.&nbsp; When a deranged wizard hunts them, whom can they turn to? Their mentor? The city guard Vayin loves? The Wizards&#039; Guild? In a world that hates duals, anyone could be their enemy, and one misstep could get them killed.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Bloodblaths]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/bloodbaths/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Bloodbaths  - A free podcast novel by Steve Libbey]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/bloodbaths/" description="<![CDATA[The Bloodbaths is the first book of Steve Libbey&#039;s new Aqua Pura Trilogy, a sword and sandal fantasy featuring a plumber on an epic quest to win back his beloved.&nbsp; Mercedes Lackey says: &quot;Steve Libbey gives the &#039;sword-and-sandal&#039; epic a kick in the tunic and  propels it into the gestalt of the 21st century, with an everyman hero whose brains triumph over brawn.&quot;  Crixus Oraan is a water artesan, an engineer who builds aqueducts and piping for bathhouses and mansions in the empire of Rond (which bears a resemblance to our own Roman Empire).&nbsp; His guild has entrusted him with a large sum of gold to establish a branch in the up-and-coming coastal town of Restia.&nbsp; In a misguided effort to win enough gold to buy a lavish house for his new fiancé Kharrina, he loses the guild&#039;s gold in a card game.A shady sea captain present at the game-and possibly responsible for fleecing him-offers to sneak him off to the wild and mysterious continent of Minq.&nbsp; Afraid to lose his status in society for his crime, he agrees, hoping to gain back the gold he lost and compensate the guild back in Rond.In this first volume in the bold new Aqua Pura Trilogy, Crixus finds employment with the Lamiae of Nistru, a cruel society where those at the top bathe in the lifeblood of those on the bottom.&nbsp; Will his conscience allow him to finish the job?By turns dark, comedic, erotic and thrilling, The Bloodbaths is a book that transcends genre to stand on its own.This podcast is read by SWC&#039;s own Veronica Giguere.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Seventh Mountain (Chronicles of a Magi, Book 1)]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-seventh-mountain-chronicles-of-a-magi-book-1/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Seventh Mountain (Chronicles of a Magi, Book 1) - A free podcast novel by Gene Curtis]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-seventh-mountain-chronicles-of-a-magi-book-1/" description="<![CDATA[A dream, surreal and frightening, begins the path of 12 year old Mark Young&#039;s future; a path set long before he was even born.&nbsp; Fortunately, it&#039;s not a path he&#039;s doomed to walk alone.&nbsp; His course leads to true friends, fortune, and a place where he learns to wield great power.This place is The Seventh Mountain, the place where Magi train.&nbsp; The Seventh Mountain conceals the direst legend known to man.&nbsp; Mark&#039;s fate lies within.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Grizelda]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/grizelda/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Grizelda - A free podcast novel by Margaret R. Taylor]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/grizelda/" description="<![CDATA[In the Republic of Corvain, anybody who has a hint of magical power is rounded up and thrown into prison.&nbsp; They&#039;re doing it to defend the new nation, says the revolutionary government - defend it from the sorcerers and sorceresses who used to be the lackeys of the man-eating Auks in the bad old days of the monarcy.&nbsp; When Grizelda, a young seamstress from the poorer part of the capitol city, suddenly finds herself the government&#039;s target, she fears she is done for.But in prison she meets a group of rat-riding pixies and earns their undying friendship by mending their clothes.&nbsp; In exchange, they help her to escape and seek refuge in the world below the city.&nbsp; Living underground means Grizelda has to adapt to the strange customs of the goblins, a cheerless bunch who storm around muttering about the dictatorship of the proletariat.&nbsp; Not content to remain in exile, Grizelda winds up entangled with a group of human revolutionaries.&nbsp; Together they hatch a daring plan to return the Republic to its original ideals, before it decayed into a police state.&nbsp; If their plan is going to work, Grizelda will have to get Communist goblins, irresponsible pixies, and revolutionaries still deeply mistrustful of magic to work together.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Noggle Stones]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/noggle-stones/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Noggle Stones - A free podcast novel by Wil Radcliff]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/noggle-stones/" description="<![CDATA[Shunned by his people and tormented by nightmare visions, Bugbear, the mad goblin scholar, ventures into the wilderness with his ne&#039;er-do-well cousin, Tudmire, to seek out an ancient ruin and the lost wisdom it holds.Soon the cousins find themselves embroiled in cosmic events as their magical world of Annwfn is merged with 19th Century Earth after an accident concerning a mysterious scroll Tudmire acquires in a crooked game of Noggle Stones.&nbsp; While fleeing the enraged ogres they cheated, Bugbear and Tudmire happen upon Martin Manchester, who appears to be a creature of mythology known as a human.&nbsp; Bugbear takes Manchester as his apprentice, agreeing to teach him the empowering ways of Non-Logical Thought.&nbsp; The trio soon discovers that dark forces have aligned against them, and the two worlds may have been merged only to be destroyed!]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Serve It Cold]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/serve-it-cold/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Serve It Cold - a free podcast novel by Ronnie Blackwell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/serve-it-cold/" description="<![CDATA[Detective Jonny C.&nbsp; Speed's life can't get much better.&nbsp; He's booked into the  French Quarter's most luxurious guesthouse, and his day job as convenience store manager is 104 miles behind him in Catherine, Mississippi.&nbsp; He's already taken care of one pro-bono missing persons job since he's been in New Orleans, and his paying client's cheating wife is a beautiful and very accommodating exhibitionist.&nbsp; Are things too good to be true? Of course they are.&nbsp; Jonny starts to worry when his client turns up dead, but when the suspects start dropping, Jonny and his crack team of beauty queens, recovering addicts, professional athletes, computer hackers, and pampered dogs find themselves caught in a twisted scheme of revenge that threatens to turn the town of Catherine inside out.]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - A free podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
