<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Post-Apocalyptic podcast novels from Podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Immortals]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-immortals/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Immortals - a free podcast novel by Tracy Hickman]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-immortals/" description="<![CDATA[<p>The future story of United States Internment Camps ... of the dreams of the pre-deceased ... and of triumph beyond oblivion.</p><p>It's 2020, and an attempted cure for AIDS has mutated into a deadlier disease, V-CIDS. The U.S., under martial law, has set up &quot;quarantine centers&quot; in the Southwest. Searching for his gay son, Jon, media mogul Michael Barris smuggles himself into one of centers only to discover that it and the other centers are actually extermination camps. With a strange assortment of allies, including the leader of the camp's gay barracks, an army officer and a local cowboy, Barris precipitates an inmates' rebellion that promises the unraveling of the death-camp system and the overthrow of the government that established it.</p><p>As read and performed by Tracy and Laura Hickman. Published as a podiobook during the ten-year anniversary of its first printing.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Tannis Island]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/tannis-island/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Tannis Island - A free audiobook by Gavin L. Lowe]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/tannis-island/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Tannis Island - A free audiobook</h1><p>Debra Karin Hillgrave is faced with a dilemma; she has first hand experienced an epic discovery, and one greater than any other in mans history, but something has gone very wrong.&nbsp; The world of man is now in grave danger.&nbsp; Debra is not a skilled writer, and she knows it, but she must tell her story to the world.&nbsp; Her tale is hap-hazard, and confusing at first, but she knows this story may save the world from destruction, or possibly it will guarantee it.&nbsp; Debra must reveal everything in her own words, as she remembers the events, her own mistakes, and those of her father.&nbsp; The tale leads them to many parts of the world, and many long lost places.&nbsp; The Discovery of a place and a people man has not seen in over ten thousand years is only the beginning of the disaster that awaits mankind.&nbsp; Debra&apos;s plight becomes a race against time, and a fight against not only this lost civilization, but also against man himself.&nbsp; In the end, a choice must be made... live together in peace with them, or choose which race will die in war?</p>]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>

