<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Sci-Fi podcast novels from Podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" type="link" text="<![CDATA[]]>" url="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Dreams and Wings (A Searcher and Stallion story)]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/searcher-and-stallion-dreams-and-wings/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Dreams and Wings (A Searcher and Stallion story) - A free audiobook by Scott Howard]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/searcher-and-stallion-dreams-and-wings/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Dreams and Wings (A Searcher and Stallion story) - A free audiobook</h1><p>One Man, One Machine, One Destiny.&nbsp; Searcher awoke, alone on a laboratory table, with an ageless body and no knowledge of his past in a post apocalyptic world.&nbsp; Now in his exoskel, a powered suit of armor, he roams the galaxy with his robotic companion Stallion, seeking clues about his unknown origins.&nbsp; Meanwhile, His existence threatens to destroy balance among the ageless ones, a group of never dying humanoids that secretly run all aspects of human society in the shadows of the surviving colony worlds.&nbsp; Is the Searcher the key to humanity&apos;s salvation.....or its final destruction......A narrated story with actors, music and sound effects.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Mr. Dead Eyes]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/mr-dead-eyes/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Mr. Dead Eyes - A free audiobook by Roberto Scarlato]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/mr-dead-eyes/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Mr.&nbsp; Dead Eyes - A free audiobook</h1><p>Strange things happen when the lights go down in the shady setting of the Roseville Hospital.&nbsp; Unexplained sightings of a man resembling that of a doctor is known to walk the hallways in search of patients he has yet to help.&nbsp; His name was Derek R.&nbsp; Schillar, M.D.&nbsp; He was a complicated man with a desire to help people, but felt that he didn&apos;t do enough.&nbsp; Now, his friend has betrayed him, his wife thinks he&apos;s dead, a mysterious detective is on his trail, and the medical staff is perplexed at the growing number of inexplicable miraculous phenomena occurring within the hospital walls.&nbsp; Is there an answer?&nbsp; Why is a dying boy drawing pictures of this man?&nbsp; And just who is Mr.&nbsp; Dead Eyes?</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Tumbler]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/tumbler/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Tumbler - A free audiobook by Brand Gamblin]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/tumbler/" description="<![CDATA[Libby Carter wanted to get away from it all, so she took a job mining asteroids as far out into the inky blackness as possible.&nbsp; However, her escape turned into a trap, leaving her stuck in indentured servitude, living on a tiny rock in space.&nbsp; As she tries to dig herself out, she gains friends and finds adventure.&nbsp; Cave-in rescues, planetary collisions, and other mishaps keep her new family fighting to stay alive.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Marker Stone]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/marker-stone/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Marker Stone - A free audiobook by Paul J. Joseph]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/marker-stone/" description="<![CDATA[There&apos;s trouble on CMC-6 and it&apos;s been brewing for a long time.&nbsp; The golden age of space travel and asteroid mining has ended almost before it began and the bean counters have taken over.&nbsp; Sally Buds&apos; patients are all suffering from low-gravity syndrome because the Canadian Mining Consortium won&apos;t spring for gravity generators and the miners won&apos;t exercise.&nbsp; On top of this the station might be facing hard times.&nbsp; An expensive mining robot disappeared while surveying a region of space known and KEL-30 or &quot;Kelthy.&quot;.&nbsp; The problem was not in replacing the robot, but rather in the fact that the machine reappeared after the replacement had been ordered.&nbsp; How could the station personnel have been so incompetent?&nbsp; But Sally has another question.&nbsp; Where did the probe go when it was out of contact?&nbsp; Where did the strange rock samples come from and why did the images it saw not correspond with known star charts?&nbsp; Her new friend Ian Merryfield, an RAF shuttle pilot, wants to know, too.&nbsp; But the station commander does not.&nbsp; What is in the Kelthy region and why do things disappear there?&nbsp; Is it a hoax intended to scare away claim jumpers or is it the greatest discovery of the twenty-first century?&nbsp; Ian and Sally intend to find out even if it means risking their careers or even their lives.&nbsp; Not knowing would be worse.]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Borrowed Time]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/borrowed-time/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Borrowed Time - a free audiobook by Keith Hughes]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/borrowed-time/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Borrowed Time</h1><p>Ness Relevant is living on borrowed time.&nbsp; Molecular implosion, cellular degeneration, and dangerous men are but a few of the perils faced by the friendly and unassuming forensic photographer.</p><p>His quiet bachelorhood is interrupted when he receives an innocent looking device in the mail from a friend and former college professor.&nbsp; Ness unexpectedly finds himself embroiled in events driven by his friend's success.</p><p>This device is the focal point of a struggle that could overturn the whole world should Ness or his friend’s invention fall prey to greedy men.&nbsp; Before his time runs out Ness must travel back to an uncomfortable past to prevent an unthinkable future.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Plitone Revisionist]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-plitone-revisionist/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Plitone Revisionist - A free audiobook by Paul S. Jenkins]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-plitone-revisionist/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Plitone Revisionist - A free audiobook</h1><p>Will Captain Paola Mackie, independent space courier, thrown out of  her home ten years previously, escape the unsavory clutches of the  man who thinks she can lead him to the notorious Revisionist  mothership secretly orbiting within the Lutrana system and plotting  to destabilize its economy, its culture, its very way of life?&nbsp; Will Paola be reconciled with her estranged and aged father before  it&apos;s too late for him to pass on his onerous legacy to her?&nbsp; And will  she finally get it together with Nantuke Orlis, the Revisionist  President&apos;s enigmatic scout?&nbsp; The Plitone Revisionist is a fast-paced, sexy science-fiction  thriller that will keep you enthralled to the end -- and beyond.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Time Crime]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/time-crime/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Time Crime from &apos;Astounding Tales, published Feb-March 1955&apos; - a free audiobook by H. Beam Piper; narrated by Nathan Lowell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/time-crime/" description="<![CDATA[<center>From Astounding Tales Published February and March 1955</center><p>The Paratime Police had a real headache this time!&nbsp; Tracing one man in a population of millions is easy—compared to finding one gang hiding out on one of billions of probability lines!</p><p>This story from 1955 has rocket ships, time travel, slaves, post-hypnotic suggestions, drugged citizens, and a complete disregard for human rights.&nbsp; And those are the good guys.&nbsp; As a look back in time at &quot;classic&quot; science fiction, it's an interesting snapshot of a time when tobacco was common, sexism was unconscious, and female characters were a long way from Lara Croft.</p><center>Narrated by Nathan Lowell.</center>]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free audiobook by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
