<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Present Day Sci-Fi Podnovels from Podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Singularity]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/singularity/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Singularity - a free podcast novel by Bill DeSmedt]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/singularity/" description="<![CDATA[<p><b>What if</b> the cataclysmic Tunguska explosion of 1908 was caused, not by a meteor or a comet, but by a microscopic black hole?</p><p><b>What if</b>  that fantastic object - smaller than an atom, older than the stars, heavier than a mountain - is still down there, orbiting deep inside the earth, slowly consuming the planet?</p><p><b>What if</b>  only a rookie government agent and an uncannily-insightful consultant stand between a renegade Russian billionaire and his plans to use the black hole to change history - or end it?</p><p><b>What if</b>  it's all true?</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Servant and the Soothsayer]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-servant-and-the-soothsayer/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The Servant and the Soothsayer - A free audiobook by Eugene Fairfield]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-servant-and-the-soothsayer/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The Servant and the Soothsayer - by Eugene Fairfield</h1><p>Paulo, a domestic servant with a reputation for back-talk, is witness to a political murder.&nbsp; When a soothsayer is brought in to solve the crime, she sees Paulo as a tool: he can get close to the suspect, whereas she, as a known mind-reader, would instantly be recognized as a threat.&nbsp; But if Paulo works for her, he may get black-balled by the corporation that provides him job, room, and board.&nbsp; He will certainly get caught in a political conspiracy.&nbsp; If that weren&apos;t enough, there are stories that soothsayers can cause terrible psychic damage, and this one, people say, has something of a temper.</p>]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free audiobook by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>

