<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Sci-Fi: Time Travel podcasts novels</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[&apos;s audio dramas]]>" url="" type="link" text="<![CDATA[Podcast audio dramas from ]]>" description="<![CDATA[Podcast audio dramas from ]]>" />-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Time Zone]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/time-zone/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Time Zone - A free audiobook by Tom Lichtenberg]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/time-zone/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Time Zone - by Tom Lichtenberg</h1><p>This is not your father's time travel. There's no machine, there is no dial. There's no telling where or when you'll go. The only thing that can change is you. It will make you what it needs to make you, to fit you in, to make it work. And when you come back, that is if you come back, it won't be the same you at all. You're messing with the nature of things, and the nature of things does not like to be messed with, as Garrett Ronson and his friends find out, the hard way.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Borrowed Time]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/borrowed-time/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Borrowed Time - a free audiobook by Keith Hughes]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/borrowed-time/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Borrowed Time</h1><p>Ness Relevant is living on borrowed time.&nbsp; Molecular implosion, cellular degeneration, and dangerous men are but a few of the perils faced by the friendly and unassuming forensic photographer.</p><p>His quiet bachelorhood is interrupted when he receives an innocent looking device in the mail from a friend and former college professor.&nbsp; Ness unexpectedly finds himself embroiled in events driven by his friend's success.</p><p>This device is the focal point of a struggle that could overturn the whole world should Ness or his friend’s invention fall prey to greedy men.&nbsp; Before his time runs out Ness must travel back to an uncomfortable past to prevent an unthinkable future.</p>]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Time Crime]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/time-crime/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Time Crime from &apos;Astounding Tales, published Feb-March 1955&apos; - a free audiobook by H. Beam Piper; narrated by Nathan Lowell]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/time-crime/" description="<![CDATA[<center>From Astounding Tales Published February and March 1955</center><p>The Paratime Police had a real headache this time!&nbsp; Tracing one man in a population of millions is easy—compared to finding one gang hiding out on one of billions of probability lines!</p><p>This story from 1955 has rocket ships, time travel, slaves, post-hypnotic suggestions, drugged citizens, and a complete disregard for human rights.&nbsp; And those are the good guys.&nbsp; As a look back in time at &quot;classic&quot; science fiction, it's an interesting snapshot of a time when tobacco was common, sexism was unconscious, and female characters were a long way from Lara Croft.</p><center>Narrated by Nathan Lowell.</center>]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast audio drama from ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[ » podiobooks.com feed]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/?title=/" text="<![CDATA[ - a podcast novel by .  Brought to you by podiobooks.com]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>" />-->
	</body>
</opml>
