<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Sci-Fi Fantasy podcast novels from Podiobooks.com</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Amerindian 2192]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/amerindian-2192/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Amerindian 2192 - a free podcast novel by J. Scott Garibay]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/amerindian-2192/" description="<![CDATA[AmerIndian 2192 is a science-fiction novel that explores the intriguing possibilities of Native Americans in mankind&apos;s star flung future.&nbsp; AmerIndian 2192 presents the story of two brothers, Wovoka and Keokuk, restoring the Native American people to a Homeland where their vibrant culture can thrive.&nbsp; Lodge ships, Cybershaman rituals and Tsimshian high technology are all elements in this action-oriented tale of interstellar politics and personal struggles.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Traitor]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/traitor/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Traitor Book One of The Turner Chonicles - a free podcast novel by Mark Eller]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/traitor/" description="<![CDATA[Last Chance - a small town set on the edge of the far frontier.&nbsp; It is a place of gentle manners and common civility.&nbsp; After all, it should be since more than three quarters of its residents are women.&nbsp; However times change when a Talent Master runs rampant, savages threaten war, and an illegal militia from an alternate universe plans invasion and empire.&nbsp; A hero is needed.&nbsp; A Savior.&nbsp; Meet Aaron Turner, the small unassuming man who runs the Last Chance General Store.&nbsp; He is this town&&apos;s&mdash;this world&&apos;s&mdash;only hope.&nbsp; Unfortunately for the town, Aaron also happens to be a soldier and Militia spy whose job is to prepare the ground for the Militia&&apos;s invasion.&nbsp; To help him with this task, he has a cellar filled with advanced weaponry and the unique ability to teleport between the two worlds.&nbsp; However after a year of living within Last Chance, Aaron is no longer sure in which direction his loyalties lie.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The House of Grey]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-house-of-grey/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[The House of Grey - A free audiobook by Collin Earl]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-house-of-grey/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>The House of Grey - A free audiobook</h1><p>14-year-old Monson Grey faces the same challenges that any freshman high school kid would.&nbsp; Difficult classes, weird teachers, food fights...girls.&nbsp; Except Monson Grey is not Monson Grey.&nbsp; At least, when he looks at himself in the mirror, the scarred face staring back is not someone he recognizes.&nbsp; Now he finds himself attending an extraordinary school, the recipient of an incredible scholarship, among ridiculously rich classmates, and with no memory of how he got there or what to expect.&nbsp; As bizarre events start to unfold around him, Monson wonders what secrets lay locked in his hidden past.&nbsp; Add all this to a mysterious silver stone, an Indiana-Jones-copycat professor, Merlin the wizard, and even Atlantis, and you&apos;ll find yourself in a fantastic tale in which magic does exist and everything is never as it seems.</p>]]>" />
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Sparkling Death]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/sparkling-death/feed/" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Sparkling Death - A free audiobook by Mark Butler]]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/sparkling-death/" description="<![CDATA[<h1>Sparkling Death - A free audiobook</h1><p>Mankind has conquered the stars, spreading out to populate the galaxy.&nbsp; Despite technological advancements the human desire for greed and profit at the expense of others still remains.&nbsp; What is the secret on Altruis 4? It is a secret that keeps its people in virtual slavery, a secret that millions will die for.&nbsp; Vance Slater and his team careen from the shark-infested depths of Ligos to the pleasure palaces of Nuvo and into the limitless depths of space in an effort to find an answer.&nbsp; As the Confederation descends into war only Vance has a chance of stopping the hostilities, but he will have to act fast for closing in is an unstoppable foe that controls the power of absolute zero.&nbsp; Featuring a fast-paced action-packed story with just a bit of sexiness, Sparkling Death will take you on a roller-coaster ride through the technology and adventure of tomorrow.</p>]]>" />
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Collapse At Hidden Verse Three Three Two]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/collapse-at-hidden-verse-three-three-two/feed/" text="<![CDATA[DarkSide Sally&apos;s Podnovel: Collapse At Hidden Verse Three Three Two]]>" htmlUrl="http://darksidesally.com/" description="<![CDATA[The Multiverse Generator is failing.&nbsp; Dimensions threaten to collapse and entire populations will cease to exist unless it is reset.&nbsp; One being from each of more than five thousand verses has been acquired, and their DNA verified.&nbsp; Only one remains.&nbsp; His name is Timothy Rayburn and he is a resident of Earth.&nbsp; The Consolidation of Organized Systems has sent a ship to retrieve him.&nbsp; Timothy is a teenager failing speech class due to a paralyzing fear of public speaking.&nbsp; He soon learns that his problems are quite small compared to the impending collapse of all existence.&nbsp; He must overcome his fear if he is to survive not only the dangers of space travel and multiversal war, but himself.]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[ - a free podcast novel by ]]>" htmlUrl="" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
