<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<opml version='2.0'>
	<head>
		<title>Podcasts</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title='<![CDATA[]]>' url='http:///' type='link' text='<![CDATA[]]>' description='<![CDATA[]]>'/>-->
		<outline type='link' title='<![CDATA[Podiobooks.com]]>' url='http://podiobooks.com/' text='<![CDATA[Podiobooks.com&#039;s homepage]]>' description='<![CDATA[Podiobooks.com - Free online serialized fiction.]]>'/>
		<!--<outline title='<![CDATA[]]>' xmlUrl='' type='rss' htmlUrl='' text='<![CDATA[ - a free audiobook by ]]>' description='<![CDATA[]]>'/>-->
		<outline title='<![CDATA[Podiobooker]]>' xmlUrl='http://feedproxy.google.com/podiobooker' type='rss' text='<![CDATA[Podiobooker]]>' htmlUrl='http://podiobooks.com/blog/' description='<![CDATA[News &amp; updates from the staff of Podiobooks.com]]>'/>
		<!--<outline title='<![CDATA[]]>' xmlUrl='' type='rss' htmlUrl='' text='<![CDATA[ - a free audiobook by ]]>' description='<![CDATA[]]>'/>-->
		<outline title='<![CDATA[Collapse At Hidden Verse Three Three Two]]>' xmlUrl='http://podiobooks.com/title/collapse-at-hidden-verse-three-three-two/feed' text='<![CDATA[DarkSide Sally&#039;s Podnovel: Collapse At Hidden Verse Three Three Two]]>' htmlUrl='http://darksidesally.com/' description='<![CDATA[The Multiverse Generator is failing.  Dimensions threaten to collapse and entire populations will cease to exist unless it is reset.  One being from each of more than five thousand verses has been acquired, and their DNA verified.  Only one remains.  His name is Timothy Rayburn and he is a resident of Earth.  The Consolidation of Organized Systems has sent a ship to retrieve him. Timothy is a teenager failing speech class due to a paralyzing fear of public speaking. He soon learns that his problems are quite small compared to the impending collapse of all existence.  He must overcome his fear if he is to survive not only the dangers of space travel and multiversal war, but himself.]]>'/>
		<outline title='<![CDATA[Dorothea&#039;s Song]]>' xmlUrl='http://podiobooks.com/title/dorotheas-song/feed' type='rss' htmlUrl='http://losoil.typepad.com/losoilcom/novels/' text='<![CDATA[Dorothea&#039;s Song]]>' description='<![CDATA[&quot;Dorothea&#039;s Song&quot; tells the story of an ordinary boy named Peter who dreams up an extraordinary fantasy realm to flee the hardships of his own life. Inspired by classic high-fantasy themes, his tale has all the makings of a great adventure—a brave elvish warrior named Dorothea, a ruthless coven of witches, a renegade elf lord and a kingdom on the verge of collapse. But as the chaos intensifies in both worlds, instead of retreating from it, Peter is forced to take a daring stand in each.]]>'/>
		<outline title='<![CDATA[Jovian Gate Chronicles]]>' xmlUrl='http://podiobooks.com/title/jovian-gate-chronicles/feed' type='rss' htmlUrl='http://podiobooks.com/title/jovian-gate-chronicles/' text='<![CDATA[]]>' description='<![CDATA[What happens when humans, ruled by the Catholic Church and the Confederacy, cross paths with intelligent aliens that claim to be prophets from God? Find out in this short science fiction short story series that consists of four episodes (total length of the collection is 142 minutes) that tell individual stories of the Jovian Gate. Partake on a journey to learn who opened the gate, question whether aliens truly are communicating with God and learn what humanity&#039;s ultimate destiny will be.]]>'/>
		<outline title='<![CDATA[Interview for a Wizard]]>' xmlUrl='http://www.podiobooks.com/title/interview-for-a-wizard/feed/' type='rss' htmlUrl='http://www.podiobooks.com/title/interview-for-a-wizard/' text='<![CDATA[Interview for a Wizard]]>' description='<![CDATA[On Halloween night, the greatest vacation spot in the world is about to be scared to death.&nbsp; A dangerous and mad wizard has escaped from jail, and there is no one who can identify him.&nbsp; With only seven days left before Halloween, Jesse and wizard special agent Ch-U-Ch race to solve the mystery, but time is quickly running out.]]>'/>
		<outline title='<![CDATA[The Secret Society of Seven Sorcerers]]>' xmlUrl='http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-secret-society-of-seven-sorcerers/feed/' type='rss' htmlUrl='http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-secret-society-of-seven-sorcerers/' text='<![CDATA[The Secret Society of Seven Sorcerers]]>' description='<![CDATA[Nicholas Fidgewidge returns to claim Lord Bane&#039;s crystal ball causing Jesse to seek the wizard Ch-U-Ch&#039;s aid.&nbsp; Meanwhile, the remaining sorcerer&#039;s are being scared to death, and with Raven Claw out of jail the chase begins.&nbsp; However, things quickly become very complicated when the wizard&#039;s two teenage boys get involved.&nbsp; On Halloween night, Lord Alex will become the next Dark Sorcerer even if it means destroying everyone who knows of his initiation.&nbsp; Follow the wizard Ch-U-Ch, his cousin Ana and Jesse into the dark world of the Society as they try to prevent Lord Alex from joining the Circle of Seven and achieving a greater goal, to obtain the secret&#039;s of Lord Bane&#039;s crystal ball.&nbsp; On Halloween night, everything must remain a secret at any price.]]>'/>
		<outline title='<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book One: Invasion]]>' xmlUrl='http://podiobooks.com/title/secret-world-chronicle-book-one/feed/' type='rss' htmlUrl='http://podiobooks.com/title/secret-world-chronicle-book-one/' text='<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book One: Invasion - A free audiobook by Mercedes Lackey and Steve Libbey]]>' description='<![CDATA[Emerging mysteriously during World War II, metahumans became icons of the best - and worst - humanity had to offer. Yet sixty years later, the world still suffers from war, greed and madness. Worse, man&#039;s nadir of systematic cruelty returns with bizarre new weapons. The metahumans of Earth must find a way to defeat this powerful foe and discover what lurks behind the scenes - a secret world hidden from our own. Mercedes Lackey, one of fantasy&#039;s most beloved voices, and new talent Steve Libbey bring you a podcast series that catapults the classic superhero into the 21st century.Book One: Invasion starts the series off with a bang - a set of coordinated attacks by Nazi warriors in futuristic battle armor. We meet our cast of heroes in the midst of chaos: Belladonna Blue, a young azure-skinned healer; Victoria Victrix Nagy, a geomancer fighting panic attacks; Handsome Devil, whose luck is metahumanly good; Red Saviour, strident leader of an anachronistic Soviet team; Red Djinni, the shapeshifting criminal; and John Murdock, a fugitive super-soldier. Watching over them all is the Seraphym, descended from the Infinite to protect humanity.As the heroes fend off the blitzkrieg attack, they are left wondering what secrets have erupted from this hidden world, and whether, once unleashed, they can be contained. For there are clues that all is not what it seems...]]>'/>
		<outline title='<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book Two: The Hunt]]>' xmlUrl='http://podiobooks.com/title/secret-world-chronicle-book-two/feed/' type='rss' htmlUrl='http://podiobooks.com/title/secret-world-chronicle-book-two/' text='<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book Two: The Hunt - A free audiobook by Mercedes Lackey and Steve Libbey]]>' description='<![CDATA[The Hunt portrays the frenzied aftermath of the devastating Thule Society attacks. Famed fantasy and sci-fi author Mercedes Lackey and newcomer Steve Libbey have joined forces to create a superhero-themed braided novel podcast series called The Secret World Chronicle. The series depicts an ensemble cast of metahuman characters coping with worldwide attacks by a mysterious, technologically advanced Nazi secret society, and the ensuing chaos.&nbsp; The Secret World is a meeting ground for pulpy adventure and thoughtful science fiction speculation, where ordinary people are elevated above their fellow humans and must grapple with the consequences of their newfound abilities.]]>'/>
		<outline title='<![CDATA[The Zombie Chronicles: Escape]]>' xmlUrl='http://podiobooks.com/title/the-zombie-chronicles-escape/feed/' type='rss' htmlUrl='http://jamesmelzer.net/' text='<![CDATA[The Zombie Chronicles: Escape]]>' description='<![CDATA[When an asteroid passes by our planet and leaves a trail of death in its wake, a quarter of the population have become the living dead.Twenty-five years later the zombies are under the control of the government. Citizens are chosen to participate in Project Mirror, a cloning project in which their "mirrors" are used as food for the undead. When one man discovers that something in his blood is being used to create an army of super-zombies, he decides to help his mirror escape. In doing so he uncovers a secret so guarded that the powers that be will stop at nothing to eliminate him and all those that he loves.The Zombie Chronicles: Escape is the first book is a series of edge-of-your-seat thrillers that will take you on an adventure beyond your wildest imagination and leave you wanting more with each episode.]]>'/>
		<!--<outline title='<![CDATA[]]>' xmlUrl='' type='rss' htmlUrl='' text='<![CDATA[ - a free audiobook by ]]>' description='<![CDATA[]]>'/>-->
		<outline title='<![CDATA[Pieces]]>' xmlUrl='http://www.podiobooks.com/title/pieces/feed/' type='rss' htmlUrl='http://www.podiobooks.com/title/pieces/feed/' text='<![CDATA[Pieces - compiled by Nobilis]]>' description='<![CDATA[Joan&#039;s world has literally fallen apart.-  She lives in one tiny piece of the shattered universe, bounded on all sides by shimmering veils.&nbsp; When the creator god, calling himself "Cassius", stumbles into the cathedral where she lives, she is drawn into an adventure of cosmic proportions.The story is told through the cracked lens of seven experienced podcast authors.&nbsp; Nobilis, Christiana Ellis, Chris Lester, Graydancer, Paul S. Jenkins, Philippa Ballantine, Brandon Crose and John Tanzer take turns, chapter by chapter writing and reading episodes of the story.]]>'/>
		<outline title='<![CDATA[Black Star Passes]]>' xmlUrl='http://podiobooks.com/title/black-star-passes/feed' type='rss' htmlUrl='http://podiobooks.com/title/black-star-passes/' text='<![CDATA[Black Star Passes]]>' description='<![CDATA[Follow along with Arcot, Morey, and Wade as they discover a revolutionary form of propulsion, visit our neighboring planets, and go up against aliens from a rogue solar system that passes close to our own.&nbsp; These three stories (Piracy Preferred, Solarite, and The Black Star Passes) were originally published as a serial in Amazing Stories magazine.Read by Scott D. Farquhar of Prometheus Radio Theatre.]]>'/>
		<outline title='<![CDATA[Heart of the Ronin]]>' xmlUrl='http://podiobooks.com/title/heart-of-the-ronin/feed' type='rss' htmlUrl='http://podiobooks.com/title/heart-of-the-ronin/' text='<![CDATA[Heart of the Ronin - A free audiobook by Travis Heermann]]>' description='<![CDATA[Thirteenth-century Japan is a dangerous place, even in a time of peace.&nbsp; Capricious gods, shape-changing animals, and bloodthirsty demons are as real and unpleasant as a gang of vicious bandits.&nbsp; From the wilderness emerges a young, idealistic warrior with his father&#039;s mysterious sword on his hip, a wise, sarcastic dog at his side, and a yearning in his heart to find a worthy master.&nbsp; He dreams only of being samurai. Little does he suspect the agony and glory that await him when his dreams come true.Finding a master should be easy for a warrior as skilled as Ken&#039;ishi, but the generations-long wars for the Imperial throne have ended.&nbsp; The land has settled into an uneasy peace and cast multitudes of proud, powerful warriors to the four winds.&nbsp; The new peace means that these masterless warriors, ronin, often must stoop to crime and banditry to feed themselves.&nbsp; Ken&#039;ishi finds himself plagued by the hatred and mistrust of peasants and samurai alike.When he saves a noble maiden from a pack of bandits, he and his faithful dog become enmeshed in the intrigues of samurai lords, vengeful constables, Mongol spies, and a shadowy underworld crime boss known as Green Tiger.&nbsp; But Ken&#039;ishi has a few secret weapons of his own, granted to him by his mysterious past and his magical upbringing.&nbsp; If only he knew more about his mysterious past, his parents&#039; murder, and the sword that seems to want to talk to him. . . .Heart of the Ronin is an action-packed historical fantasy, set against the backdrop of ancient intrigue and impending war, the first of a sweeping three-part epic filled with deadly duels and climactic battles.&nbsp; Creatures of folklore and myth are as real as the katana in one&#039;s hand.&nbsp; And just as deadly.]]>'/>
		<outline title='<![CDATA[The Corridor]]>' xmlUrl='http://podiobooks.com/title/the-corridor/feed' type='rss' htmlUrl='http://podiobooks.com/title/the-corridor/' text='<![CDATA[The Corridor - A free audiobook by Zan]]>' description='<![CDATA[The Corridor is a fantasy/horror story about Stuart Morrow, a man who has lost all hope and reason to live. However, a strange coincidence brings him unexpectedly into contact with a multitude of worlds beyond our own. Hunted by a despot who rules over countless alternate realities, Stuart&#039;s only hope is to seek help amongst the assortment of bizarre and grotesque characters who await him in the Corridor.]]>'/>
	</body>
</opml>
