<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<opml version="2.0">
	<head>
		<title>Podcasts</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" url="http:///" type="link" text="<![CDATA[]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline type="link" title="<![CDATA[Podiobooks.com]]>" url="http://www.podiobooks.com/" text="<![CDATA[Podiobooks.com&#039;s homepage]]>" description="<![CDATA[Podiobooks.com - Free online serialized fiction.]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - A free audiobook by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Podiobooker]]>" xmlUrl="http://feedproxy.google.com/podiobooker" type="rss" text="<![CDATA[Podiobooker]]>" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/blog/" description="<![CDATA[News &amp; updates from the staff of Podiobooks.com]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - A free audiobook by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Collapse At Hidden Verse Three Three Two]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/collapse-at-hidden-verse-three-three-two/feed/" text="<![CDATA[DarkSide Sally&#039;s Podnovel: Collapse At Hidden Verse Three Three Two]]>" htmlUrl="http://darksidesally.com/" description="<![CDATA[The Multiverse Generator is failing.  Dimensions threaten to collapse and entire populations will cease to exist unless it is reset.  One being from each of more than five thousand verses has been acquired, and their DNA verified.  Only one remains.  His name is Timothy Rayburn and he is a resident of Earth.  The Consolidation of Organized Systems has sent a ship to retrieve him. Timothy is a teenager failing speech class due to a paralyzing fear of public speaking. He soon learns that his problems are quite small compared to the impending collapse of all existence.  He must overcome his fear if he is to survive not only the dangers of space travel and multiversal war, but himself.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Dorothea&#039;s Song]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/dorotheas-song/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://losoil.typepad.com/losoilcom/novels/" text="<![CDATA[Dorothea&#039;s Song]]>" description="<![CDATA[&quot;Dorothea&#039;s Song&quot; tells the story of an ordinary boy named Peter who dreams up an extraordinary fantasy realm to flee the hardships of his own life. Inspired by classic high-fantasy themes, his tale has all the makings of a great adventure—a brave elvish warrior named Dorothea, a ruthless coven of witches, a renegade elf lord and a kingdom on the verge of collapse. But as the chaos intensifies in both worlds, instead of retreating from it, Peter is forced to take a daring stand in each.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Jovian Gate Chronicles]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/jovian-gate-chronicles/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/jovian-gate-chronicles/" text="<![CDATA[]]>" description="<![CDATA[What happens when humans, ruled by the Catholic Church and the Confederacy, cross paths with intelligent aliens that claim to be prophets from God? Find out in this short science fiction short story series that consists of four episodes (total length of the collection is 142 minutes) that tell individual stories of the Jovian Gate. Partake on a journey to learn who opened the gate, question whether aliens truly are communicating with God and learn what humanity&#039;s ultimate destiny will be.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Interview for a Wizard]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/interview-for-a-wizard/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/interview-for-a-wizard/" text="<![CDATA[Interview for a Wizard]]>" description="<![CDATA[On Halloween night, the greatest vacation spot in the world is about to be scared to death.&nbsp; A dangerous and mad wizard has escaped from jail, and there is no one who can identify him.&nbsp; With only seven days left before Halloween, Jesse and wizard special agent Ch-U-Ch race to solve the mystery, but time is quickly running out.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Secret Society of Seven Sorcerers]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-secret-society-of-seven-sorcerers/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-secret-society-of-seven-sorcerers/" text="<![CDATA[The Secret Society of Seven Sorcerers]]>" description="<![CDATA[Nicholas Fidgewidge returns to claim Lord Bane&#039;s crystal ball causing Jesse to seek the wizard Ch-U-Ch&#039;s aid.&nbsp; Meanwhile, the remaining sorcerer&#039;s are being scared to death, and with Raven Claw out of jail the chase begins.&nbsp; However, things quickly become very complicated when the wizard&#039;s two teenage boys get involved.&nbsp; On Halloween night, Lord Alex will become the next Dark Sorcerer even if it means destroying everyone who knows of his initiation.&nbsp; Follow the wizard Ch-U-Ch, his cousin Ana and Jesse into the dark world of the Society as they try to prevent Lord Alex from joining the Circle of Seven and achieving a greater goal, to obtain the secret&#039;s of Lord Bane&#039;s crystal ball.&nbsp; On Halloween night, everything must remain a secret at any price.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book One: Invasion]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/secret-world-chronicle-book-one/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/secret-world-chronicle-book-one/" text="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book One: Invasion - A free audiobook by Mercedes Lackey and Steve Libbey]]>" description="<![CDATA[Emerging mysteriously during World War II, metahumans became icons of the best - and worst - humanity had to offer. Yet sixty years later, the world still suffers from war, greed and madness. Worse, man&#039;s nadir of systematic cruelty returns with bizarre new weapons. The metahumans of Earth must find a way to defeat this powerful foe and discover what lurks behind the scenes - a secret world hidden from our own. Mercedes Lackey, one of fantasy&#039;s most beloved voices, and new talent Steve Libbey bring you a podcast series that catapults the classic superhero into the 21st century.Book One: Invasion starts the series off with a bang - a set of coordinated attacks by Nazi warriors in futuristic battle armor. We meet our cast of heroes in the midst of chaos: Belladonna Blue, a young azure-skinned healer; Victoria Victrix Nagy, a geomancer fighting panic attacks; Handsome Devil, whose luck is metahumanly good; Red Saviour, strident leader of an anachronistic Soviet team; Red Djinni, the shapeshifting criminal; and John Murdock, a fugitive super-soldier. Watching over them all is the Seraphym, descended from the Infinite to protect humanity.As the heroes fend off the blitzkrieg attack, they are left wondering what secrets have erupted from this hidden world, and whether, once unleashed, they can be contained. For there are clues that all is not what it seems...]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book Two: The Hunt]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/secret-world-chronicle-book-two/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/secret-world-chronicle-book-two/" text="<![CDATA[The Secret World Chronicle, Book Two: The Hunt - A free audiobook by Mercedes Lackey and Steve Libbey]]>" description="<![CDATA[The Hunt portrays the frenzied aftermath of the devastating Thule Society attacks. Famed fantasy and sci-fi author Mercedes Lackey and newcomer Steve Libbey have joined forces to create a superhero-themed braided novel podcast series called The Secret World Chronicle. The series depicts an ensemble cast of metahuman characters coping with worldwide attacks by a mysterious, technologically advanced Nazi secret society, and the ensuing chaos.&nbsp; The Secret World is a meeting ground for pulpy adventure and thoughtful science fiction speculation, where ordinary people are elevated above their fellow humans and must grapple with the consequences of their newfound abilities.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Zombie Chronicles: Escape]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-zombie-chronicles-escape/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://jamesmelzer.net/" text="<![CDATA[The Zombie Chronicles: Escape]]>" description="<![CDATA[When an asteroid passes by our planet and leaves a trail of death in its wake, a quarter of the population have become the living dead.Twenty-five years later the zombies are under the control of the government. Citizens are chosen to participate in Project Mirror, a cloning project in which their "mirrors" are used as food for the undead. When one man discovers that something in his blood is being used to create an army of super-zombies, he decides to help his mirror escape. In doing so he uncovers a secret so guarded that the powers that be will stop at nothing to eliminate him and all those that he loves.The Zombie Chronicles: Escape is the first book is a series of edge-of-your-seat thrillers that will take you on an adventure beyond your wildest imagination and leave you wanting more with each episode.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Pieces]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/pieces/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/pieces/feed/" text="<![CDATA[Pieces - compiled by Nobilis]]>" description="<![CDATA[Joan&#039;s world has literally fallen apart.-  She lives in one tiny piece of the shattered universe, bounded on all sides by shimmering veils.&nbsp; When the creator god, calling himself "Cassius", stumbles into the cathedral where she lives, she is drawn into an adventure of cosmic proportions.The story is told through the cracked lens of seven experienced podcast authors.&nbsp; Nobilis, Christiana Ellis, Chris Lester, Graydancer, Paul S. Jenkins, Philippa Ballantine, Brandon Crose and John Tanzer take turns, chapter by chapter writing and reading episodes of the story.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Black Star Passes]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/black-star-passes/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/black-star-passes/" text="<![CDATA[Black Star Passes]]>" description="<![CDATA[Follow along with Arcot, Morey, and Wade as they discover a revolutionary form of propulsion, visit our neighboring planets, and go up against aliens from a rogue solar system that passes close to our own.&nbsp; These three stories (Piracy Preferred, Solarite, and The Black Star Passes) were originally published as a serial in Amazing Stories magazine.Read by Scott D. Farquhar of Prometheus Radio Theatre.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Heart of the Ronin]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/heart-of-the-ronin/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/heart-of-the-ronin/" text="<![CDATA[Heart of the Ronin - A free audiobook by Travis Heermann]]>" description="<![CDATA[Thirteenth-century Japan is a dangerous place, even in a time of peace.&nbsp; Capricious gods, shape-changing animals, and bloodthirsty demons are as real and unpleasant as a gang of vicious bandits.&nbsp; From the wilderness emerges a young, idealistic warrior with his father&#039;s mysterious sword on his hip, a wise, sarcastic dog at his side, and a yearning in his heart to find a worthy master.&nbsp; He dreams only of being samurai. Little does he suspect the agony and glory that await him when his dreams come true.Finding a master should be easy for a warrior as skilled as Ken&#039;ishi, but the generations-long wars for the Imperial throne have ended.&nbsp; The land has settled into an uneasy peace and cast multitudes of proud, powerful warriors to the four winds.&nbsp; The new peace means that these masterless warriors, ronin, often must stoop to crime and banditry to feed themselves.&nbsp; Ken&#039;ishi finds himself plagued by the hatred and mistrust of peasants and samurai alike.When he saves a noble maiden from a pack of bandits, he and his faithful dog become enmeshed in the intrigues of samurai lords, vengeful constables, Mongol spies, and a shadowy underworld crime boss known as Green Tiger.&nbsp; But Ken&#039;ishi has a few secret weapons of his own, granted to him by his mysterious past and his magical upbringing.&nbsp; If only he knew more about his mysterious past, his parents&#039; murder, and the sword that seems to want to talk to him. . . . Heart of the Ronin is an action-packed historical fantasy, set against the backdrop of ancient intrigue and impending war, the first of a sweeping three-part epic filled with deadly duels and climactic battles.&nbsp; Creatures of folklore and myth are as real as the katana in one&#039;s hand.&nbsp; And just as deadly.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Corridor]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-corridor/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-corridor/" text="<![CDATA[The Corridor - A free audiobook by Zan]]>" description="<![CDATA[The Corridor is a fantasy/horror story about Stuart Morrow, a man who has lost all hope and reason to live. However, a strange coincidence brings him unexpectedly into contact with a multitude of worlds beyond our own. Hunted by a despot who rules over countless alternate realities, Stuart&#039;s only hope is to seek help amongst the assortment of bizarre and grotesque characters who await him in the Corridor.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Children of Rhatlan]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/children-of-rhatlan/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/children-of-rhatlan" text="<![CDATA[Children of Rhatlan - A free audiobook by Jonathan Fesmire]]>" description="<![CDATA[Garum and Vayin are &quot;duals&quot;, twins trapped in each other&#039;s minds and bodies, sharing one life. When a deranged wizard hunts them, whom can they turn to? Their mentor? The city guard Vayin loves? The Wizards&#039; Guild? In a world that hates duals, anyone could be their enemy, and one misstep could get them killed.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Beautiful Red]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/beautiful-red/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/beautiful-red/" text="<![CDATA[Beautiful Red - A free audiobook by M. Darusha Wehm]]>" description="<![CDATA[The future is boring. Technology has solved the world&#039;s most pressing problems, leaving people with tedious work and mundane play. Jack is a Security Officer Class 5, which sounds important, but isn&#039;t. However, her banal life as a cubicle worker by day and tinkerer by night is interrupted when she discovers that her employer&#039;s computer system has been invaded.Jack enlists the help of her only friends - her co-worker, Gilles and Adrian, an online friend she&#039;s never met - to help her track down the source of the invasion. Her investigation leads her to a shadowy group called the Red, where Jack learns that not everyone lives a life of quiet servitude.Even though she believes that the Red are responsible for a series of gruesome attacks, Jack begins to become attracted to their worldview. In her search for the people responsible for the attacks, she confronts the leaders of the group as well as her own burgeoning sense of self-awareness.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Bloodblaths]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/bloodbaths/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/bloodbaths/" text="<![CDATA[The Bloodbaths  - A free audiobook by Steve Libbey]]>" description="<![CDATA[The Bloodbaths is the first book of Steve Libbey&#039;s new Aqua Pura Trilogy, a sword and sandal fantasy featuring a plumber on an epic quest to win back his beloved. Mercedes Lackey says: &quot;Steve Libbey gives the &#039;sword-and-sandal&#039; epic a kick in the tunic and  propels it into the gestalt of the 21st century, with an everyman hero whose brains triumph over brawn.&quot;  Crixus Oraan is a water artesan, an engineer who builds aqueducts and piping for bathhouses and mansions in the empire of Rond (which bears a resemblance to our own Roman Empire). His guild has entrusted him with a large sum of gold to establish a branch in the up-and-coming coastal town of Restia. In a misguided effort to win enough gold to buy a lavish house for his new fiancé Kharrina, he loses the guild&#039;s gold in a card game.A shady sea captain present at the game-and possibly responsible for fleecing him-offers to sneak him off to the wild and mysterious continent of Minq. Afraid to lose his status in society for his crime, he agrees, hoping to gain back the gold he lost and compensate the guild back in Rond.In this first volume in the bold new Aqua Pura Trilogy, Crixus finds employment with the Lamiae of Nistru, a cruel society where those at the top bathe in the lifeblood of those on the bottom. Will his conscience allow him to finish the job?By turns dark, comedic, erotic and thrilling, The Bloodbaths is a book that transcends genre to stand on its own.This podcast is read by SWC&#039;s own Veronica Giguere.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The House of Grey]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-house-of-grey/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-house-of-grey/" text="<![CDATA[The House of Grey - A free audiobook by Collin Earl]]>" description="<![CDATA[14-year-old Monson Grey faces the same challenges that any freshman high school kid would. Difficult classes, weird teachers, food fights...girls.  Except Monson Grey is not Monson Grey.  At least, when he looks at himself in the mirror, the scarred face staring back is not someone he recognizes.  Now he finds himself attending an extraordinary school, the recipient of an incredible scholarship, among ridiculously rich classmates, and with no memory of how he got there or what to expect.  As bizarre events start to unfold around him, Monson wonders what secrets lay locked in his hidden past.  Add all this to a mysterious silver stone, an Indiana-Jones-copycat professor, Merlin the wizard, and even Atlantis, and you&#039;ll find yourself in a fantastic tale in which magic does exist and everything is never as it seems.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Legon Awakening]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/legon-awakening/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/legon-awakening/" text="<![CDATA[ - A free audiobook by yn jen]]>" description="<![CDATA[Set in a world that is not our own, Legon Awakening takes you through an epic journey into a land full of imagination and innovation.Join Legon and his sister, Sasha, search to understand their true heritage, confused at the possibility that of being part human and part elf. Surrounded by elves, the newly introduced Iumenta race, Dragons and Humans; Legon and Sasha&#039;s lives are filled with adventure and fantasy on their search for answers as they begin an epic journey of discovery; not to mention the incredible battle scenes which will be surely to capture your imagination!]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[In the Service of Samurai]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/in-the-service-of-samurai/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/in-the-service-of-samurai/" text="<![CDATA[In the Service of Samurai - A free audiobook by Gloria Oliver]]>" description="<![CDATA[The choice: Serve the undead or become one of them.Toshi never expected the strange visitor who one evening stepped foot insidehis master&#039;s shop. A samurai smelling of the sea, dripping on the ground,algae strung from his armor. For the first time in his life, he discoversthat monsters do roam the earth. And this one has been specifically lookingfor him.Dragged from his home and all he has ever known, Toshi must now use hisacquired skills in foreign maps to help the creatures who have taken him.Yet at every turn there are problems. There are even those seeking toterminate his very life, not wanting his new master to succeed in hisassigned task. And when they do find it, Toshi discovers his new master&#039;senemies have prepared for their eventual arrival, leaving him the only onecapable of recovering what has been lost. Can he do what even the undeadcannot? Or will he fail and be forced to wander the world as one of them?]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Seventh Mountain (Chronicles of a Magi, Book 1)]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-seventh-mountain-chronicles-of-a-magi-book-1/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-seventh-mountain-chronicles-of-a-magi-book-1/" text="<![CDATA[The Seventh Mountain (Chronicles of a Magi, Book 1) - A free audiobook by Gene Curtis]]>" description="<![CDATA[A dream, surreal and frightening, begins the path of 12 year old Mark Young&#039;s future; a path set long before he was even born. Fortunately, it&#039;s not a path he&#039;s doomed to walk alone. His course leads to true friends, fortune, and a place where he learns to wield great power.This place is The Seventh Mountain, the place where Magi train. The Seventh Mountain conceals the direst legend known to man. Mark&#039;s fate lies within.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[New World Orders]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/new-world-orders/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/new-world-orders/" text="<![CDATA[New World Orders - A free Audiobook by Edward G. Talbot]]>" description="<![CDATA[In the nineteen-sixties, a group of wealthy men concludes that it&#039;s already too late to stop global warming from destroying the planet. But they have a plan to save themselves.Twenty years later, Jack Crowley and Jim Patterson stumble onto the conspiracy, and every answer they find is accompanied by more questions - and more deaths.Jack is a former idealist, turned cynical by his years working as a New York tabloid editor. But his enthusiasm returns as he looks into the work of a NASA scientist who tells Jack about cover-ups at the space agency.  Jim is a detective with little patience for conspiracy nuts. But he hates loose ends, and is unable to let go of the inconsistencies in another suspicious NASA death.  Soon, his investigation leads him to Jack, and they join forces.As Jack and Jim dig deeper, they are targeted by the type of killers that don&#039;t usually miss. From Washington to Las Vegas to the Middle East, they manage to stay one step ahead of their pursuers in a race to expose the truth, and maybe, just maybe, save the world.]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[Terra Incognita]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/terra-incognita/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/terra-incognita/" text="<![CDATA[Terra Incognita - A free Audiobook by Gary Hicks]]>" description="<![CDATA[Drawn together apparently by the hand of fate, Trent and Cole escape the oppressive totalitarian domed city that has nurtured them all their lives.  Outside they discover a world they could never have imagined. They are pursued by the city Militia, intent on returning them to the secretive entity that oversees every facet of the city.  They are joined by Floyd, who turns against the Militia; but then they are captured once more and once again freed by those they would have considered most unlikely to help them.  The trio begin to understand the truth of their world and must decide for whom they will fight in the coming wars...]]>"/>-->
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Masha Chronicles]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-masha-chronicles/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-masha-chronicles/" text="<![CDATA[The Masha Chronoicles - A free audiobook by Lisa Beth Kovetz]]>" description="<![CDATA[A noir page-turner detailing the roller-coaster adventures of Masha, a reluctant young assassin.  When Masha meets American businessman, Charlie Hammerschmidt, she thinks she&#039;s found the ticket out of Kiev&#039;s underworld.  When Charlie is murdered in her apartment, she discovers the ride is just beginning.The Masha Chronicles is a full cast PodioDrama featuring Margot Avery, Nina Bernstein-Simmons, Brendan Corbalis, John Farrell, Maggie Low, Willard Morgan.  Engineered by Dan Molad.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Origin Scroll, Book 1 of the Targa Trilogy]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/origin-scroll/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/origin-scroll/" text="<![CDATA[Origin Scroll, Book 1 of the Targa Trilogy - A free audiobook by Richard S. Tuttle]]>" description="<![CDATA[Origin Scroll is the first volume of the Targa Trilogy and the cornerstone of the epic fantasy Alcea Collection which spans sixteen volumes in three series.Alexander Tork is an apprentice lumberman, a fifteen year old who is forced to take the lead when his village is attacked by a pack of vicious beasts. But darker things lurk in the lands of Targa and Cordonia, an evil questing for an artifact that will shake the very Universe. Alex, and two more unknown youths, Oscar and Jenneva, are the only ones who can prevent the end of their universe... they just don&#039;t know it yet.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Dark Quest, Book 2 of the Targa Trilogy]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/dark-quest/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/dark-quest/" text="<![CDATA[Dark Quest, Book 2 of the Targa Trilogy - A free audiobook by Richard S. Tuttle]]>" description="<![CDATA[Dark Quest is the second volume of the Targa Trilogy, which is the cornerstone of the epic fantasy Alcea Collection which spans seventeen volumes in three series. The Targa Trilogy began with Origin Scroll.The evil magician, Sarac, has been banished to another Universe, but his followers strive to free him. Sarac&#039;s assistant. Mordac, gathers hundreds of dark magicians and instructs them to gather every book in the world, no matter what it takes. While his minions brutally execute his orders, Mordac plots the downfall of all of the governments on the continent. As Alexander and Jenneva try to halt the coming chaos, their own country turns against them.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Lost Gods]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/lost-gods/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/lost-gods/" text="<![CDATA[Lost Gods - A free audiobook by Drew Beatty]]>" description="<![CDATA[Kweku Anansi is just another member of the African diaspora, trying to make a place for himself in his adopted home of Toronto, Canada. He dreams of better days, of a time when he could be stop running small time cons just to make the rent. He dreams of the life he used to live, centuries ago when he was revered as a god.A chance encounter with a fellow con man with a dark and secretive past of his own, plunges them both into the dark world of the lost gods, gods who would do anything to be worshipped again. Including destroying the world, if necessary.How far will Anansi go to reclaim his godhood? What will he give up to have true power again? The answers can be found in &quot;Lost Gods&quot;, a new weekly podcast novel from author Drew Beatty.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Grizelda]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/grizelda/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/grizelda/" text="<![CDATA[Grizelda - A free audiobook by Margaret R. Taylor]]>" description="<![CDATA[In the Republic of Corvain, anybody who has a hint of magical power is rounded up and thrown into prison.  They&#039;re doing it to defend the new nation, says the revolutionary government - defend it from the sorcerers and sorceresses who used to be the lackeys of the man-eating Auks in the bad old days of the monarcy.  When Grizelda, a young seamstress from the poorer part of the capitol city, suddenly finds herself the government&#039;s target, she fears she is done for.But in prison she meets a group of rat-riding pixies and earns their undying friendship by mending their clothes.  In exchange, they help her to escape and seek refuge in the world below the city.  Living underground means Grizelda has to adapt to the strange customs of the goblins, a cheerless bunch who storm around muttering about the dictatorship of the proletariat.  Not content to remain in exile, Grizelda winds up entangled with a group of human revolutionaries.  Together they hatch a daring plan to return the Republic to its original ideals, before it decayed into a police state.  If their plan is going to work, Grizelda will have to get Communist goblins, irresponsible pixies, and revolutionaries still deeply mistrustful of magic to work together.]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Noggle Stones]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/noggle-stones/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/noggle-stones/" text="<![CDATA[Noggle Stones - A free audiobook by Wil Radcliff]]>" description="<![CDATA[Shunned by his people and tormented by nightmare visions, Bugbear, the mad goblin scholar, ventures into the wilderness with his ne&#039;er-do-well cousin, Tudmire, to seek out an ancient ruin and the lost wisdom it holds.Soon the cousins find themselves embroiled in cosmic events as their magical world of Annwfn is merged with 19th Century Earth after an accident concerning a mysterious scroll Tudmire acquires in a crooked game of Noggle Stones. While fleeing the enraged ogres they cheated, Bugbear and Tudmire happen upon Martin Manchester, who appears to be a creature of mythology known as a human. Bugbear takes Manchester as his apprentice, agreeing to teach him the empowering ways of Non-Logical Thought.  The trio soon discovers that dark forces have aligned against them, and the two worlds may have been merged only to be destroyed!]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[The Mark of a Druid]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-mark-of-a-druid/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/the-mark-of-a-druid/" text="<![CDATA[The Mark of a Druid - A free audiobook by Rhonda R. Carpenter]]>" description="<![CDATA[When twenty-six-year-old Eve McCormick awakes, the images from her nightmare are indelible. The dream feels so real she must force herself to get a grip. This experience is just the beginning for Eve, a Los Angeles clinical hypnotherapist and researcher investigating whether reincarnation is fact or fiction.Unstoppable visions of an ancient lifetime steal days from her. The danger escalates when she wakes up physically injured and marked with a strange symbol. While Eve battles the past to maintain her sanity and safety, her project is jeopardized as another researcher&#039;s attempts to take over. One partner dies and another is accused of inappropriate conduct. Eve and her friend, Dr. Andrea McMurray, don&#039;t believe in coincidence and probe their shared visions for answers. On the other side of the Atlantic, Welshman Ryerson Sanders is haunted by his dreams and believes Eve&#039;s research project can help him. For both of them, an ancient Celtic prophecy and long-sought revenge entangles the past with the present. A druidess and a shape-shifter must join to save the druid way of life, while a queen conspires to kill Erin&#039;s only high king. Will the oaths and agendas of the past reach across the centuries to strengthen or to destroy?]]>"/>
		<outline title="<![CDATA[Heirs of the New Earth]]>" xmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/heirs-of-the-new-earth/feed/" type="rss" htmlUrl="http://www.podiobooks.com/title/heirs-of-the-new-earth/" text="<![CDATA[Heirs of the New Earth - A free audiobook by David Lee Summers]]>" description="<![CDATA[The Earth has gone silent. John Mark Ellis and the crew of the Sanson are sent to investigate. When they arrive, they find vast alien machines known as Clusters in orbit. Fearing the worst, they land and discover that the once overcrowded, polluted Earth has become a paradise of sorts. The problem is over half the population is dead or missing and the planet's leaders don't seem to care. As Ellis works to unravel the mystery, sudden gravitational shifts from the galaxy's center indicate something even worse is in the offing. Can Ellis save the galaxy from the heirs of the new Earth?]]>"/>
		<!--<outline title="<![CDATA[]]>" xmlUrl="" type="rss" htmlUrl="" text="<![CDATA[ - A free audiobook by ]]>" description="<![CDATA[]]>"/>-->
	</body>
</opml>
